[
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR GAME",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=204675",
    "date": "February 16, 2025",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. Last night after the Dunk Contest, Ja said he might be willing to give it a shot.  Giannis chimed in.  Zach LaVine also mentioned it.  Is there any part of you that regrets never doing it?  And with a procession of people maybe saying they might do it, would it propel you to give it a chance at next year's All-Star Game?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   No, there's no part of me that has regrets about not doing it.  Obviously, I had a couple moments where I wanted to do it, and it just never worked out that way going into the following season, either, because of injuries or I just wasn't up for it. But I don't know.  If those guys do do it, those are superstars in our league, and obviously we know the athleticism of the guys that you just named.  It would be pretty cool.  We'll see."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Obviously your team, the Lakers, made a huge deal a couple weeks ago to trade for Luka Doncic.  I'm wondering if in any way having a 25-year-old talent like that makes you think about the end of your career and if it could be extended further than year 23, et cetera?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   No, I have not given it that type of thought.  Just the excitement of being able to add a caliber player like that, a generational talent like that to our franchise, it's something that's given me energy. I'm looking forward to seeing what we can do.  We only had two games so far, and I believe he's been on a minutes restriction since he came back from the calf.  He hasn't played since Christmas, I believe.  As he continues to get in form, I think we could be really good going down the stretch.  But we'll see what happens."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Curious your thoughts of the overall state of the league.  You've been through a lot of stuff in your two decades.  Where do you find the game to be right now?  What ways could it be better?  What ways maybe is it better now than it was when you started?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Well, the fact of how many international channels and places and players that come into our league and viewers we have all over the world, the game continues to expand, and that's a great thing for our game. We love our game.  The game of basketball is beautiful.  It's done so many things for us players and everybody in this room, as well, to be able to cover it.  We're always just trying to figure out ways how we can continue to build the game, how we can continue to make it better and better.  It's better from when I entered the league in 2003, and hopefully it continues to be even better when I'm done playing, as well."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You had said a couple months ago that you had thoughts about where the game was going and you talked about threes and things like that and you said this wasn't the proper forum to discuss it.  I wonder if today is a more proper forum to discuss it.  Ideally if you could have the game look the way you think is the best way to play basketball, would it look like it's played now, or would there be differences?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I mean, the game can always continue to get better and better.  But that's just for all of us to try to figure out what's best for our sport.  We want to continue to engage in our viewership, continue to engage in our consumer that loves our sport and continue to understand that the guys that play the game and have their minds on how we can continue to improve the game. To answer your question, no, this is definitely not the room.  There's too many faces I have no idea who it is in here.  I would not open up to this room about that. But I'm definitely always trying to have thoughts and questions and hopefully solutions.  That's the most important, of how we can continue to build our game.  That's what's most important."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. This is not the how-many-years-left question, but now that you're 40, year 22, all these accolades, obviously, how do you balance still being in the moment and trying to win championships and doing all the things that you're wired to do versus knowing that the finish line is obviously closer and appreciating what you've done and where you are?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I think they merge right into one another.  I think I have a great appreciation for the moment because I understand that it's not going to be a lot of moments going into the future, whenever that time comes. You have an opportunity to really, really truly appreciate every single moment and take it all in, no matter the good, the bad, the adversity, whatever comes with the day-to-day process of being a professional and still trying to play for championships, but more importantly just engaging in every single day and every single moment of being able to do what I love to do, and I've been doing it for such a long time, been a professional for 22 years.  I've been playing the game at a level where coaches and referees was involved since I was eight.  So, this is something I've always dived into and always loved the process. I think they just intertwine together."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You have a huge fan base in China; do you have any plans to visit China?  What's your message to show the fans there who adore you?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Yeah, I've been to China a lot, and I've always had a great deal of respect for the culture, for the way they love the game of basketball, and every time I've went and left, they've always welcomed me with open arms to come back.  That's always been a fun trip for me.  My message to them, like it's always been, if you love the game, play it as much as you can, enjoy it, play free, and be around the great people that love the game, as well.  It makes the game that much more fun. It's always been a treat, either if I was going there for Nike or the NBA or for the Olympics.  I've always had a good time."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Wemby said that he had a list of questions that he wanted to ask you.  What advice would you give him and the other young guys who are hoping to have a career that resembles yours?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Well, obviously it always dictates on what the questions that he wants to ask me.  But as far as Wemby, I mean, it seems like from the outside looking in that he has a great head on his shoulders.  He seems like he loves the game, that he takes care of his body, the process and everything. You're going to get out of the game what you put into it.  Iâ€™ve seen one quote that he says that nobody better call him past 9:00 at night because he's either reading or he's asleep.  I think that's super cool.  I think that's super dope.  That lets you know where his mind frame is at, where he is at intellectually, and I think he's been great, obviously, for the franchise with the Spurs, but he's going to be great for our league for so many years to come."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I just wanted to follow up on tonight's game.  You've got Stephon Castle and the Rising Stars team going against the OGs, you, KD, Steph.  What's your approach to that new format, and what will we see from you tonight?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   You won't see anything from me tonight, unfortunately.  I will not be in uniform tonight.  Still dealing with ankle and foot discomfort, so I will not be playing tonight, unfortunately.  I hate that, but I'm looking forward to seeing the format. This is the first year for it.  I know we've got a lot of great -- calling us the OGs, that's hilarious.  We do got a few guys with gray hair, so that makes sense.  So that should be fun. I saw the quote the other day with DK [Dalton Knecht] say he was going to play against me.  So I guess I'll see him in practice and we can go at it then."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Back in 2007, you hosted Saturday Night Live.  You were the last active NBA player to host that show.  We've got All-Star, but they're also celebrating their 50th anniversary this season.  What's it like to be a part of that show's legacy, and what NBA players should host that show next?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   To be a part of the Saturday Night Live legacy is something that -- a dream come true.  It's been on, obviously, my entire life, and seeing so many great actors grace those skits every single Saturday and so many entertainers that come there and do their bits, as well, it was fun. It was super fun, and hopefully I get the opportunity to do it again.  I would love to do it again.  I was so young.  You said 2006? 2007? I was 21, 22 maybe.  It was super fun. I don't know.  I don't know.  Kevin Love is hilarious, by the way, and he's a great friend of mine, and I could definitely see him doing Saturday Night Live for sure.  He's one of my great friends and he's hilarious.  But it was definitely a treat and something that I can always look back and say I was on a show that Will Ferrell has been on and so many great guys.  Bill Hader is a good friend of mine.  It was pretty cool."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Can you talk about the state of the Lakers-Celtics rivalry and rivalries in the NBA more broadly?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   When it comes to rivalries, if it's that deep rooted, then it will always live on.  The Celtics and Lakers, you look at Ohio State-Michigan, you look at Yankees-Red Sox.  There's just certain matchups that no matter who's out on the floor or who's on the gridiron or -- it is what it is because of the tenure and the legacy of it.  That's what stands with the Lakers and the Celtics, for how many years we've been competing against that franchise and whatever, and both have had so much success.  It will always stand the test of time forever."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You're not playing tonight; that's going to be a record that ends that'll probably never come down, consecutive All-Star starts at 20.  My question was when you were 30 and we were talking about who is coming behind you, that discussion may have been a little premature.  But now that you're 40 and you're talking about the end at some point, do you have a player in mind who will be the best player in the league in five years?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I don't, to answer that question.  I do not.  There are too many great young players right now to just say, well, this one guy will be the best player in the league.  Our league is filled with so many talented players, so many guys that can transcend the game on the floor and off the floor, and I think it's in a really good place. It was definitely premature at 30 to ask me that question, but our game is in a really good place."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. We go around the world reviewing different basketball courts and we started in the UK and we went to the I Promise School, traveled all the way there, reviewed that.  I want to know from you, one basketball court that means the most to you or you played on growing up that we need to check out and review.",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Wow.  That's a great question.  I've played on so many indoor and outdoor courts growing up in Akron, Ohio, that they all have a special meaning to me.  I played at Elizabeth Park projects when I was growing up.  I played Summer Lake Recreation Center.  I played at the YMCA downtown.  I played at the Urban League.  I played at outdoor courts like Perkins Pool, Hawkins Court, Ed Davis, as well, in my hometown. Me and my best friends, who we're still best friends today, we went all over the city either on our bikes or we walked around and we would go look for a game and see if guys were playing ball either indoor or outdoor, and we wanted to get a run in no matter what. It's a lot of courts in our city that I don't know if they're still, like, actively playing ball.  I know a lot of kids don't really be outside as much as we did when we were younger, but there's a lot of courts that hold a lot of meaning to me because it started the whole love of the game for me, just being able to go out and play just for the love of the game and the freedom that we had."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. To follow up on the foot and the ankle, you played on Wednesday in Utah.  There's a game scheduled this Wednesday.  Because of the fires and rescheduling.  Do you anticipate being available at the start of this week?  Or was this more kind of a maintenance type of wear-and-tear situation?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I mean, it's a little bit of both.  I was hoping that it would feel a lot better this morning, but it's not where I want it to be.  With 30 games left and us trying to make a playoff push in the wild, wild west, I feel like it's important for me to take care of myself and understand what's coming on. I don't want to say it's maintenance -- well, it is maintenance, but at the same time, it's like, I have to look out for myself when it comes to this injury that I've been dealing with for years. I hope to be available on Wednesday.  We have to have a makeup game.  So, I am headed back to LA tonight.  There will be no vacation for me, so I head back to LA tonight and back to rehab tomorrow and getting ready for practice on Tuesday, and hopefully I can play against Charlotte on Wednesday and hopefully play against Portland on Thursday.  It's a big stretch for us."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "ALL-STAR GAME",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=194257",
    "date": "February 18, 2024",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, for you, an NBA-record 20th All-Star selection.  What has the All-Star Game meant to you in your career and how it has evolved, if it has evolved, from your early stages to now?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I think as a kid growing up and loving the game of basketball and watching the NBA All-Star Weekend and seeing the Sunday game, I always had dreams and visions if I was able to play the game at a high level and give everything to the game, hopefully I could be a part of that game someday. It's just been an absolute honor to be able to grace the floor throughout my career and be out there with the greatest players in the world year in and year out. This is very humbling, very blessed, and it's something I will never forget obviously.  It's part of my journey."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, you missed the last game prior to the break in Salt Lake City because of the left ankle.  Did you seek any treatment on it in the days leading up to the All-Star Game?  What's your plan in terms of minutes tonight?  And how can you manage that and just your health in general to try to get this team as far as they can go the remainder of the season?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   That's most important.  Yes, I did seek treatment the last few days, trying to get my ankle as strong and as back to where I feel confident that I can finish off this last third of the season. I won't be playing the entire game tonight, for sure.  I can get out there and run around with the young guys for a little bit and then shut it down at some point to give my body, and my ankle more importantly, another opportunity to rest. I'm seeking some more treatment tomorrow going into this week, because we have quite a few days this week as well.  We don't play until the end of the week.  See how that goes.  But the most important thing for me is definitely my health, where I'm at right now, where our team is leaning.  We're trending in the right direction. Obviously, with our Laker team, it's been about health all year.  Trying to do what's best for me for the betterment of the team."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, in year 21, how are the ways that you affect the game?  How has that changed, in terms of both methods and frequency?  And how has that affected the players around you, and has it given guys opportunities to maybe take on more roles, bigger opportunities?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Yes.  I think for me, I can affect the game in a lot of ways.  At this point in my career, it's still the same way.  I can affect the game by being on the ball, being off the ball, cutting from the weak side, slashing from the weak side, running in transition.  I have the ability to shoot the ball in space at more frequency at a higher level than I was early in my career.  So I've worked on that. My mind is just sharper than anything.  It's allowed me to go out there and sometimes just outthink the game and not have to physically be imposing out on the floor for 40 minutes or 42, whatever the case may be that I'm out there.  I could pick my spots. When I need to be more aggressive offensively or less aggressive and allow guys like D-Lo and A.R. to run the team, and I can play off the ball, whatever the case may be.  Being able to have a dominant threat like AD and being able to throw the ball to him and wait and see what the defense is going to do and play off with that. I guess I'm just a lot smarter than I was in my first ten years compared to these last ten years."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I want to talk about defense, on the day of the All-Star Game.  You've been in the league for so long where the three-point shot has changed.  I think we talked about how that shot is shot more often than how it's defended.  From your perspective as someone who, especially now, has to defend so many threes on your team defense, what's your perspective how it's changed and what you can do to defend threes?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I guess each team is going to dictate what your defense allows you to do or what you want to take away.  At the end of the day, we're All NBA players, and you can't take away everything.  Guys are going to score, guys are going to shoot threes, guys are going to put up numbers.  It's what you're willing to give up, not what you want to take away. Every team is different.  Every team's portfolio is different of how they attack the game.  If you do your scouting, if you do your research, you know players' tendencies, you can be proactive more than reactive. You're absolutely right, the game that's definitely got to, because of analytics, when that tapped into our game, it's more just like layups, dunks, free throws, threes.  A lot of teams are trying to shy away from the midrange.  A lot of teams are trying to shy away from a lot of other things that, when I came into the league, that was very important. Depending on the teams that you're playing, you know the teams that want to shoot 40, 50 threes a game.  You know the teams that want to shoot 25 to 30.  You just have to do your scouting and be prepared for it."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, obviously it's your 20th All-Star Game, setting a record.  For the last generation, you've been one of the faces of the league.  When you came into the league, there was a lot of talk about who would be the person to succeed Michael Jordan eventually as the face of the league.  Now questions crop up of, when you eventually stop playing, who would be able to succeed you in that role.  I'm just curious, just looking forward, to however long it is until you stop, how do you see that playing out?  Who do you see potentially being able to do that?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I don't know, because when I came into the league, I didn't look at myself as the face of anything.  I didn't look at myself as the next Michael or the successor to Michael. When I came into the league, the first thing that I thought about was I have to start over now.  I have built my rep in high school from my freshman year to my senior year, from being a 14-year-old freshman, I was 6'2\", 180 pounds, and I was like, okay, how can I make a name for myself at St. Vincent-St. Mary, all the way to my senior year, where I was the number one player in the country. That's the same thing I did when I got drafted.  I did not come in with the mindset I was the number one player in the country still.  I came in with the mindset I have to start over and I'm just one of 450 guys.  I think that's what allowed me to build and build and build. I didn't think about being the face of the league.  I knew I was being put in a position that I was being the face of a franchise, NBA franchise, at 18 years old.  It was very stressful, and I knew the odds were stacked up against me and a lot of people wanted to see me fail.  And I just kind of used that as motivation. But at the same time, understanding that I still have to be a professional.  I know it's a lot to ask for a teenager, but I wanted to represent my family with the utmost respect, represent my city with the utmost respect, do it on the floor at a high level, but also do it off the floor at a high level.  Whatever came out of that came out of that. We have a great young group of guys in our league right now that is playing spectacular basketball and also being great off the floor as well.  But I don't think you just say, okay, well, this guy's the next person to be the face of anything.  You have to just let it happen organically and then see what happens. But we have some great, great players in this league that can carry anything if they put their mind to it and they want it."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, I know you talked about the All-Star Game sort of in the breadth of your career, but I'm wondering about the particulars at this point in your 20th version, 19th version.  I remember your first All-Star Game saying you're looking around the locker room at Allen Iverson and Grant Hill and Vince Carter, and it feels special.  What is it at 19, 20 years in that feels special at this particular age?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Being here.  You still get that moment where I'm in the locker room looking at Steph, AD, KD, Kawhi, Joker, Luka all those guys.  Those are just a few of the names.  Those are the guys in the West.  So you still have that feeling like, this is pretty cool. I still at heart and like deep inside, I'm still like that 18-year-old kid that came into this league from Akron, Ohio, which is like you don't really have many inspirations.  You've got to grab it from somebody, and it's usually like a family member or a basketball coach or a football coach or a teacher or somebody like that.  It's not many people that make it on TV or make it to doing special things that you think is special. When you're a kid, you think like musicians and people in sports, you think those are the only special people.  But actually it's my Little League coaches and my mom and my uncle and things of that nature.  I still have that feeling still. I was just clowning with AD before I came in here.  I looked to my left and see who I was sitting next to, and I'm sitting between AD and Steph, probably two of the best players that are going to play this game.  Obviously, we know what Steph is about and we know what AD's about.  So pretty cool still."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, I know it's impossible to forecast what you're going to feel like 4 1/2 months from now or how deep the season will go for you guys.  But when you think about the Olympics, it's 11 games at the most, but at the same time, it's 5 1/2 weeks and a lot of miles.  Knowing how much you put into keeping your body as great as you can keep it, how daunting does that feel?  I guess how confident are you that, if all goes right, you'll want to be there and you'll want to put yourself through the grind of it all?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Yeah, I mean, I told myself before the season when I committed to being a part of the Olympic team, obviously it was all predicated on my health.  As it stands right now, I am healthy enough to be on the team and perform at a level that I knew I could perform at. Like you said, there's still time left in the season, a third left in the regular season.  Obviously, I don't know what the future holds as far as postseason, whatever the case may be.  Like you said, it's 11 games, but it is 5 1/2 weeks, and it's more miles put on these tires. I've always -- if I'm committed, which I am, to Team USA, then I'm going to commit my mind, body and soul to being out there for Team USA, being out there representing our country with the utmost respect and go out and play. But the one thing I know for sure, I don't have to carry the load.  I've never had to carry the load on any one of the three teams I've been on, the '04 team, the '08 team and the '12 team.  I just try to do my best and be as great as I can be on the floor in the minutes I'm out there. I'm not sure right now what the full team is going to look like, but from some of the names, I know I don't have to feel any pressure going out there to feel like I have to carry the team.  That's going to be a full 12-man roster that's capable of doing it both offensively and defensively on any given night versus any country in the world."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, you sometimes react on social media when a guy scores 70 points, and it's happened a few times recently.  What are you thinking when you watch that game in terms of the offensive ability to put up that many points?  Then secondarily to that, do you see someone getting 80 and 90 the way the game is played today?  In what circumstance is that going to happen?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   First of all, it's (expletive) great to see you.  It's so great to see you, Jeff (Zillgitt).  Love this.  And the fact that you got the last question is even greater.  You tried to hide in the back.  I love that as well.  Love you, man.  Wow, it's great to see you. To your question, there's so much scoring in this league.  You can't really put your hands on people too much.  I think there's guys that have learned that ability to get to the free throw line very frequently out on the floor.  You have guys shooting 20 -- I've seen guys shoot 15 to 20 threes in a game. We have some great scorers in this game, that when you see guys putting up 50s, 60s, 70s, it's like you're watching the game, you're like, oh, man, he either had a heater, he caught fire.  You've seen guys this year scoring like 40 in the first half. I don't know, you've got so many great talents in this league.  Would I sit here and say I think guys can score 80 or 90?  Yeah, why not?  It's been done before.  Talent is talent no matter what generation it is.  '50s, '60s, '70s, '80s, '90s all the way until now, talent is talent, and great basketball and great scorers are going to be great scorers no matter what era they're in.  Once a great scorer gets going, there's really nothing you can do. I know you've asked this question before, and a lot of you guys have asked, what does it feel like to be in a zone?  Once a guy's in a zone, there's nothing you can do.  If a guy decides he wants to stay in the zone, or you've seen Caitlin the other night when she broke the record, there's nothing you can do.  There's nothing you can do. If the game's flowing at a very good pace and you've got a heater from the midrange, you've got a heater from the free throw line, you're shooting threes, you shoot 15 threes, you make 10 of them, that's 30 right there.  You go to the free throw line 15 times and make another 13, 14, that's 43 points right there.  You could very easily make another 10, 12, 15 points from two-point land and just be at 60, 70, 80. I think it's possible.  I mean, we've seen Kobe.  We've seen Kobe do it.  Kobe -- obviously, I'm not going to put too many guys on Kobe's level, but when you have a hot streak, we've seen Kobe live put up 81.  I think it could be done."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I'll use the opportunity for a bonus question.  Assuming --",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Of course you get a bonus question.  You don't have to ask that.  Of course."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Assuming that you're closer to the end of your career than the beginning of your career --",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I am.  I promise you."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Have you mapped out what that looks like to you in terms of how many more seasons?  Then does it end with the team you're playing for right now?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I have not mapped out how many seasons I have left.  I know it's not that many.  I also don't know if I will -- I was asked this question a couple days ago.  Will you kind of take the farewell tour, or will you kind of just Tim Duncan it? I'm 50-50, I'm going to be honest, because there's times when I feel like I guess I owe it to my fans that have been along this journey with me for two decades plus, to be able to give them that moment where it's every city and whatever the case may be and they give you your flowers or whatever the case may be.  That seems cool. But the other side of I've never been that great with accepting like praise.  It's a weird feeling for me.  I never really talked about it much, but it's just a weird feeling for me.  So to go in each city, if that's the case -- I don't know.  I've seen Mike's, I've seen Kobe's.  I've seen a lot of guys.  I just don't know how much I -- how I'd feel.  I don't know if I'd feel great about it.  Maybe the only child in me maybe. But I don't know.  I am a Laker, and I am happy and been very happy being a Laker the last six years, and hopefully it stays that way.  But I don't have the answer to how long it is or which uniform I'll be in.  Hopefully it is with the Lakers.  It's a great organization and so many greats.  But we'll see.  I don't know how it's going to end, but it's coming.  It's coming, for sure."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "ALL-STAR GAME",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=194258",
    "date": "February 18, 2024",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, you did mention in your pregame limited minutes tonight.  How do you feel, especially in light of the ankle that you spoke on?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I'm feeling okay.  I definitely wasn't going to put too much pressure on the game tonight for me physically.  I want to try to be as healthy as I can be physically.  This last part of the season is very important for us.  I got to make sure of that."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, you said you were going to seek further treatment on the ankle.  Will that treatment prevent you from playing Thursday in Golden State?  Do you know yet?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   It possibly could.  It depends on the recovery process.  So possibly, but we will see."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You achieved almost everything a player has dreamed of.  What is the great dream for LeBron James?  What else are you pursuing?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Still just my love for the game.  I'm not pursuing anything, but my love for the game runs deep.  Just trying to give everything I can to the game until I have nothing left, in the sense of just my love. It's not about the physical or things of that nature.  It's just about the pure joy of going out and playing a game that I love.  I know I don't have much time left, but while I'm out there, just trying to play with a lot of joy and a lot of fun."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, 211-186 are things we have never seen in an All-Star Game.  You know that Adam and others from the league are talking about making it more competitive.  Is this what players want?  Is this what you think fans want too?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I don't know.  I think it's something we need to figure out.  Where is the median?  This is what a lot of the games are starting to look like too.  We wanted to get more pace into the games.  We wanted to get more shots.  We wanted the game to be more free flowing.  We stopped letting the game -- be freedom of movement, a lot of freedom of movement now.  That's what our games are like in the regular season now. They let us tighten up in the postseason.  It's a deeper dive into a conversation of how we can shore up this game.  Obviously from a player's perspective, it's fun to get up and down.  But at the end of the day, our competitive nature don't like to have free-flowing scoring like that. But I think the good thing that came out of tonight was none of the players were injured, and everybody came out unscathed or how they were before the game started.  So it's a deeper conversation."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, two really quick for you:  There was a social media post going around of you dunking in your first ever All-Star Game.  You doing it again tonight, kind of almost the exact same kind of signature one-handed dunk.  Big picture, to do this 20 times now that you've done it, how did that sit with you?  Also wanted to ask you about the moment you had with Oscar pregame and how important that was for you.",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   One, I don't know, man, it's super surreal and super crazy and just very humbled and blessed that I can be able to still perform on the stage at this point in my career and be able to do some of the things that I did 20 years ago.  I think that's pretty cool. I always acknowledge the greats.  I understand the greats that came before me and the people that laid down the foundation for this sport to be as great as it is today.  I happen to be a recipient of that.  Because of Big O and so many other great players, obviously, if anybody know my history, they know how much I admire Big O, not only for what he contributed to the game, but also what he stood for off the floor as well. We've always had a really cool relationship, and every time I get an opportunity to see him, we just pick it back up where we left off.  To see him tonight was a treat for me.  I didn't expect to see him.  I didn't know he was going to be here.  So it was a treat for me to see him again."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, what kind of improvement have you seen on the game of Victor Wembanyama?  And what do you think about his season?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I've been asked about Victor before, and I just think he's going to continue to get better and better and better and better the more games he plays.  He has one of the greatest coaches in basketball history in Coach Pop, and he's going to learn it the right way by just being around Pop.  Pop is one of my favorite guys. The kid is special.  He's going to continue to get better and better.  If he's doing that at 19 now, just imagine what he's going to look like at 21, 22.  So a special kid."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. As a historic veteran, seeing players like Banchero and other players coming into their first year as All-Stars, what is that like for you seeing them be established now?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   It's awesome.  I remember my first All-Star Game and looking up and seeing the likes of Allen Iverson and Kobe Bryant and Kevin Garnett and those guys, and I was just in awe.  Just to see guys in their first All-Star Games, like you said, Paolo and the rest of the guys here, it's special.  It's special for them. I think you saw the raw emotion that Jalen Brunson showed when they asked him after a Knick game how he felt being an All-Star.  I think you saw the raw emotion, and that's how much he cares about being acknowledged and for him to be a first-time All-Star is just super cool. To be a part of their moment, because this is their moment, is something I can look back on and be like that was a cool moment."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. We spoke this time last year, and you talked pretty eloquently about the common values that you have, one of the game's greats, with a young Filipino kid who's falling in love with basketball in a way that Filipinos very uniquely do.  I want to talk about one of those values, the value of hope.  You've been through a lot of adversities in your life and in your career.  What helps you find silver linings?  What helps you maintain hope?  And how important is it for you to be a silver lining for people who need it?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   For me, what I find is a silver lining is looking at my upbringing and looking at kids that are in situations that I was in when I was younger, trying to be an inspiration to them, letting them understand that there is a way out.  I was one of the kids that made it out. So it's my responsibility and my duty to let them know that no matter what you're going through, there is a path out.  If you just commit to your dream and you can make that dream become a reality.  I think that's what it's all about. I've shared a great relationship with the Philippines and TITAN and us having that -- we share some of the same core values.  I always respected that even when I went over there and spent a lot of time in the Philippines in Manila. Sometimes that's all a kid has is hope, and that's okay.  As long as you don't give that up.  Don't ever give that up because it's always brighter on the other side, for sure."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA IN-SEASON TOURNAMENT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=193132",
    "date": "December 9, 2023",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, after spending three days here in Vegas, you got a sense for the kind of fan support in the city.  I was curious about your observations now of Las Vegas as an NBA city?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Has not changed.  My enthusiasm about being here post-career, bringing a team here has not changed.  The fans are amazing here.  They have everything already:  WNBA team, they have a baseball team coming in soon, NFL team, hockey team, F1 was just here over the Thanksgiving week.  Everything is here.  This is a place that loves great attractions and I think the NBA will be another great addition to this city. Obviously we see the success with Summer League and things of that nature and the Aces as well.  It will be fun."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. AD, LeBron led the way in the semifinal and you took things over tonight.  All the times that you played together, winning the title, the other big games in the playoffs, how did you come together and do it again in this context?",
        "answer": "ANTHONY DAVIS:   We've been doing it together for a long time, five years now, and we just figure it out.  We know each other's tendencies, what we like to do.  Obviously in crunch time, we get to our infamous pick-and-roll and it's tough to stop. We feed off one another.  Thursday, LeBron had it going. Tonight, it was me, and he still did his thing. But it wasn't just us two.  Obviously the whole team, Austin, D-Lo, everybody contributed tonight. Cam with his defense.  T.P.  It was a great team win tonight."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You two guys celebrated a title together feels like forever ago in Florida, but what did this experience with this group tell you about those prospects moving forward?  And did the intensity of these games show you that this could be a group that has a real shot at doing it again in May and June?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think that's thinking too far down the road.  We want to put it in perspective that it's still December.  We like where we are right now but we want to continue to work our habits, continue to get healthy as well. But I think right now where we are in December, I would take it.  I would take it.  But I'm definitely not looking to May and June.  That's too far.  There's too many steps that need to be taken still in order for our team to be who we want to be once the postseason starts. As of today, I like the way we played in the semifinals on Thursday and then tonight.  Our defensive intensity, in order for us to win and win at the highest level, we have to defend.  We've been doing that over the last few weeks."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. The stats won't count tonight toward the regular season, but the way that you were the catalyst for the defense, what does it mean for you to do that in a game that matters?",
        "answer": "ANTHONY DAVIS:   Obviously means a lot because it helped the team win.  But any time I step on the floor, I know I'm the anchor of the defense, giving guys the freedom to press up and get some ball pressure, and if they get beat, I'm there at the rim to alter the shot or block it. But that's my job.  I'm constantly talking with the guys.  Especially me and Bron have great chemistry as far as our defensive schemes and what we like to do, the four and the five.  Overall, I think we've been locked in defensively.  Obviously it helps getting Vando back and Cam and Rui.  We're able to do a lot more things defensively.  But it's my job to be the anchor and lead the team on the defensive end."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, you've now played five seasons and counting with AD.  That's more than you played with Dwyane and Chris Bosh in Miami, and more than you've played with Kyrie and Kevin in Cleveland. What has he meant to your career?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Everything, especially at the later stage of my career, to be able to get a young, hungry alpha male to go out there and just do the things that he does.  It's definitely given me an opportunity to be able to not only watch as he's continued to grow, but also be able to try to inspire him as well as he continue to grow in his career and vice versa. I feel like when we are on the floor together and we're healthy, we know when we're capable of doing.  We've played too many games together, shared too many moments together, played in too many big moments together to fail each other.  It's been everything, like I said, especially at the later stage of my career."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Seems like I ask you guys this question often, but what does it mean to have Austin Reaves play at this level?",
        "answer": "ANTHONY DAVIS:   Means a lot.  What he did tonight, but what he's been doing this entire season has been unbelievable.  He actually takes a lot of pressure off us, too.  We draw so much attention and he's able to go one-on-one or playmake for himself or for the other guys. He's meant a lot to our organization and to our team.  There's nothing that he can't do on the offensive end, and he's locking in defensively.  He means a lot to our ballclub, and it just shows every time he steps on the floor."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You just said you know what you and AD are capable of when you guys are on the floor together, but no one from this current roster, no one else was on that championship team, what have you learned about the rest of the group over going 7-0 in the In-Season Tournament?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Just growth.  I think every moment we grew.  The In-Season Tournament, 7-0, it's been high-intensity games and we've just grown.  I feel like guys have felt a lot more comfortable in their roles.  We've had a pretty good understanding of rotations. You know who you're going to be playing with and you know what you guys want to do out on the floor. And like AD said, getting Vando back, getting Rui back has helped our frontcourt, our size, and getting Cam back has helped us a lot.  Not too many people talk about it, but one of the biggest shots of the game was they made their run, cut it to three and Cam hits that big-time three in front of our bench to put it up six.  We didn't go back after that.  Cam has been big-time for us and I'm happy to see him thrive under this role with us because he deserves it, for sure."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. There's a lot said about you and your offensive performances throughout the regular season.  To have this kind of performance, 40 and 20 on this stage what does it mean to you and what does it mean for you?",
        "answer": "ANTHONY DAVIS:   I mean, it don't really mean much.  I just try to do everything I can to win a basketball game.  Obviously, my teammates put me in a great position to be successful.  Obviously, this is special for us, just winning the inaugural In-Season Tournament. But we want to also win the same thing in June. It's a step in the right direction, obviously, but even though it's a big performance, it's another game and we've got to continue to get going starting back on Tuesday."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA IN-SEASON TOURNAMENT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=193098",
    "date": "December 7, 2023",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. You've been in more big games than most anybody, but just wonder mentally how you approach a game like this.  You see some of the charges drawn and the focus, but what are the actual things that you're thinking about that you're trying to set an example for on the floor and how did it play out?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I think you just said it: trying to lead by example, make plays on the floor, be unselfish, try to make the right plays offensively, defensively, cover for my teammates and live with the results."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. It wasn't too long ago that you said to us that this team, this Lakers team, wasn't built so that you and Anthony had to shoulder all the load.  But what can it be if you guys are playing the way you guys have been playing of late with this group?  You're starting to get a glimpse of maybe what the next four or five months could look like for this team?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I think we're starting to figure it out.  You know, you guys have been asking me over the last couple months, what do you think about the team and what do I think we can be.  My answer was realistic:  We don't know because we haven't had our team. But we are starting to get healthy.  We are starting to see what our team looks like.  We know who we are going to be playing with out on the floor.  Guys are feeling in a really good rhythm offensively and defensively.  It definitely helps, being able to log minutes with different lineups and things of that nature, so that you kind of know what you're going to flow into offensively and you know what you're going to do defensively.  It helps.  It helps a lot."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. AD, you've been in the league for over a decade at this point.  There's not many firsts that you're experiencing in your career.  Now coming here to Las Vegas for the inaugural In-Season Tournament and playing in the championship, what does being in a new, a first situation, bring out of your game excite you and invigorate you?",
        "answer": "ANTHONY DAVIS:   Just the whole environment.  Like you said, it's the first time any of us have been in this In-Season Tournament, especially the finals. So I think that in itself is exciting for our ballclub.  I guess on top of adding the incentives and things like that.  But I think the excitement around it, the atmosphere, the energy, the competitiveness that it brings out of teams is going to be fun."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Saturday is still ahead of you, but the typical rhythms of the NBA season don't necessarily allow for this type of intensity, this type of must-win basketball to be played.  How do you think that's going to help this team big picture, having gone through this in the first quarter of the season?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I don't know.  I mean, that's to be seen.  I think we are starting to get a feel for who we need to become as a team in order for us to win basketball games and be consistent.  We know that defensively we are starting to really, really tap into that, like, okay, we got to defend every single night.  And when we defend, we are going to give ourselves a chance to win every night.  I think when you got guys on a string, you've got guys communicating defensively, you might have a breakdown here but then you've got one of your teammates on the back line that is picking up for you, it brings a lot of good mojo to the team. I think we hang our hats on our defense.  Then offensively, we want to be low in turnovers and we want to share the ball.  We've got 31 assists tonight.  We have five turnovers in like the first five minutes of the game, and then we only had nine for the rest of the game.  That's big time."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. For both of you, what are your early thoughts on the matchup with Indiana on Saturday?",
        "answer": "ANTHONY DAVIS:   They are a good ballclub.  We were actually talking about maybe last week that they score a lot of points.  A lot of 140s and things like that, 130s.  Obviously, the head of the snake is Tyrese, with good role players around him who complement him very well. They are young.  They are scrappy.  They get out and run, and they play the right way.  So it's going to be a test for our defense, for sure.  But it's going to be an exciting game."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. This one is also for both of you.  You guys have had some of your most dominant performances as part of this tournament.  What did you learn about this team that you did not know before the tournament?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   That the funky courts does not bother us.  (Laughter.)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Adam Silver has come up with the bubble, the Play-In and the In-Season Tournament.  Where do you think the In-Season Tournament ranks, and do you like putting your mark on these new things that Adam either has had to do or wanted to do?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Well, we've been successful with the first two. Where I rank it, the bubble is one, obviously.  We won a championship.  But we also had an opportunity to play in Play-In games.  I think we've had two -- one against Golden State and one against Minnesota last year -- and we won both to give us a nod into the postseason.  And this has been good so far as well to us, too. We've got to finish our breakfast on Saturday.  That's the most important thing.  But like I said -- yeah, he's pretty good.  Adam, like I said, what was that, yesterday, I said Adam is a genius.  He does a great job, for sure."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. The one thing you had not experienced was playing in the NCAA Tournament.  Does this feel like it approximates that experience?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   It's funny, my trainer was like, \"You know, one thing you haven't done in your 21-year career is be in the Final Four,\" before the game started today.  I chuckled a little bit. I played in my high school.  I went to the state championship every year, all my four years.  But once you start the postseason, it is win-or-go-home, and you can't lose or that's it. I did have that experience, but this is definitely heightened, being NBA players and what's at stake and things of that nature.  I guess you can say that."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Looks like Bronny is going to play on Sunday.  What would it mean to see him back out there?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Everything, and more.  Looking forward to that, for sure.  Super excited.  Super excited for that moment.  Just one, I can't wait to see him run out with his teammates.  And then once he checks into the game, whenever that case may be, it's going to be a big moment for our family. Obviously, it will be a big moment for him.  But he can speak upon that once he decides he wants to talk.  But it's a big milestone for our family, for sure, and it's another step for him on his journey in his basketball career.  So, looking forward to it."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA IN-SEASON TOURNAMENT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=193082",
    "date": "December 6, 2023",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. What's the main message to the team in a new situation like this?  You've been in so many in the NBA but this one is new.  How do you proceed going into the semis?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I don't know, just a game.  We'll prepare.  We understand what's at stake, being the first In-Season Tournament.  But I'm not adding pressure to my teammates.  It's still game 24, if I'm not mistaken.  It's actually game 23.  I'm not adding no pressure to my teammates.  We're going to go out and play our game, and win, lose or draw, we'll be all right."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Is there any -- in terms of the preparation that changes for you personally and just kind of the added stakes and competing at this level this early in the season?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Rest, for me.  Coming off that game last night took a lot out of me physically and mentally and things of that nature.  Just getting my rest.  That's the only thing that I'm concerned about -- or not even concerned, that I've got to worry about. As far as preparation for the game, that stays the same no matter where I'm at.  But just trying to get as much rest as I can."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. As a four-time champion, if you were to win on Saturday night, would you like to see a banner in L.A. over the In-Season Tournament?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   That's up to the league.  I don't have an answer for that."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. As I'm sure you know, there was a tragedy today at UNLV.  I'm curious how you found out about it and if that affects the mood getting into Vegas and getting settled with everything coming tomorrow.",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Yeah, my brother from back home texted me and told me to be safe out here because he heard about the shooting at UNLV.  First of all, I don't know, was there any casualties or -- first of all, my condolences go to the families that lost loved ones, families and friends and everything. It just goes back to what I said before about guns in America.  I think it's such a longer conversation, but we keep dealing with the same story, this same conversation everybody single time it happens, and it just continues to happen.  The ability to get a gun, the ability to do these things over and over and over, and there's been no change is literally ridiculous.  It makes no sense that we continue to lose innocent lives, on campuses, schools, at shopping markets and movie theaters and all type of stuff.  It's ridiculous.  The fact that we haven't changed anything -- it's actually been easier to be able to own a firearm.  It's stupid."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Pelicans have a lot of size.  How is that going to be for you guys in the particulars of this tournament?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I mean, you absolutely just said it.  They have a lot of length, a lot of size, wings, bigs.  Herb Jones, BI, Zion, Valanciunas.  They come off with Murphy.  They've got just a lot of size, and they're missing Larry Nance.  But they've got a lot of size. The one thing that's been beneficial to us over the last couple games, we've started to add our depth and add our size, too.  Being able to bring back Cam, bring back Rui, Vando has played a couple games now, so we've added some size, too.  Jax came back, played some minutes for us last night. We understand their size and their paint attacks.  They do a good job of attacking the paint, putting pressure at the rim.  We've got to be ready for that.  We've got to be ready for it."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Obviously still a couple games left to go, but having been through most of this tournament and seeing how it's played out, are there any things you would like to see the league change about it or tweak about it for next year and beyond?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I don't know, I haven't thought about it.  If I had some time to think about it, I might have a better answer, but haven't really thought about it.  We just played the games.  When we've had games on Tuesdays and Fridays, we've played them.  You kind of know it's a tournament game.  Sometimes you kind of forget about it until you get to the arena either at home or on the road and you see the court and then you know it's a tournament game.  But I haven't thought about if I would have any changes. But I mean, if it's not broke, don't fix it, and it seems like it's going really well."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. To your point, it seems like across the league, teams and players have bought into this maybe faster than the general public might have expected.  Have you felt like this has gotten more momentum internally faster than maybe you would have thought?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Listen, Adam Silver is a genius, so it's that simple.  So it's going to work."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You guys have a lot of moments together, especially with that high-low pass.  Talk about those two things.",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   First of all, it's not just Bronny at a game; it's Bronny, period.  To have the ability to be able to point at him and see him smiling and alive.  It's literally that simple, to have that moment with my son knowing the situation that happened earlier in the summer, just to have that -- I'm not saying I took it for granted before, but it puts everything in perspective for sure.  That's that. And then, two, yeah, me and AD, we have that chemistry because it's just bigger than us just going out and dribbling the basketball and saying, okay, let's shoot it up at the rim and try to make a layup or a dunk or a jump shot or free throw or whatever.  Very smart, and we've been through so many battles in our five years that we've played together that we can tell each other things or sometimes we can just look at each other and know how either things are going to unfold or how we want to impact a certain play or certain situation throughout the course of a 48-minute game."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. A lot of people are listening from Spain right now.  I know you are a wine lover.  If you had something to celebrate on Saturday, would Spanish wine be in that plan?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Yeah, if you get some for me.  You bring me some Spanish wine, I'll have some."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've been very vocal about owning a team in Las Vegas in the near future.  Are you excited to see the atmosphere this week?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Yeah, absolutely.  I mean, it's crazy to say this, but Vegas is a sports town.  You look at the Aces and you look at the hockey team, you look at the Raiders.  I heard the A's are coming here soon.  Obviously, Summer League has been here for years.  We just had F1 here over Thanksgiving.  I mean, it's a sports town.  Hopefully I can bring my franchise here someday.  That's the ultimate. Yeah, they know what they're watching.  They show a lot of support.  Sports is gigantic here right now, and they definitely support their clubs here.  That's for sure."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA WESTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: LAKERS VS. NUGGETS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=187284",
    "date": "May 22, 2023",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. There were a few times in playoffs past you went the full 48, the series against Boston like three times in 2012 and a couple others.  Is that something you decided before the game and being on the court that much, trying to find your legs that much, did that symbolize anything about what this run has been like for you?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   For me it's just a mindset.  Training the mind, you train the mind, the body will fall where it may and take care of the rest.  Knowing, coming into a game where I may have to play a full game, that's just my mindset, and wasn't able to come through, and wasn't able to get the win.  That was just my mindset going into tonight."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Throughout the year, we've talked about how long this season was.  I think I've seen you yawn more than I've seen anybody yawn through the course of a season.  But how did this group energize you as it got into the postseason and as you got a chance to get one level away from the Finals?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think it energized me from the moment I was out for those four weeks and just seeing the type of team that we had, the type of energy that we brought into the locker room, the type of energy we brought onto the floor.  You know, I just couldn't wait to join these guys with action and get on the floor and I knew how much I could make an impact with the group of guys. But it was always -- it was an exciting moment when we were able just to bring those guys into the locker room.  You know, we were just a better team right away, and it results in getting to the Western Conference Finals."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. The franchise goal and your goal personally is championships in L.A.  This group got close, eight wins away, but how do you view moving on to next year, year 21 with the Lakers, and do you think contender status now or there's upgrades to be made?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I haven't even thought about next year.  I don't know."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. If I could stick to this year then.  It was a four-game series.  Every game had winnable moments and you guys certainly showed it.  When you reflect on it, what were the margins, the edges that Denver ultimately was successful with?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Me and AD were just talking in the locker room for a little bit.  I think we came to the consensus, this is if not, one of the best teams, if not the best team, we've played together for all four years.  Just well orchestrated, well put together.  They have scoring.  They have shooting.  They have play-making.  They have smarts.  They have length.  They have depth.  And one thing about their team, when you have a guy like Jokic, who as big as he is but also as cerebral as he is, you can't really make many mistakes versus a guy like that. And even when you guard him for one of the best possessions that you think you can guard him, he puts the ball behind his head Larry Bird style and shoots it 50 feet in the air and it goes in, like he did four or five times this series [laughter].  So you do like this to him [tipping cap]."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. How do you reflect on your individual season, year 20?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I really don't.  It's not who I am.  I guess I'll reflect on my career when I'm done.  But I don't know.  I'll let you guys talk about it. The only thing I concern myself with is being available to my teammates, and I don't like the fact that I didn't play as many games as I would've liked because of injury.  That's the only thing I care about is being available to my teammates."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Is there a sense of frustration because of what happened throughout the course of this particular series?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I mean, of course, that's human nature when you're a competitor.  Obviously frustrated.  Not being able to close out one of these games where you were in every game.  You know, two games in Denver, two games here, were winning [in] every game.  We were up 15 at the half.  They hit us with a 36-point quarter, took momentum of the game.  We still and had an opportunity but just couldn't make plays down the stretch. That's the frustrating part.  You tip your hat to them.  Like I said, it's a great team."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. How do you balance the disappointment of a missed opportunity but also look at this roster that's kind of reloaded and has potential for even greater things next year, potentially a championship roster, how do you balance the disappointment but also the hope for next year?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I mean, I don't know.  Like I said, I haven't began to even think about next year.  We had a great run but we fell short of our goal.  Our goal is to win championships.  That's what this franchise is about and we fell short of that.  That's disappointing."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I'm curious if you would walk us through, the day starts with Carmelo Anthony, someone who you were, are, very close with, and your contemporary announcing his retirement and you getting ready to play in a Western Conference Finals game as the last man standing, if you will, from that class.  What was that like for you?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Well, I kind of knew the announcement was going to happen because I shot the video a week ago [laughter] that you guys seen today.  So, people probably think I'm lying about that, too, huh?  I shot that video like a week ago, so I already knew the announcement was coming, just didn't know which day, but it happened today. Still bittersweet, honestly.  That's one of my best friends when I got into this league, even before I got into this league.  We had so many moments when we were in high school from competing against each other to sitting outside of a hotel room at 2 or 3 o'clock in the morning on the steps of a hotel and just talking about our journey up until where we were 17, I was 16, he was 17, and what we could possibly do going forward, what we could possibly do for our mothers, what we could possibly do for our families if we just continued to stay focused.  I believe we was a driving force for one another.  We were locked at the hip since high school. And then you guys saw once we got into the NBA, he was always a motivating factor for me, being in the Western Conference, I was in the East.  So, I would play our games and then rush home downtown Cleveland where I had an apartment my first two years in the league, and rushed and turned the Nuggets games on and watched Melo play.  All the way to the point where we didn't make the playoffs my first year, I was in Denver for his first playoff game.  You could look that up, too, just in case you think I'm lying about that, too. So definitely just a bittersweet moment today to see one of my great friends, I never say call it quits, just to say that, you know, it's an amazing run.  An amazing accomplishment.  An amazing career.  And you know we just we'll always be joined at the hip no matter what."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What, if anything, did Jokic prove to you during this series?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Nothing.  I know how great he is.  I know how great Jokic is.  There are certain guys in this league that play the game a certain way, a certain way that I like to play the game as well, and he's one of them where you are always off balance when you are guarding a player like that because of his ability to score, rebound, shoot.  He sees plays before they happen.  There's not many guys in our league like that. So you already knew you was going against a beast once the series started, and not only just about his game.  Everybody gets cracked up into his stats but I don't think a lot of people talk about, like, this part of his game [indicating cerebral].  Maybe it's not talked about it, because a lot of people don't understand it, but I do.  He's special."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. How confident are you with this roster to go into next year to say that you'll be back and not just be back, but go further?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   To be honest, I'm not quite sure what the roster will look like next year.  I think myself, AD, Max Christie, I think Vando has a team option, player option, something like that, I don't know who else -- I mean, the roster is not set.  Obviously that's Rob and the front office, they are going to figure out the best way to put this team together to go forward in the fall.  But it's not like we have a team full of multi-year guys that's stuck in a contract right now.  So, I don't know, we'll see."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. There was a video making the rounds of you shooting before the game, and they were doing a rehearsal for the trophy presentation on the court.  Did that motivate you or annoy you?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   It was a little motivating factor for me tonight."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Obviously all-time scoring record, another season where you essentially defeat Father Time again.  On a personal level, how would you evaluate the season that you had?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I don't know.  I love to play the game.  I love to compete.  I love to be out there for my guys, my teammates, whoever I have that particular year.  I think it was special in the fact that having a first-year coach, first-year coaching staff, to be able to take them to the Western Conference Finals, I think that's dope for Coach Ham and his coaching staff going forward.  That's pretty amazing. For me, it's all about availability for me and keeping my mind sharp and things of that nature, being present on the floor, being present in the locker room and bus rides and plane rides, things of that nature.  It's challenging.  It's challenging for sure.  It was a very challenging season for me, for our ballclub, and obviously we know whatever went on early on or whatever the case may be.  It was cool, a pretty cool ride. But I don't know.  I don't know.  I think it was okay.  I don't like to say it's a successful year because I don't play for anything besides winning championships at this point in my career.  You know, I don't get a kick out of making a Conference [Finals] appearance.  I've done it, a lot.  And it's not fun to me to not be able to be a part of getting to the Finals. But we'll see.  We'll see.  We'll see what happens going forward.  I don't know.  I don't know.  I've got a lot to think about to be honest.  I've got a lot to think about to be honest.  Just for me personally going forward with the game of basketball, I've got a lot to think about. Appreciate it."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA WESTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: LAKERS VS. NUGGETS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=187224",
    "date": "May 20, 2023",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. From a leadership perspective, what's the message to your teammates right now, down 0-3?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I mean, just got to get one.  Just one at a time.  Just focus on Game 4, and you know, that's all you can really think about.  I mean, obviously this game is over and done with.  We had some opportunities but we didn't come through. So just get ready for Monday and just got to get one.  It's a one-game series for us.  Every game counts, obviously."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You guys had I think a one or two-point lead midway through the fourth --",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   One-point lead."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. And then they went on an 11-0 run --",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   We had back-to-back turnovers, they hit two threes, called time-out.  That was the game."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What did you see?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   That was the game.  We had back-to-back turnovers.  After Rui made two free throws, we went up one and had back-to-back turnovers and they hit back-to-back threes, and made us take a time-out and we never got back in rhythm."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. This team has been in a fight-for-survival mode for months.",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   For sure."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Has there been any buildup from that, in terms of like you guys having to be so locked in for, what, 40, 50 games?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Yeah, we still are.  We still are.  We have to come in obviously tomorrow and watch film and be disappointed and upset and whatever the case may be. And use that and use some of the miscues or whatever the case may be, and also some of the things that we did well to apply to Game 4.  You know, that's all you can worry about."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What is Denver doing in the series so far that's allowed them to be successful?  You guys faced them in the Conference Finals a couple years ago; they have All-Stars; they have accomplished with their team.  But where do you think the edge has been for them?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I mean, obviously Jamal was fantastic in the first half today.  He got them off to a great start, and even with that, we were only down three at the half. I think it's been the timely shots by their role players.  Obviously I think the KCPs and Michael Porter Jrs. and Bruce Browns, even Jeff hit a big-time timely shot today when we were kind of going on a run.  I think it's been the supporting cast that have kind of made those timely shots that's allowed them to kind of have the edge."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You guys had \"0.3 percent\" written on the whiteboard very recently signifying your chances of making the playoffs; you did any ways.  Obviously the odds of coming back from a 3-0 deficit are every tougher but is that belief still there?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I mean, it should be.  I hope so.  I can't speak for the guys right now because I don't know what's going on through all their minds right now.  But I still do. So you know, it's time to go right back home and start to refuel and start the treatment process and recovery process and get ready for Monday.  My mindset is always locked in as if it's Game 1."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Follow-up to that.  The only way you can win this is to make history.  You've made history so many times before.  You know the game.  Does that thought even cross your mind that that's the only way you can do it and you would like to make history again, obviously?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Of course.  That's the only mindset for me for sure."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What's the biggest challenge trying to defend Jamal Murray, with him in particular?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I mean, once he gets going, it's kind of hard to turn him off.  I mean, obviously you know, he got going from the very beginning. We watched one clip at halftime where we allowed him to see the ball go in because we didn't match up in transition. And early in the first quarter, and he had one from their left wing by their bench, wide open shot.  And a guy that has that type of rhythm, and we all know, I mean, Jamal is one of those guys in our league that if you -- he'll run off 20 in a quarter or 30 in a half, and that's what he did tonight. So everyone in our league knows that, especially when he gets going and he gets to bouncing and shooting the three-ball, shooting the mid-range, posting up smaller guards. He can score at all three levels of the game - from the paint, from the free throw line and also from the three-point line.  You tip your hat.  He's a hell of a player. Appreciate it."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA WESTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: LAKERS VS. NUGGETS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=187164",
    "date": "May 18, 2023",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. Was that the ankle that you caught late and how is it feeling?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Yeah, I think I stepped on somebody's foot.  I think it was maybe Aaron Gordon or one of the guys underneath the basket, but it will be fine."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What did you feel like when Denver was hitting those five straight threes?  What's the differences in your coverages and what you're trying to do battling Jokic versus what you're giving up on the outside?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Only one of them was uncontested.  All of them was great contests.  Two of Jamal's threes was right in the face of me and AD.  The Michael Porter Jr one by our bench was right in the face of AR after a transition, they were in transition.  Bruce Brown had one as well with a contest. They made -- that was it, the three-point line is what killed us in the fourth, but I didn't see many breakdowns though."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Did they do anything different defensively tonight against you than in Game 1, and what do you think it will take to bounce back in Game 3?",
        "answer": "ANTHONY DAVIS:   No.  I got the same looks.  A lot of them were just short tonight.  I'll be better."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Not that it's an excuse but you guys exerted so much energy early against Jokic, did you feel like fatigue was a factor at all?",
        "answer": "ANTHONY DAVIS:   No. LeBRON JAMES:   I mean, if you're not tired in the postseason, I mean, everybody's tired."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Obviously two teams playing here, you're playing the No. 1 team in the West, and Jamal had a remarkable performance particularly in the fourth quarter.  What did you see out him and what type of rhythm was he able to find against you guys' defense?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   He made shots.  He made shots at the end of the clock when we guarded for 24 seconds, and he made two big-time shots, one over AD and one over myself.  Had his mid-range game going.  But he had his three-point shot going in the fourth.  It's no surprise to anybody, he's done it before.  Hate to be on the other side of it but I don't feel like we had many breakdowns when he was doing what he was doing.  He made shots and sometimes it's a make-or-miss league. I feel like defensively we were really good.  They shot 43 percent for the No. 1 offense in the league.  And so it just sucks that those five threes in the fourth definitely killed us."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What did you guys make of the starting lineup adjustment going back to the starting lineup you guys have been using for most of the second half of the season and just kind of playing bigger lineups in general tonight?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   It doesn't matter at this point who starts, who comes off the bench, it's just about how we can get it done and win a game.  That's all that matters."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. They haven't lost a game at home in the postseason, neither have you guys.  If you include the Play-In I think you won the last seven.  Does that give you guys any more -- is that a benefit for you guys going home knowing you haven't lost a game?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   We still got to play with the same desperation as we did tonight.  We came out with an L but doesn't give us any more comfort.  We can't go into any postseason game with comfort, just because you either haven't lost at home or you're going back home.  I think it's even more you got to be on edge, because when you go home you get in your own bed, get around your family, everybody's being cool and jolly and everything.  Nah, you got to be even more on edge when you go home.  So, we got to understand that going back and being down 0-2.  There's no reason for us to get comfortable."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. After these two games what do you think you need to improve and keep doing now that you are going home?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think we improved from Game 1 to Game 2.  And if we can do the same thing from Game 2 to Game 3, we put ourselves in a position to win."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've been in this position before, every time you've won.  From a mental and emotional standpoint what do you take out of that that can be applied, if anything?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   What you take out of it is the fact that this is not the NCAA tournament, it's the first team to four wins.  We have an opportunity to go home and play great basketball and hold serve.  So until a team beats you four times then you always have an opportunity to come out of it.  So that's the confidence that we should have.  I know it's going to be a tough hill to climb up, but we still have an opportunity to play good basketball and play the best basketball of the series in Game 3. Like I said, if we can get better from Game 2 like we did tonight to Game 3, then we put ourselves in a position to do that."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You made the one three and then you had the two other looks there.  What did you think about those shots that you got down the stretch and just overall, you know, you're coming off 40, your efficiency wasn't there the way it was in Game 1.",
        "answer": "ANTHONY DAVIS:   I liked both the looks.  Made the first.  Second one was back rim.  And the next one in the same exact spot, rims in and out.  So, I liked all the looks that I got today.  Just a lot of them was short.  I'm going to continue to shoot those shots and I got to be better, more efficient, help the team win.  So, I'll be better."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. The dunk in the first half is not a play we often see.  The ball squirts out like that.  There was another play I think in the third where you guys got an offensive rebound and Dennis could have held for one, he shoots.  When the margins are so slim are those the plays that kind of eat at you between now and Game 3?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   No, I mean those are -- obviously you have an opportunity, I mean, my opportunity puts us up 10 and instead it was an eight-point deficit in the game for us.  Obviously, that's sucks that that ball squirted out of my hand like that, whatever the case may be, maybe hit my knee or whatever, but unforced turnover by myself.  Horrible.  Especially on the road.  The same thing at the end of the third.  I missed a three -- I believe we were up five -- I miss a three.  Jamal Murray tried to save it, saves it right to AD and we swing it to AR.  And Dennis had a pretty good look, but we had an opportunity to hold and not take the shot with a five-point lead.  And instead they get the block, Bruce Brown gets the block, Joker pushes it, throws it to the right corner away from our bench.  KCP, we get a great contest on KCP from AR.  And I thought it was a great block by AD, to be completely honest, but they called goaltending, instead of being up five we're up three.  So those are momentum plays, for sure, both of them."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA WESTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: LAKERS VS. NUGGETS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=187108",
    "date": "May 16, 2023",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. Talk about the shift you guys had when Rui was in the lineup and you were playing off-ball on Jokic.",
        "answer": "ANTHONY DAVIS:   Something that we just went to, a little adjustment.  Different adjustment just throughout the course of the game.  We did end up liking it.  Stayed with it for a while.  Maybe something we go to in Game 2, once we go back and look at the film. But just thinking about it right now, something that we liked.  Just to also have me roaming and things like that.  But like I said, good adjustment but we'll go back and look and see ways that we can be better."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What did you notice about the way Denver hit first? Was the key on the glass with Jokic and how did you adjust over the course of the game?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Yeah, it took us a half to get into the game and that was pretty much the ballgame right there.  We have to understand that we have to start from the tip-off, and they punched us in the mouth to start.  I think they had more offensive rebounds than we had total rebounds in the first half, and you know, that led to them getting second-chance points. They also got them on fast break and killed us in the fast break in the first half and was 10-for-10 from the free throw line.  I know the game is won in 48 minutes, but they set the tone in 24 minutes and we were playing catch-up for the next 24."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've been through so many of these before.  How can the team be affected by cutting the margin down to three like you did tonight and going into the next game versus it staying out of reach?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   In postseason it doesn't matter if you cut it to one or you're down 20, if you lose, you lose.  They are 1-0 and we have to come back with desperation going into Game 2.  We have to play better, we have to rebound better.  I thought we did a good job of not turning the ball over.  That's one thing we've been very conscious about in the postseason, but we've been better in transition and tonight we werenâ€™t that great in the first half but we cleaned it up in the second half.  So, we need to be better in all facets of the game."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What was the key to that fourth quarter stretch where you hit Austin a couple times?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Just kind of reading the game.  It's always a game between the game and just reading the game and making the proper reads. You know, they started to go to a 3-4-5, switching pick-and-rolls but any time I was involved with AD they started to switch Jokic onto me and try to keep it body on body, because AD was doing a great job of getting to that pocket and doing what he does best with his floaters and things of that nature. We know we have opportunities and we can go to other things that also can work for us with myself handling the ball, try to get in pick-and-roll, try to get the good matchup, seeing how they are going to play, if they are going to switch or hard show or whatever the case may be and we just try to exploit that and allow AR [Austin Reaves] to get going in the fourth."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You were very complimentary of Jokic before this game.  Can you describe how he played, and in particular, what did you say to him when he made that crazy shot right before the half?",
        "answer": "ANTHONY DAVIS:   I mean, he's a two-time MVP, very skilled, obviously as his numbers show.  Made many tough shots.  We just have to make it tough for him, switching up matchups and schemes on him.  But he's been playing well through the entire season and especially in these playoffs.  You tip your hat to him. And that shot, I just looked at him and just smiled.  Nothing else I could have done, 40 feet away from the basket, one dribble, kind of throws it up and it goes in.  Definitely one of them nights. You know, we're encouraged about the second half of the game, and things we can get better at and make some adjustments going into Game 2."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You guys found stuff after the first half but how much of it do you think was the size on the court to start the game?  You guys didn't go small and they are a pretty big team and I think at one point they had nine offensive rebounds on the first 11 misses in the game.  How much of a factor do you think that was?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Some of them was effort plays.  Some of them was just out of reach.  You know, we had a couple opportunities to get early defensive rebounds; we wasn't able to do that.  One of them was a block-out by me and Jokic coming down the middle was one of his offensive rebounds. I think some of them was effort and some of them is about size but for the majority, some of them in the first half, we wasn't just locked in.  We wasn't in tune.  He had six offensive rebounds in the first quarter; he had six offensive rebounds for the game.  So that just lets you know we started to get more in tune with what we need to do and how we need to block out and how we need to hit bodies and things of that nature, and I think we got better as the game went on."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Austin and Rui said they felt there was a lack of energy and effort in the first half.  Do you agree with that and how do you explain lack of effort in Game 1 of the Western Conference Finals?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   We'll be better.  We'll be better.  We know we didn't play up to our capabilities in the first half.  I even thought in the third quarter when we were going back and forth making shots, I thought we were still in tune with it.  They were just making some, you know, shots with hands in their faces, bodies on bodies. But you know we'll be better in Game 2, that's for sure."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. A lot to be made about Jokic tonight and his performance but what about AD's game?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   AD was phenomenal, 40 and 10, changed shots at the rim.  But he's been -- AD has been great all postseason, so we are not worried about that.  You know, so we just have to do our job, as well, myself, chipping in, everybody down the ladder from there.  It's nothing that surprised us about AD's performance. We have to do a great job of just backing him up, not only on the offensive end to relieve pressure off of him but also on the defensive end, as well.  When he's changing shots, we have to clean glass, we have to help, we have to make our rotations clean.  That allows us to do what we need to do offensively. Appreciate it."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA WESTERN CONFERENCE SEMIFINALS: LAKERS vs  WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=186955",
    "date": "May 10, 2023",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. I wanted to ask you about AD first, just your level of concern with him after he took that shot?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I didn't see the shot.  I just seen the aftermath.  But the medical team said he's doing better.  That's what matters the most."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. How much a part of that do you figure now as you get back for Game 6, a situation you've been in before, maybe a little bit of uncertainty about AD, but how do you approach this as a leader going back on the plane?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   That we have another opportunity.  Obviously they played exceptionally well here tonight, and we had some good moments, but not as close to 48 minutes as we needed to be, but we've got another opportunity on Friday, and we look forward to the matchup again."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. It was a tie game with about four minutes to go in the second quarter and then we know this is a team that can go on runs, but when you think back to the late second quarter, early third that you felt like on your team's end that contributed to that run?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I mean, we kind of made a run, we had an opportunity to -- I missed an easy jump hook in the lane to cut the lead to three.  AD, right after I missed the jump hook, he had an opportunity to have a tip dunk, missed it.  We blew a coverage, Klay hit a three on that right wing, put them up eight, and then we came back down, missed again, and then Steph hit the big one at the end of the quarter. We know they're a team of runs, and you've got to be able to match that, and they just kept it going in the third, obviously."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. The conversation the last 48 hours has been, from the Warriors standpoint, gamesmanship from your team and flopping.  Do you feel like that affected anything in terms of the way the game was dealt with tonight on the court?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I just know that our coaching staff and us players, we don't work on flopping.  That's not even a part of our game.  Our game is to attack, attack the paint.  We don't mind physical contact.  We actually like the contact.  We don't shy away from it. We're just not a team that goes out there looking for flopping opportunities.  That's just not us.  It's actually never been any team that I've played on in my 20 years where we've been a flopping team.  It is what it is.  They have their right to say what they want to say, but the game is always won between the four lines, and we've got to be better on Friday for sure."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Earlier today you were named to the all-NBA third team.  I think this is 19 straight years for you.  Knowing what you've done and dealt with physically and stuff like that, how does this one hit differently in year 20?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I guess I don't take those moments for granted.  When you get an opportunity to be recognized as one of the best players still in the league and have one of the best seasons and make all-NBA team, I don't take anything that I've been able to accomplish for granted and I'm always appreciative for the -- to be a part of any selection in this league.  There's so many great players, so many great teams, and a lot of guys this year had some really good seasons, great seasons.  To be a part of that class of 15 guys, when I seen the list, is still pretty cool, even at my age and where I'm at right now, year 20.  Just don't take it for granted. Obviously I've got bigger fish to fry, but those small moments, those small wins right there is all part of the journey, all part of the legacy as far as what I do on the floor in this league, so that's pretty cool."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. In your career, you've played in plenty of Game 6s where you have a chance to clinch.  You also just had that last series.  Is there something you think this team this year needs to focus on Friday in comparison to the past?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I mean, every moment is its own challenge and is its own game and is its own opportunity to see what you're made of, and we can't base last series on to this series.  This series is different.  The opponent is different.  The challenges is different. Friday is another opportunity for us to see where we are, to see what we're made of, and to go out there with I guess the grit and the fight that we've had since we came together after the All-Star break, very resilient team, and we respond well to adversity, and we look forward to that, to getting an opportunity to play again on Friday."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You guys are 6-0 between the play-in, first round through the Warriors series at Crypto.com this postseason.  I wanted to know if you have any message for the Laker fans planning to come to the game on Friday?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Well, we didn't handle our business tonight, so I look forward to seeing our fans for another game in the second round.  You know, those six games are out the window.  It's over and done with.  Our job is to try to be 1-0 on Friday.  I look forward to that opportunity."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Last Game 6 you guys played, you said you guys approached it like Game 7 mentality, didn't want to go back to Memphis for Game 7.  I assume the same approach going into this one?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Yeah, it's the same.  It's the same."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA WESTERN CONFERENCE SEMIFINALS: LAKERS vs  WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=186871",
    "date": "May 4, 2023",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, after Game 1 you said you were anticipating some differences.  What did you find to be the most effective?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   They made their adjustments.  We knew they were going to do that.  That's what a championship team does.  They held serve on their home court tonight. We got to obviously see the adjustments they made, we got to make our adjustments coming into Game 3."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. A.D., Draymond started on you.  Played different with the spread offense.  How did that impact you?",
        "answer": "ANTHONY DAVIS:   I don't think so.  I mean, I took all the same shots I took in Game 1.  I just missed them.  Elbow jumpers.  Pocket passes to the floater.  Same exact looks.  Didn't shoot no shot that I didn't shoot in Game 1.  Just missed them.  That's all. Like Bron said, made adjustments, shot the ball extremely well from three. We'll be better.  I'll be better making those shots.  We'll get back home on our home floor and try to take care of business."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Where did you feel like the game slipped away tonight?  Was it the third quarter or before halftime?",
        "answer": "ANTHONY DAVIS:   Yeah, I mean, going into half, up 11, went on a run.  Then obviously third quarter, we know they're a big third quarter team.  Came out, had 43 in the third, also 41 in the second.  Not like us on the defensive end to give up those type of quarters. So we got to be better defensively.  I think going into halftime, made that run, got away from us."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, you've seen them go on crazy runs in games.  What is the key to not letting those build and stack?  How do you have to combat that?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   You got to keep scoring, get to the free-throw line as well, or just get points in the paint.  They're going to go on runs.  That's what they do.  But you got to keep scoring, try to hold the fort down. You give credit where credit is due.  They played exceptionally well tonight and we didn't.  The series is tied 1-1.  That's where we're at."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've been one of the best defensive teams in the league over the last month plus.  Warriors are pretty unique the way they play compared to the rest of the league.  What do you think it will take to make your defense shine as much as it has?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   We still are.  That doesn't change.  We're still the best defensive team in the league, if not one of them.  So that doesn't change.  That's what we hang our hats on. But like I said, you give credit where credit is due.  Klay was spectacular tonight.  Draymond was great in the pocket pass with the rolls, things of that nature.  JaMychal gave them big-time.  Those 12 minutes felt like 24 minutes, 30 minutes.  He was big-time for their team in the starting role tonight, too. You give credit, like I said where credit is due.  We move on to the next game.  But our defense, that's where we hang our hat.  That doesn't stop no matter who we're playing against."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Did you come out of this all right, how do you feel?  Do you feel you contested their three-pointers enough in this game?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   We feel great, and yes, we contested threes."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. When they go small, it stretches the defense, gets shooters to the corners.  Does that change the way they were able to defend you with their movement?  Did you feel they were more active in passing lanes?",
        "answer": "ANTHONY DAVIS:   Yeah, I think they were a little more active in the pocket.  They kind of clogged the paint in our pocket passes that were pretty open Game 1.  Didn't help that we didn't really shoot the ball well from three. If we start making those shots, making those threes, be tough for them to pull in to kind of take away those pocket passes, us playing in the paint. That's all I think it was.  They made an emphasis on making sure they tried to find the guys on the perimeter, on the three-point line, clog the paint up a little bit."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA WESTERN CONFERENCE SEMIFINALS: LAKERS vs  WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=186838",
    "date": "May 2, 2023",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. Everyone knew coming into this series when you look at the Warriors' lineup that you could be a featured part of the Lakers attack.  What do you think allowed you to be so effective tonight?",
        "answer": "ANTHONY DAVIS:   The guys gave the ball to me in the right spots.  A lot of it came out of pick and roll, post-ups, some offensive rebounds.  Just being aggressive when I do catch, looking to score, looking to play make to the other guys. That was the guards finding me early, which allowed them to play free later on in the game."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, this team has been through challenges throughout the course of the season.  What did you think of the mental resolve to withstand a 14-0 run in this building late and close those guys out with poise?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I mean, that's been us since we made acquisitions with our new guys.  We've been able to be very resilient in games.  Like I said, we've been playing lot of basketball for about two and a half months now, just trying to punch our clock and to be able to play right now in the post-season. We've been very resilient.  Tonight versus a team like Golden State, defending champions, we know how great they are on their home floor over the years.  To withstand that, it's another good step for our ballclub."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Anthony, thinking about Game 2 and adjustments that Golden State might make, what are the ways that you think it changes when they go smaller or Draymond plays more of a five?  What do you expect from them in their building in Game 2?",
        "answer": "ANTHONY DAVIS:   It's going to be a different game.  They're going to make adjustments.  We're going to make adjustments.  The building will be probably a little bit louder.  Obviously they don't want to go down 0-2.  The crowd will be more into it. I'm going to continue to be aggressive.  I know our guys are going to continue to be aggressive.  Obviously we know that Draymond likes the help, so if they do decide to put him on me, figure out ways I can be effective with him doing his thing defensively. But who knows.  I mean, we'll see what happens in Game 2 if they make that adjustment.  If they don't, still try to find ways to attack."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What did you make of the defensive game plan tonight?  Felt like you guys were controlling them defensively.",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   We've got to do a better job.  I think even though late they made a run, throughout the second half only giving up 48 points, that's really good.  But we had a couple lulls when they allowed those guys, Steph, Klay and Jordan, to get some looks, they were really tuned in.  They're going to get their looks anyways, so we can't have our own personal problems.  We got to be better.  We got to be better. We love the game plan, but we got to be better as the guys on the floor."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. A.D., as much as you dominated in the post-season, do you feel like you're proving people wrong or does that matter to you?",
        "answer": "ANTHONY DAVIS:   It doesn't matter to me.  I don't care what no one thinks.  Only the guys in the locker room, coaching staff, only opinions that I care about.  Other than that, I just go out and play basketball, do what I can do to help the team win. Opinions outside the locker room, what guys say, guys think, is irrelevant to me."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Coach Ham said both you guys have kind of been a rock for him, kept him afloat mentally in a lot of ways.  What kind of advice have you had for coach?  What do you think about how he's grown this rookie season for him?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   For us, we've been a part of this franchise the longest that's on this franchise right now.  We've had our battles together. For us to be able to have that relationship with the coaching staff, have that relationship with Coach Ham, him to be able to trust us on the floor that we can be a extension of his, relay his commands, his messages, it just makes it a lot calming for him that he knows he has guys on the floor that has been in a fight, has been in a foxhole and has experience in tough games. Every game and every day is another learning experience for our coaching staff and for us.  We just try to make it as seamless as possible when we step on the floor with the game plan they're giving us."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You probably knew they were going to make a run towards the end.  When you were not able to score and they did catch you, was that a lack of execution on your part or did you simply miss some shots?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   No, never a lack of execution with us.  At the end of the day we only had eight turnovers, so that let us know we was not sloppy with the ball.  We were executing at a high level. Just missed some shots.  I can think about four or five shots.  A.R. had a shot from the left wing, missed it.  I had a fade-away jumper in the paint and missed it.  I was able to hit A.D. on a cut.  One of his patent jump hooks, he missed it, got the offensive rebound, missed it again.  They lost it around their sideline, gave us another extra possession.  A.D. had a wide-open three opposite of their bench. Sometimes it's a make-or-miss league.  We executed to perfection, we just didn't make it."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, both you guys aren't too statistically inclined, it's about getting the W.  You had the 20/20 last round, A.D. has a 30/20.  He joins Shaq, Elgin, Kareem and Wilt, franchise players who have done that.  How does that encapsulate him joining a list like that, what he's doing for your team right now?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I mean, the Lakers franchise over the years, over the course of their existence, has always had dominant big men, dominant guys that have been a force at the rim.  That's why their jerseys are in the rafters.  A.D. will be up there when he's done playing.  The No. 3 will be up in the rafters. He continues to show why he's one of the best players that we have in this league.  For us, it's a treat for us to be able to have such a dynamic player that cannot only go out and get you 30 and 20, but also command the paint defensively, can switch out the guards, also get you five assists, as well. It's a treat for us, a treat for the Laker franchise to have another one that wears the purple and gold that's in the present right now."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, you have had a lot of great historical games against Warriors in the old stadium.  How do you feel winning your first Playoff game in the new Chase Center as a Laker?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   It's always great to win in the post-season, no matter where you are, no matter who you're playing.  It's very difficult to win in the post-season. Like you said, I got a lot of history in Oracle, a lot of battles in that arena over the years.  It's definitely a different feeling walking here into a post-season game, being in the Chase Arena now, like you said. That Warriors and the GS, those colors hasn't changed.  So my focus and my respect for them hasn't changed, as well.  It's just an honor to be able to play this game at a high level, play with other great players, then also look on the other side and see other great players, being a part of that's historic, something that lasts a lot longer than we are today.  That's pretty cool.  Thank you."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR GAME 2023",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=183866",
    "date": "February 19, 2023",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, how do you view the 23 games remaining in the Lakers' season in terms of the challenges that you've had in your career?  Obviously, the goal everyone is stating is to make the postseason.",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   It's 23 of the most important games of my career for a regular season.  It's the type of mindset that I have and I hope the guys will have coming back off the break."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Physically, how are you feeling for that 23-game stretch knowing that obviously things can change?  You've been battling this foot thing.  How has this time off helped, and how did you come out of Thursday's game?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   This couple of days has helped, not having to stress it being out on the floor.  So it's helped.  I'm going to try not to go too crazy in the game.  I'm going to have some fun, but not go too crazy. The most important thing for me right now is to maintain my health and be available to my teammates after this break because we have to make a strong push if we want to do anything special. So feeling pretty good right now.  I came out of the game Wednesday feeling pretty good."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, first of all, looked like you got away for a couple of days with Savannah.  What did that time away do for your mindset?  Now that you've had a couple of days to think about how that game went right before the break, what are your thoughts about the flow of the new team and roster?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Well, I mean, it's always great to spend time with your best friend, so that's always unique. As far as our team, I love what we were able to accomplish the other day, on Wednesday night.  The worst thing for us is that we had to go on a break.  I would have loved if we could have played Friday and got a couple of games under our belt because it's the first time our whole group was together from top to bottom. But it is what it is.  We all take advantage of it.  We all take advantage of the rest.  Kind of get some nicks and bruises out of the way if any guys had them. It's not saying they're all going to just go away, but you can feel a little bit better, for sure, going into next week."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I know you're focused on the last 23, of course, but did you take any time during the break just to reflect on what the chase meant, what the record means, the significance it had to so many people outside of yourself?  And in a weird way, are you kind of glad it's over so you can focus on the playoff push?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   No, I did not.  Literally the only time that I kind of had a little reflection is when the Lakers' social media post, they posted the one with my whole family on there that I actually posted I believe yesterday or the other day.  It's hard for me to stop watching that because watching Zhuri's reaction to that is, like, the greatest -- it's so cool. If I'm having a bad day, I know exactly where I can go to fix my day.  Seeing Zhuri's reaction to that moment was pretty, pretty cool. It's not like I'm happy that it's over, because I didn't put too much pressure on myself for it.  It's not like it was something that I was -- I wasn't chasing it.  I was just hooping, I guess, and it just happened. It came organically because I've been available.  I've put the work in.  I've been gifted to do some great things out on the floor, and I just tried to apply that every single night that I was available to my teammates and my franchise, the three franchises I played for. It wasn't like a stress release or a stress relief because it wasn't something I really had a goal set of doing."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Leading up to the scoring record, you always said that you had no idea how you would react. Were you surprised by how much it hit you and how much it has hit you since?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I don't know if it's really sunk in to what I was able to accomplish.  I know the history of the game.  I know there are some records and there are some accomplishments.  There are some things that happened that people questioned when it happened years before that if they would ever see it again or if it would ever be eclipsed or if it would ever be taken over. I know the history of sport and professional sports that I'm a part of.  So I understand the significance and how special that is.  But as far as me individually, I don't know. It's hit me a couple of times.  I was able to see that video and see my daughter's reaction, and that was pretty cool.  Just the warm reception that I've gotten from family and friends and peers and things of that nature, I understand that it was something that's pretty cool and could stand for quite a while."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, this is now 19 All-Star Game (selections) for you, tying Kareem's record.  What does that mean to you in the history of the NBA?  And also wanted to ask you about you think of the development of Lauri Markkanen?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I'll answer your first question.  It's an honor.  Any time I'm compared to any of the greats that have played this game, those guys laid the path both on the floor and off the floor for guys like myself to be able to walk, talk, run, jump, do the things that I do every single day.  So it's pretty cool being a part of history. As far as Lauri, I think it's all about more and more opportunity.  The talent has always been there since he came from Arizona and he got drafted by the Bulls.  You saw the talent. Then when he went to Cleveland, you saw the talent as well, what he is capable of doing.  But now he is a centerpiece, focal point here in Utah, and he is able to showcase not only his talent, but showcase it even more because they run a lot through him.  So he is able to do it more often. Always been a talented kid.  And I've always liked him because he has always worn LeBron shoes, too, so he has always been cool with me (smiling)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. With the new change of the draft process this year, how do you see this will bring a new excitement to yourself and all the others?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I don't know.  I guess it just takes us back -- it's taken me back to grade school, when you lined everybody up across the free throw line and you had two captains and you picked.  You know?  I take him.  I take him.  I take her.  You know?  You go from there. That's what I'm envisioning it being today.  That's pretty much it.  I think it's going to be cool for the fans to be able to witness that.  A lot of people who never have been put in that position or being able to draft teams and things of that nature.  I think it's a different format, so it will be pretty cool.  We'll see what happens."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I want to go back to the top where you said the next 23 games will be some of the most important of your career.  Given everything that you've accomplished over 20 years, that's a pretty strong statement.  Why do you feel that way about this particular season?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Because I want to make a push to make the playoffs.  I don't want to see myself not being part of the postseason for two years straight.  It's just not part of my DNA.  We're sitting up here talking about the record and things of that nature, and that's all cool, but I'm more passionate about trying to make the postseason and give ourselves a chance to compete for another Larry O'Brien Trophy. That's just who I am.  That's what I'm cut from.  So I hope I can figure out a way to just make sure that I'm available on the floor every single night for these 23 games to give us a chance, give our group a chance to be able to compete every night and give ourselves a chance to win every night so we can give ourselves a chance to get into the postseason."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. As you reach milestone after milestone, play year after year, how does that affect the way you reflect on the accomplishments that you've had and continue to get?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I don't really think about it.  I'm not a guy who kind of, like, basks in his accomplishments.  I've won the championship four times in my career, and pretty much after the three parades or the celebration that we had, I was right back trying to figure out what the team was going to look like next year and how I can be better the following year.  That's just who I am. I guess when I throw the shoes over the wire, or over the backboard, and say this is it for me, then maybe I'll have an opportunity to sit back with my friends and my family, my buddies, we sit down and drink some wine, drink some Lobos and enjoy just the journey then. But I'm very weird when it comes to celebrating myself.  I'm not comfortable with that.  Hopefully I'll get better.  I should get better at some point."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. There are a lot of Chinese people that come here that just want to see you in person, especially at All-Star.  Can you show some love to them?  They would be so happy for that.",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I'm here.  I'm here.  I'm here for all my Chinese fans -- ni hao, xie xie, all that good stuff.  Let's have a good time in Salt Lake.  Yeah, welcome."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, what would you consider your secret to your longevity?  And you spoke about many times how you would like to play with Bronny before you end your career, but the way that you are playing now, do you see even an opportunity where you may be able to play with Bryce before your career is over, considering how well you're still playing?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   My secret?  Well, I tell you my secret, it wouldn't be a secret anymore.  But I would say just dedicating myself to the game.  I've never cheated the game.  There's a saying in sports called the \"game gods,\" and when you cheat the game gods or you shortcut the game gods, karma comes with that, and they will figure out a way to get you back. I learned that at a very young age. I've never cheated the process of how great I can be or how I can maximize my potential or how I can try to be the best teammate or how I can put myself in a position that I can help our team win. So I think that's part of it.  The game has given back to me, and I always just try to give everything I can back to the game. As far as Bryce, yeah, listen, I don't know how much longer I got to play in this beautiful game.  I know I'm on the other side of the hill, for sure.  I'm not doing another 20.  That's for damn sure.  I'm not doing that (laughing).  But we'll see what happens. Most important for my kids, at the end of the day I just want them to continue to be great -- just great young men.  Sports and all that other stuff will take care of itself."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. A couple of months ago you mentioned that you would like to own a team, bring it to Las Vegas and so forth.  Your thoughts on that.  But, also, maybe it's two, three, four years away, whatever, but last night -- or yesterday we were talking to Kyrie, and he was kind of mentioning how cool it would be for some of the players to start with the diverse ownership and if they have the wherewithal to be owners of teams and from the top down kind of own teams.  Can you talk a little bit about that, and just your continued desire, Vegas and whatever?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I can speak about myself.  I am not fortunate enough to be able to see the full transcript of what Kyrie said, so I don't want to mix up any words that he had to say.  But as far as myself, I see myself being a part of the game even when I'm done playing. Ownership is something I'm a part of now off the court in a lot of things that I do.  To be able to translate that to the game of basketball, I feel like I could give back to this game in so many fashions, even when I'm not in uniform, that could benefit the sport. I would love to at some point down the road own an NBA franchise and be able to bring a winning franchise to a city.  Like I said, Vegas is a really cool city, and they're doing some great things in sports these days. Obviously, you see what the Aces are doing.  You have the Raiders there.  You have the Kings there, the hockey team.  They're doing a lot of great things down there. We'll see what happens and go from there.  I think it's the Kings.  It's not the Kings, is it?  The who?  The Golden Knights, yes.  Kings are in L.A., right?  Oh, two Kings in L.A.  Got it (smiling)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I'm sure you went beyond your dreams with all your amazing accomplishments, but usually when a dream comes true, there's a new goal coming up.  What is your dream right now to shape your legacy the way you want it to be, and what did it take for you to become the man and athlete you've become?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   To continue to build my community.  I started a long time ago, and right now, if you ever have an opportunity to go to Akron, Ohio, we can point you guys in the right direction to see what we got going on down there with my foundation. Just trying to build up the community, build up a lot of underprivileged kids to make them feel wanted and loved and like their dreams can become reality. So we have a lot of things going on not only with the I Promise School and the University of Akron, but with the housing community that we have where we're bringing in families that are underprivileged that can't afford their own housing. That's just three things.  There's so much that we have going on, but we want to continue to build that and hopefully take it somewhere else at some point, but obviously the most important thing for me is the streets and the places that I rode my bike and walked on. That is definitely a big part of my legacy, if not the biggest when it comes to everything I do off the floor."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You said obviously one of the most important stretches of your career in terms of regular-season games.  You want to get in the postseason again.  You look at how the Western Conference seems about as wide open as it's been in a long time.  You could say the same thing for the league.  How good a chance do you feel like you guys have if you could just get in, and how wide open do you think things are this year compared to normal?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Obviously, it's game by game.  Take it one game at a time and let the chips fall where they may. I've always been confident in any club that I've been on once we got into the playoffs that we can compete with anyone, and I feel no different now.  With the roster the way we're shaped up right now, if we can finish off this regular season on the right foot, then we can compete versus anyone in the Western Conference, if not the whole league. But it's going to take a lot of commitment, which is okay.  That's what it should be about.  We're professionals.  What else do we have to do?  Make sure the family is good when you leave the house.  You have people helping you around the house.  Y'all good?  Let's commit to this.  Let's commit to this and go from there. But, yeah, I feel like we can -- if we can punch our ticket, we can compete versus anyone."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I also sit on the brand team of Titan, which you know well, obviously.  We've had three collaborations --",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   We sure have."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. -- on your signature shoe.  I think on paper there's not a lot that a Filipino kid from Manila and the NBA's all-time leading scorer have in common, but through your generosity of your platform and your signature sneaker, you've allowed Titan to tell parts of that Filipino story, this audacious love for basketball that Filipinos have.  I think Filipinos, especially young Filipinos, all around the world feel seen.  They feel validated by the game's greatest athlete.  I was just hoping to ask you to maybe reflect a little bit on what our teams have accomplished on those three collaborations so far.  Without giving away too much, maybe your excitement for what our teams have planned in the future.",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   First of all, before we even collaborated, I had an opportunity to go to the Philippines and do a couple of things with Nike and continue to promote the game of basketball.  Played in a couple of All-Star Games over there as well.  Went throughout the city and had an unbelievable time being in the Philippines.  I always had a great deal of respect and love for Manila.  It's great. As far as our collaboration and our partnership, I think it's only going to continue to get better as we continue to not only dive into each other, dive into what we love about each other, but also about our own core values, which we share. You know, that Titan and crown representation goes hand in hand. It's been a great journey so far, and I'm looking forward to continuing that."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Curious about your love of basketball in the '90s.  Do you recall your routine as a kid in the '90s getting ready to watch the All-Star Game on Sunday?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I'm not going to sit up here and say I remember my routine, but I believe the first All-Star Game that I actually sat down and watched was the -- was it '97 in Cleveland?  Because it actually came on local television, so we could watch it in Akron on local television.  '97.  Kobe was a rookie.  MJ was in that game.  It was pretty cool for me and my friends.  I think we were 11 years old at the time or 13.  Thirteen at the time. I got an opportunity to watch that game.  Wasn't fortunate enough to be able to watch some of the games before that because a lot of those games were nationally televised games, and I didn't have nationally televised channels.  No cable.  Just the local channels. I don't remember the routine, but I definitely just remember watching, like, the national anthem and just they're panning from left to right to all the All-Stars and me visualizing someday, through the grace of God and through hard work and dedication and my love for the game, maybe I could be one of those kids someday that could stand across that free throw line and be a part of a national anthem in an All-Star Game.  I thought it was pretty cool.  So, yeah."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Just wondering if you could talk about Josh Giddey's game and the season he is having so far.",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Josh Giddey is really, really good, man.  Obviously, a tall point guard.  He is a triple-double-type of playmaker every single night because of his ability to rebound at his size, his distinctive passing and he has the ability to score in the paint. I think he is going to continue to get better and better.  They have a really good young core over in OKC.  They don't even have Chet there just yet. Josh is a really good player, along with the other rookies that they have this year.  Obviously, we know first-time (All-Star) Shai is really good and the rest of that crew over there. Pretty good player, for sure.  You guys should be proud."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "ALL-STAR GAME: TEAM GIANNIS VS. TEAM LEBRON",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=183867",
    "date": "February 19, 2023",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, how do you view the 23 games remaining in the Lakers' season in terms of the challenges that you've had in your career?  Obviously, the goal everyone is stating is to make the postseason.",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   It's 23 of the most important games of my career for a regular season.  It's the type of mindset that I have and I hope the guys will have coming back off the break."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Physically, how are you feeling for that 23-game stretch knowing that obviously things can change?  You've been battling this foot thing.  How has this time off helped, and how did you come out of Thursday's game?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   This couple of days has helped, not having to stress it being out on the floor.  So it's helped.  I'm going to try not to go too crazy in the game.  I'm going to have some fun, but not go too crazy. The most important thing for me right now is to maintain my health and be available to my teammates after this break because we have to make a strong push if we want to do anything special. So feeling pretty good right now.  I came out of the game Wednesday feeling pretty good."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, first of all, looked like you got away for a couple of days with Savannah.  What did that time away do for your mindset?  Now that you've had a couple of days to think about how that game went right before the break, what are your thoughts about the flow of the new team and roster?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Well, I mean, it's always great to spend time with your best friend, so that's always unique. As far as our team, I love what we were able to accomplish the other day, on Wednesday night.  The worst thing for us is that we had to go on a break.  I would have loved if we could have played Friday and got a couple of games under our belt because it's the first time our whole group was together from top to bottom. But it is what it is.  We all take advantage of it.  We all take advantage of the rest.  Kind of get some nicks and bruises out of the way if any guys had them. It's not saying they're all going to just go away, but you can feel a little bit better, for sure, going into next week."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I know you're focused on the last 23, of course, but did you take any time during the break just to reflect on what the chase meant, what the record means, the significance it had to so many people outside of yourself?  And in a weird way, are you kind of glad it's over so you can focus on the playoff push?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   No, I did not.  Literally the only time that I kind of had a little reflection is when the Lakers' social media post, they posted the one with my whole family on there that I actually posted I believe yesterday or the other day.  It's hard for me to stop watching that because watching Zhuri's reaction to that is, like, the greatest -- it's so cool. If I'm having a bad day, I know exactly where I can go to fix my day.  Seeing Zhuri's reaction to that moment was pretty, pretty cool. It's not like I'm happy that it's over, because I didn't put too much pressure on myself for it.  It's not like it was something that I was -- I wasn't chasing it.  I was just hooping, I guess, and it just happened. It came organically because I've been available.  I've put the work in.  I've been gifted to do some great things out on the floor, and I just tried to apply that every single night that I was available to my teammates and my franchise, the three franchises I played for. It wasn't like a stress release or a stress relief because it wasn't something I really had a goal set of doing."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Leading up to the scoring record, you always said that you had no idea how you would react. Were you surprised by how much it hit you and how much it has hit you since?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I don't know if it's really sunk in to what I was able to accomplish.  I know the history of the game.  I know there are some records and there are some accomplishments.  There are some things that happened that people questioned when it happened years before that if they would ever see it again or if it would ever be eclipsed or if it would ever be taken over. I know the history of sport and professional sports that I'm a part of.  So I understand the significance and how special that is.  But as far as me individually, I don't know. It's hit me a couple of times.  I was able to see that video and see my daughter's reaction, and that was pretty cool.  Just the warm reception that I've gotten from family and friends and peers and things of that nature, I understand that it was something that's pretty cool and could stand for quite a while."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, this is now 19 All-Star Game (selections) for you, tying Kareem's record.  What does that mean to you in the history of the NBA?  And also wanted to ask you about you think of the development of Lauri Markkanen?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I'll answer your first question.  It's an honor.  Any time I'm compared to any of the greats that have played this game, those guys laid the path both on the floor and off the floor for guys like myself to be able to walk, talk, run, jump, do the things that I do every single day.  So it's pretty cool being a part of history. As far as Lauri, I think it's all about more and more opportunity.  The talent has always been there since he came from Arizona and he got drafted by the Bulls.  You saw the talent. Then when he went to Cleveland, you saw the talent as well, what he is capable of doing.  But now he is a centerpiece, focal point here in Utah, and he is able to showcase not only his talent, but showcase it even more because they run a lot through him.  So he is able to do it more often. Always been a talented kid.  And I've always liked him because he has always worn LeBron shoes, too, so he has always been cool with me (smiling)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. With the new change of the draft process this year, how do you see this will bring a new excitement to yourself and all the others?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I don't know.  I guess it just takes us back -- it's taken me back to grade school, when you lined everybody up across the free throw line and you had two captains and you picked.  You know?  I take him.  I take him.  I take her.  You know?  You go from there. That's what I'm envisioning it being today.  That's pretty much it.  I think it's going to be cool for the fans to be able to witness that.  A lot of people who never have been put in that position or being able to draft teams and things of that nature.  I think it's a different format, so it will be pretty cool.  We'll see what happens."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I want to go back to the top where you said the next 23 games will be some of the most important of your career.  Given everything that you've accomplished over 20 years, that's a pretty strong statement.  Why do you feel that way about this particular season?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Because I want to make a push to make the playoffs.  I don't want to see myself not being part of the postseason for two years straight.  It's just not part of my DNA.  We're sitting up here talking about the record and things of that nature, and that's all cool, but I'm more passionate about trying to make the postseason and give ourselves a chance to compete for another Larry O'Brien Trophy. That's just who I am.  That's what I'm cut from.  So I hope I can figure out a way to just make sure that I'm available on the floor every single night for these 23 games to give us a chance, give our group a chance to be able to compete every night and give ourselves a chance to win every night so we can give ourselves a chance to get into the postseason."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. As you reach milestone after milestone, play year after year, how does that affect the way you reflect on the accomplishments that you've had and continue to get?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I don't really think about it.  I'm not a guy who kind of, like, basks in his accomplishments.  I've won the championship four times in my career, and pretty much after the three parades or the celebration that we had, I was right back trying to figure out what the team was going to look like next year and how I can be better the following year.  That's just who I am. I guess when I throw the shoes over the wire, or over the backboard, and say this is it for me, then maybe I'll have an opportunity to sit back with my friends and my family, my buddies, we sit down and drink some wine, drink some Lobos and enjoy just the journey then. But I'm very weird when it comes to celebrating myself.  I'm not comfortable with that.  Hopefully I'll get better.  I should get better at some point."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. There are a lot of Chinese people that come here that just want to see you in person, especially at All-Star.  Can you show some love to them?  They would be so happy for that.",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I'm here.  I'm here.  I'm here for all my Chinese fans -- ni hao, xie xie, all that good stuff.  Let's have a good time in Salt Lake.  Yeah, welcome."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, what would you consider your secret to your longevity?  And you spoke about many times how you would like to play with Bronny before you end your career, but the way that you are playing now, do you see even an opportunity where you may be able to play with Bryce before your career is over, considering how well you're still playing?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   My secret?  Well, I tell you my secret, it wouldn't be a secret anymore.  But I would say just dedicating myself to the game.  I've never cheated the game.  There's a saying in sports called the \"game gods,\" and when you cheat the game gods or you shortcut the game gods, karma comes with that, and they will figure out a way to get you back. I learned that at a very young age. I've never cheated the process of how great I can be or how I can maximize my potential or how I can try to be the best teammate or how I can put myself in a position that I can help our team win. So I think that's part of it.  The game has given back to me, and I always just try to give everything I can back to the game. As far as Bryce, yeah, listen, I don't know how much longer I got to play in this beautiful game.  I know I'm on the other side of the hill, for sure.  I'm not doing another 20.  That's for damn sure.  I'm not doing that (laughing).  But we'll see what happens. Most important for my kids, at the end of the day I just want them to continue to be great -- just great young men.  Sports and all that other stuff will take care of itself."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. A couple of months ago you mentioned that you would like to own a team, bring it to Las Vegas and so forth.  Your thoughts on that.  But, also, maybe it's two, three, four years away, whatever, but last night -- or yesterday we were talking to Kyrie, and he was kind of mentioning how cool it would be for some of the players to start with the diverse ownership and if they have the wherewithal to be owners of teams and from the top down kind of own teams.  Can you talk a little bit about that, and just your continued desire, Vegas and whatever?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I can speak about myself.  I am not fortunate enough to be able to see the full transcript of what Kyrie said, so I don't want to mix up any words that he had to say.  But as far as myself, I see myself being a part of the game even when I'm done playing. Ownership is something I'm a part of now off the court in a lot of things that I do.  To be able to translate that to the game of basketball, I feel like I could give back to this game in so many fashions, even when I'm not in uniform, that could benefit the sport. I would love to at some point down the road own an NBA franchise and be able to bring a winning franchise to a city.  Like I said, Vegas is a really cool city, and they're doing some great things in sports these days. Obviously, you see what the Aces are doing.  You have the Raiders there.  You have the Kings there, the hockey team.  They're doing a lot of great things down there. We'll see what happens and go from there.  I think it's the Kings.  It's not the Kings, is it?  The who?  The Golden Knights, yes.  Kings are in L.A., right?  Oh, two Kings in L.A.  Got it (smiling)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I'm sure you went beyond your dreams with all your amazing accomplishments, but usually when a dream comes true, there's a new goal coming up.  What is your dream right now to shape your legacy the way you want it to be, and what did it take for you to become the man and athlete you've become?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   To continue to build my community.  I started a long time ago, and right now, if you ever have an opportunity to go to Akron, Ohio, we can point you guys in the right direction to see what we got going on down there with my foundation. Just trying to build up the community, build up a lot of underprivileged kids to make them feel wanted and loved and like their dreams can become reality. So we have a lot of things going on not only with the I Promise School and the University of Akron, but with the housing community that we have where we're bringing in families that are underprivileged that can't afford their own housing. That's just three things.  There's so much that we have going on, but we want to continue to build that and hopefully take it somewhere else at some point, but obviously the most important thing for me is the streets and the places that I rode my bike and walked on. That is definitely a big part of my legacy, if not the biggest when it comes to everything I do off the floor."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You said obviously one of the most important stretches of your career in terms of regular-season games.  You want to get in the postseason again.  You look at how the Western Conference seems about as wide open as it's been in a long time.  You could say the same thing for the league.  How good a chance do you feel like you guys have if you could just get in, and how wide open do you think things are this year compared to normal?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Obviously, it's game by game.  Take it one game at a time and let the chips fall where they may. I've always been confident in any club that I've been on once we got into the playoffs that we can compete with anyone, and I feel no different now.  With the roster the way we're shaped up right now, if we can finish off this regular season on the right foot, then we can compete versus anyone in the Western Conference, if not the whole league. But it's going to take a lot of commitment, which is okay.  That's what it should be about.  We're professionals.  What else do we have to do?  Make sure the family is good when you leave the house.  You have people helping you around the house.  Y'all good?  Let's commit to this.  Let's commit to this and go from there. But, yeah, I feel like we can -- if we can punch our ticket, we can compete versus anyone."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I also sit on the brand team of Titan, which you know well, obviously.  We've had three collaborations --",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   We sure have."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. -- on your signature shoe.  I think on paper there's not a lot that a Filipino kid from Manila and the NBA's all-time leading scorer have in common, but through your generosity of your platform and your signature sneaker, you've allowed Titan to tell parts of that Filipino story, this audacious love for basketball that Filipinos have.  I think Filipinos, especially young Filipinos, all around the world feel seen.  They feel validated by the game's greatest athlete.  I was just hoping to ask you to maybe reflect a little bit on what our teams have accomplished on those three collaborations so far.  Without giving away too much, maybe your excitement for what our teams have planned in the future.",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   First of all, before we even collaborated, I had an opportunity to go to the Philippines and do a couple of things with Nike and continue to promote the game of basketball.  Played in a couple of All-Star Games over there as well.  Went throughout the city and had an unbelievable time being in the Philippines.  I always had a great deal of respect and love for Manila.  It's great. As far as our collaboration and our partnership, I think it's only going to continue to get better as we continue to not only dive into each other, dive into what we love about each other, but also about our own core values, which we share. You know, that Titan and crown representation goes hand in hand. It's been a great journey so far, and I'm looking forward to continuing that."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Curious about your love of basketball in the '90s.  Do you recall your routine as a kid in the '90s getting ready to watch the All-Star Game on Sunday?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I'm not going to sit up here and say I remember my routine, but I believe the first All-Star Game that I actually sat down and watched was the -- was it '97 in Cleveland?  Because it actually came on local television, so we could watch it in Akron on local television.  '97.  Kobe was a rookie.  MJ was in that game.  It was pretty cool for me and my friends.  I think we were 11 years old at the time or 13.  Thirteen at the time. I got an opportunity to watch that game.  Wasn't fortunate enough to be able to watch some of the games before that because a lot of those games were nationally televised games, and I didn't have nationally televised channels.  No cable.  Just the local channels. I don't remember the routine, but I definitely just remember watching, like, the national anthem and just they're panning from left to right to all the All-Stars and me visualizing someday, through the grace of God and through hard work and dedication and my love for the game, maybe I could be one of those kids someday that could stand across that free throw line and be a part of a national anthem in an All-Star Game.  I thought it was pretty cool.  So, yeah."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Just wondering if you could talk about Josh Giddey's game and the season he is having so far.",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Josh Giddey is really, really good, man.  Obviously, a tall point guard.  He is a triple-double-type of playmaker every single night because of his ability to rebound at his size, his distinctive passing and he has the ability to score in the paint. I think he is going to continue to get better and better.  They have a really good young core over in OKC.  They don't even have Chet there just yet. Josh is a really good player, along with the other rookies that they have this year.  Obviously, we know first-time (All-Star) Shai is really good and the rest of that crew over there. Pretty good player, for sure.  You guys should be proud."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "ALL-STAR GAME: TEAM GIANNIS VS. TEAM LEBRON",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=183871",
    "date": "February 19, 2023",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, now that you've been through it, what do you think of the live draft process, and what was the moment that you enjoyed the most out of that?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I think the fan interaction that we got.  You know, I thought it was okay.  I liked the last format.  I liked the format on TV.  I think it was a little bit -- it looked fun, more fun, cooler, whatever the case may be. But, you know, it's always good to try some things and see how we can get better with things.  Especially with our game.  It's always great to have an opportunity to try new formats, new ways to spice up the game, spice up the viewership and things of that nature. All in all, though, it's been a great All-Star Weekend.  I think everybody who was a part of it should feel really good about it.  And salute to Salt Lake for hosting it."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What happened to your hand?  How is it?  Was the plan always to be some version of this --",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Coach Malone is a defense-minded coach.  I had him in my early days in Cleveland. I told him I would get one stop tonight for him.  I tried to get one little chase-down block, and got my finger caught in the rim.  But I'll be fine.  I'll be fine.  I don't think it's too much to worry about.  For precautionary reasons, I just had to take the rest of the night off."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, not every day you get to pick your own teammates.  Picked Kyrie second among your starters.  What was it like having him as a teammate tonight, and what's the relationship like between you guys?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   You know, it's the first time for us being teammates, so (smiling) -- no, it's always great to team back up with Kyrie.  You know how I feel about him both on the court and off the court.  It's always good to see him. I'm very proud of him.  Very proud much the man that he has become in his life right now.  So All-Star Weekend is always great to get an opportunity to be around the guys that you watch play, that you admire play, that you compete against, but that you just love the way they play the game of basketball.  So tonight was another instance."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, earlier today we asked you in a million ways, like, has it sunk in being the all-time leading scorer, but tonight you were introduced as that, and then you stood on that stage with Kareem and Karl Malone.  What was all that like?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   It's a surreal feeling.  You know, obviously, I didn't get an opportunity to watch Kareem live, but I know the history of the game.  I got an opportunity to watch a lot of his games, the replays or seeing footage of him. I did get an opportunity to watch a lot of Karl Malone games live.  To see the way they graced the court with their ability, you have the physicality of Malone's game, but he has some finesse as well with his mid-range jump shot, with his ability to run the floor and beat point guards and shooting guards down the floor.  Kareem's game, a unique game that no one has ever been able to try to patent or try to steal from. They were just so dominant in their eras.  They were so unique in their own game.  It's the reason that they are two of the all-time greatest basketball players that this world has ever seen. That moment for me is, like, I'm standing in between these guys, and I'm, like, it's such a surreal feeling.  Growing up -- I know you hear this story over and over, but it's just a part of my DNA.  Growing up in Akron, Ohio, and thinking about playing games to 21 or 33 with my brothers and my friends growing up, we always would try to emulate certain players. And to be mentioned with some of the greatest to ever play this game, along with Karl and along with Kareem, it's just an honor for sure."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, what were your thoughts on Mac McClung's performance last night in the Dunk Contest?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   He solidified himself as one of the -- probably one of the greatest slam dunk competitors that we've had in the history of the game."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "ALL-STAR GAME: TEAM DURANT VS. TEAM LEBRON",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=173184",
    "date": "February 20, 2022",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. What was it like hitting the game winner at the All-Star Game in Cleveland, and then also being celebrated as a member of the NBA 75th Team?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   To answer your first question, I couldn't have dreamt it.  I could not have dreamed of that moment any better than the actuality that just happened.  For me to be back here, like I keep stating, 35 minutes south of where I grew up here in Akron, Ohio, to hit the game-winner in the All-Star Game where me and my guys back in the back, we used to watch the All-Star Game.  I remember 25 years ago we were 12, 11, wishing that we had the opportunity or the means to come up to Cleveland and see some of the greatest basketball players of all time because they inspired us so much. For me to be here today, for my best friends to be here, for my wife and my kids and my family, my mom.  There are so many people that seen me grow from really a young toddler to who I am today.  I couldn't even -- I couldn't picture that moment any better. To answer your second question, to be a part of the 75 greatest basketball players to ever play, it just takes me back to my childhood once again growing up in Spring Hill and having all my inspirations taped on my wall, Allen Iverson and Jason Kidd, Gary Payton, Michael Jordan, Magic Johnson, Oscar Robertson.  To see those guys today and then be on stage with those guys it is -- you guys don't understand.  I'm trying to make you understand as much as I can, but it's just crazy."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Hey, LeBron, over the last 19 years whenever you've had a big moment in your career, you tweet \"a kid from Akron\" or you say \"a kid from Akron.\"  What does that phrase mean to you?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   You can look back there.  We're literally all kids from Akron.  We are a group of young men who always felt like we was looked over because of the popularity and notoriety that cities like Cleveland and Columbus and Dayton and Canton even gets mentioned because of the Pro Football Hall of Fame and Cincinnati gets mentioned.  We always felt like we were the fly-over city. I just remind myself and remind my following and the group of fans and the people that follow my journey that I'm a kid from Akron or one of the kids from Akron that has made it and trying to make it possible for the next kid from Akron.  Yeah, that's what it's about."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What was it like watching Steph, especially in the third quarter?  And then you're now 5-0 as a captain of picking All-Star teams.  What's your strategy when it comes to picking the team?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   First of all, well, I mean, Steph, come on, man.  This guy is from a different planet.  He literally has an automatic sniper connected to his arm, and when he lets it go, not only himself, but everybody on the floor, in the stands, on TV, on their phones, whatever you are watching on, you think it's going in every time.  Nine times out of 10 and sometimes 10 times out of 10 it does go in. To be out there and watch that kid from Akron as well shoot the ball the way he shot it, it was unbelievable.  It was pretty cool."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, looked like you sought out Michael after the ceremony.  You had a moment with him.  What was that like for you, and can you share anything about what you guys said?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Yeah, because there was so much chaos going on after we all kind of split.  I did not want to lose the opportunity to shake the man's hand that inspired me throughout my childhood.  I haven't had much dialogue with him in my 20 years or 19 years in this business, but part of me wouldn't be here without MJâ€™s inspiration.  I always wanted to be like him growing up. It's crazy that the game-winning shot tonight was a fadeaway, and it was inspired by MJ.  The way he wore his shoes, the way he wore his uniform, I mean, all the way down to some of the cars that he drove, how much he inspired me.  I didn't want to waste that opportunity because we're just not in -- we're not in the same building a lot and haven't been in the same building a lot throughout my career.  It meant something to me."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Just with everything that you have done with your old teammates for the whole week, you said this was beyond your dream, but is this something you'll remember for the rest of your life?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I hope through great health, I hope so.  Obviously, health is the most important, but I hope I'll never forget this moment.  It would be cool if 25 years from now when they do the top 100 that it's back here. Yeah, I'll probably never forget this moment.  It's something that I'm glad my kids got to witness.  Then when my grandkids show up at some point, I'll be able to show them some footage of what their granddad was able to accomplish when he played the game of basketball."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've played here since you left, but the reaction tonight when you were introduced and you kind of threw up your arms and kind of let out that roar, how did that feel to you to sort of hear the way that you were embraced here?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   When they said \"from Akron, Ohio, the kid from Akron, Ohio,\" that was pretty cool.  And then just hearing the ovation that I got from these fans here, they seen 11 years of my NBA career, and they saw pretty much, I mean, four years of my high school career, and some of them even followed me all the way back to when I started playing basketball at Summer Lake at the A.R.B., that's Akron Recreational Bureau, if you don't know.  I'll tell you that anyways. I mean, these guys have followed my journey.  For me to be back here, like I said, today, and for them to give me that warm welcome, didn't only mean something to me, but it meant something to my family and friends that are here, and my kids from my school are all over this place.  It's just super dope.  Super, super, super dope, and I was very humbled and appreciative of that."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You're right, we don't understand what that's like.  If it's possible for you to try to explain what it was like to be in the middle of that grouping with every -- well, not every player, but so many players of significance over the last 50, 60 years?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Even with the guys, David, that was not here, you still felt their presence.  You felt their presence on that stage.  I don't know.  It would be like going to your favorite musician's concert in the greatest stadium, and you are literally on stage with them while they're performing, and the sense of \"I can't believe that I'm here.\"  That's the best way that I can put it.  I can't believe I'm sitting next to Bruce Springsteen while he is playing in a stadium in London with 160,000 people, or I'm in the Garden with Jay-Z or whoever that person is.  I'm sitting here with Whitney Houston onstage in a coliseum with 90,000 people and you're on stage.  That's kind of what it felt like for me.  I just couldn't believe it. Every time they would announce another name, I didn't even get an opportunity to, like, rejoice in the player that they had named.  It was, like, Gary Payton.  I was, like, wow.  Then J Kidd showed up, and then A.I. showed up, and then it was D. Wade, C.P., and Steph.  I was just tripped out.  I was tripped out."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. We've talked a lot this year about how tough and draining this season has been for you.  Can you describe sort of the joy that you felt tonight and how much did you need that?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   You can tell this is the most you're going to get out of me for a long time because once I get back to the season, I'm getting back to my shelter mode.  But, listen, man, the joy of just being home, we stayed back home in Akron all weekend while I was here, seeing my guys.  Even though I see them when I come back home in the summer, we always link up.  There's just something special.  We've never spent an All-Star Weekend all of us together.  Every last one of them was here, Sian, Willy, Dru, Frankie, Brandon, we were all here together for the first time.  Then having my mom in the building and having my wife and my kids here, it's just -- how much more can a man ask for really when you have an opportunity to live this moment with everybody that has seen you come up? Let me not forget Maverick, Rich and Randy as well.  We all spent All-Star Weekend together for the first time in my career, and I don't know if that will ever happen again.  So, there's no reason for me not to have joy."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. So many great players were here this weekend, 75th Anniversary, but only a few guys have had to carry the league.  You're one of them.  What does that responsibility mean to you, and do you see anybody coming down the pipeline here that are willing to do all of the things that you have done as an ambassador?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   It's a responsibility, for sure.  Somebody did it before me and put it in a position where it was my responsibility to make sure I kept it where it was and also make it even more grand and make it better than what it was and represent this league with the utmost respect.  I'm seeing my brother Carmelo walk down the hall right there. But just not only play the game the right way, but also mean something off the floor as well because there are so many generations that look for inspiration.  It's always pretty cool to see the guys that come into our league and they say their favorite player growing up was LeBron James.  That means something to me because I feel like I have so much more to do than just playing the game of basketball.  I hope it was also how I inspired them off the floor, how to break the narrative of keeping your friends around and them being able to work a room without my presence, being able to give back to your community in a way if you feel passionate about it. I've held that title of the ambassador of the league for -- nobody ever told me to do it, but I felt like if I wasn't going to do it, who was going to do it?  I took that with a lot of responsibility, and I'll continue to do it until I'm done playing the game. It will fall in the hands of the next one, whoever that may be.  We'll see.  Appreciate it, guys."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR MEDIA DAY",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=173143",
    "date": "February 19, 2022",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. (No microphone.)",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I'm sorry.  Oh, my guys?  Absolutely.  Absolutely.  Well, I mean, I speak to them almost every day.  We have that connection and that friendship that's been going on since we were 9 years old.  So, like I said, they're here.  Willie, Sian, Dru, Romeo, Frankie, Brandon, all of us are all here this weekend, and this is the first time we've all spent the All-Star Weekend together.  So it makes it even more special."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Do you take different approaches to these All-Star Games?  How are you going to go about it?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I have no idea.  I think I've taken different approaches, just depending how my body was feeling or how the season was going at that point in time.  If I needed more rest, then I'm not trying to burn out during the All-Star Game, but at the same time I'm going to give the fans a little bit of something because this is what it's all about.  Just being smart about it, obviously. I've been a part of quite a few of these games, so definitely want to be smart about my minutes and things that I play.  It's the only time and only game throughout the season where I'm okay talking about my minutes. (Laughter)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. When you're around your peers, how often do they talk to you about your recovery regimen?  Does that come up a lot?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   No, it hasn't.  We're all like moving so fast throughout All-Star Weekend.  We've been pulled and tagged on, and you got to go here, you got to go there, you got to do this, you got to do that, that we don't always get an opportunity to kind of just like have many conversations.  I've had a few over my career with a few guys.  I won't name names, but, no, that's only come up a few times in my career.  Yeah."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Are you surprised considering you're redefining longevity?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I don't want to say I'm surprised, but guys -- everyone has their own method of how they feel they could create longevity in the sport and make sure their body stays in the top-tier shape.  They're All-Stars for a reason.  So they're doing something right.  I feel like guys have their own regimen and things of that nature, but I have never been a closed door when it comes to anything I've done in my career."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Obviously, you're 37, 19th season, talk about that and how much you spend on your body.  This year what's gone into the mental and physical challenges?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Every season has its own mental and physical challenges.  This is no different.  This is the strangest season I've been a part of so far.  I don't want to just talk about the injuries but COVID protocols.  You have guys go out for false positives.  You have had guys go out for real reasons.  We've had our head coach be out for several games.  We've had injuries.  We've had a little bit of everything.  I mean, I've been out at points in time in the season.  It's just been very challenging, very physically and emotionally draining at times, but that's the NBA season for you.  If you are not having your mindset on that happening, then you're setting yourself up for failure.  I've always kind of known that's going to happen at some point throughout the season."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. As the leader of the team, what do you feel you need to adjust for this team to get better and try to finish and win a championship?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I love the way we've played the last few games.  At the trade deadline, the energy shifted in our locker room and I love the way we've played the last couple of games.  One resulted in a win.  One resulted in a loss in the Bay.  But I hope we can continue that same energy, that same connectivity, and as a leader of the team, obviously, it starts and ends with me, and we go from there."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Can you talk to us about the scoring.  You've been able to pick it up?  What about this particular run you are on, how do you explain it?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I don't.  I can't.  I don't know.  Just in a groove, I guess.  I work on my game.  I work on my craft.  You guys have seen me when you come to practice, and I'm working on my game or before the games or off days.  I'm trying to see ways that I can continue to stay in great rhythm and see ways I can continue to get better, even at my age.  I'm never satisfied.  I can't explain the groove that I'm in right now offensively.  I guess just playing some good basketball. Just trying to be efficient.  Besides the Golden State game the other night, we've been extremely efficient, and that's the most important for me.  I'm not just out there jacking up a bunch of shots to be doing it.  I want to be efficient when I'm doing it as well."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. (Question about Luka Doncic.)",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Because I love everything about his game.  I love everything about him.  The way he plays the game reminds me of the way I play the game.  We're just triple threats.  We rebound.  We pass, which is the number one thing on our mind, trying to keep our teammates engaged and keeping our teammates feeling good on the floor, keeping our teammates in rhythm.  And we will put 40 on you too if you disrespect us."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Just wondering, you, obviously have a huge emphasis on the youth coming through.  There's a 19-year-old Australian named Josh Giddey.  What do you make of him so far?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   He is really, really, really good.  He has a great pace about the game.  Great vision.  I've always loved pass-first guards who can see plays happen before they happen.  Josh is one of those kids who can definitely see the game a lot quicker than a lot of guys out on the floor, and he has shown it.  I think he has three straight triple-doubles and playing beautiful basketball. The MVP over there is Sam Presti.  He the MVP.  Josh Giddey is great.  Sam Presti, I don't understand, his eye for talent.  He drafted KD, Russ, Jeff Green, Serge Ibaka, Reggie Jackson, Josh Giddey and the list goes on and on and on.  This guy is pretty damn good."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You have experienced a lot of different All-Star venues.  How is Cleveland doing this year?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I just talked about 25 years ago when I was a kid.  I was 12 years old.  I was stating that earlier and how I wished I had the means and the ability to come up to Cleveland and just feel that energy and hopefully bump into one of those guys.  I had so many dreams of being an All-Star when I was a kid, growing up in Akron and having a team that was 35 minutes north of us, even though as much as I love MJ, love the Bulls, you know, just having that inspiration, having pro teams right up 77 North, you know, and having the Browns and the Indians at the time, now the Guardians and having the Cavaliers.  I remember when they were playing not even -- a lot closer, Richfield.  I remember that. To sit here 25 years later doing what I love to do, dreaming about what I love to do, believing in what I wanted to be, it's just unbelievable. I mean, Cleveland is very deserving of this platform and this moment.  They got two All-Stars of their own in the game in D.G. (Darius Garland) and the big fella, Jarrett Allen.  And they got another guy in the All-Star, and that's me.  It's great, man.  I'm Pushin' P, capital P, you know?  That's what I'm doing."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL STAR",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=162944",
    "date": "March 7, 2021",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, was being out there and kind of watching Steph and Giannis and stuff like that, how much fun was that?  Did it get fun for you at any point?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Absolutely.  That's why I drafted them, man.  It's guys that I obviously compete against on a nightly basis.  But guys that I'm just in awe of.  Giannis and Steph, it's my first time teaming up with Steph, and it was an honor to be on the floor with him.  A guy that I've seen come and be the player that he is today.  It was just great to be out there with Steph and Giannis and the rest of the guys, too."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Obviously this process was kind of -- it is what it was, I suppose, probably without a better way of putting it, but now that you're through it, $3 million for HBCUs, what did you make of the day?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Well, any time you're able to benefit a situation like HBCUs or give back to the communities that don't get the support that we wish that we would get more of, I think it's all beneficial.  All in all, obviously the league did a hell of a job of being able to put this together still.  The PA did a great job of backing that, and then us as players we came in and did our job.  We'll get ready for the second half of the season."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What do you do now the rest of this week?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Head back to L.A. and spend a couple days with my family and then start preparing.  I'm going to keep my body fresh, work out, train and just get ready for the second half."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Do you think these couple days can be a recharger for you?  Is it enough time?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I hope so.  Is it enough time?  I'll take any time, obviously.  So I'll take full advantage of the time that we have.  Is it enough time?  No, it's never enough time, but we're not on the side of time.  I'm not on the side of time.  I'll take full advantage of what I have and be okay with it."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You guys have been pretty open about having to use games as practices.  Practice in the 2021 season probably isn't a real thing.  What can you actually really expect to get out of a practice now?  What's practice in 2021 like?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   It's very challenging.  First of all, in order to get into the building you have to take a test.  You have to wait 35, 40 minutes, sometimes an hour for the results to come back.  Some guys' results come back faster than others.  There can be a possible time where it could be an invalid test.  You have to test again, so you may miss a workout that you have scheduled.  You may miss prepping yourself to get ready for a practice, and then once you get into the building, it's just very challenging.  You're playing every other day.  You don't know when you're going to have practice time.  You don't know as far as what the restrictions and with COVID and things of that nature if you're going to have all your guys. So it's very challenging for all teams, not just us.  It's something I've never experienced before in my career, and it doesn't allow you to -- practice makes perfect, and it's true, but we have not had a lot of time to do that."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You're 4-0 in these games now when you've gotten to pick your team.  Are you going to be a GM when you retire?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I hope that they allow me to retire from being an All-Star captain, so I can retire with a perfect 4-0 record.  I'll keep that forever.  But we'll just see what happens. I always try to pick the right team, and I've been lucky enough for four years to pick the right team.  Guys go out and compete and play to win.  I've been on the winning side of all four."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I was wondering if there's been any debate or discussions ahead of the game to use this platform to again raise awareness for racial inequalities and stuff or is that a past thing kind of?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   No, I don't want to say it's a past thing, but we didn't have any discussions about it.  I think the one thing that our players do a hell of a job of always talking about social justice and talking about voter suppression and talking about systemic racism and things that go on in our communities and things that go on in America.  We have this platform, and we always use that to the best of our ability on shedding light on those situations."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. With four titles, Finals MVP and other trophies, what's next for LeBron James?  What is the next big goal?  Maybe to play with Bronny in the NBA?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   That's definitely one of my goals, but that's a long-term goal.  My son right now is in high school and enjoying what being a teenager is all about.  But that would be pretty cool to go on my resume if I'm able to be on the same court as my son some day in this league.  The league has given me so much, and I just try to give back to it.  So if I'm able to give back the way I play the game, the way I inspire the game, what I brought to the game and also be able to give back by giving my son or lending my son to the NBA, that would be a treat for me and it would be an honor for myself. I've got a lot of things that I'm still passionate about and motivated about still doing in my career, and still trying to win championships.  That is the goal right now, and that is the motivation right now."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: LAKERS VS. HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=160601",
    "date": "October 11, 2020",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. Three seasons ago after you beat Toronto, you told Cleveland.com that you didn't have anything left to prove when you were asked what you have left to prove. I wanted to know if that's changed over the past three years.  Did you feel you had something to prove, and why is this one so important for you?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think personally thinking I have something to prove fuels me.  It fueled me over this last year and a half since the injury.  It fueled me because no matter what I've done in my career to this point, there's still little rumblings of doubt or comparing me to the history of the game and has he done this, has he done that. So having that in my head, having that in my mind, saying to myself, why not still have something to prove, I think it fuels me."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. All the circumstances surrounding this one, being in Orlando, having a four-and-a-half-month hiatus away from family, everything going on in the country, how does that add context to this fourth ring versus the other three?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think they are all special in their own right.  They all have their obstacles, things that went on throughout the course of the year, both on and off the floor. But one is not less than the other, because when you're able to put yourself in this position to be able to win a championship, first thing you start to think about is how much work you've put in over the course of the year.  How much you've sacrificed, how much you've dedicated to the game and to your craft.  That's always been the most fulfilling thing for me, besides seeing my teammates as happy as they are.  Being able to know that you can put the work in, literally trust the process, live about the process and then see the results.  I think not only from a basketball player, but from everybody, whatever craft, whatever workspace you're in, to be able to put the work in and live along the process and build along the process and be able to see results, I think we all live for that moment."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Could you sense with the mental wear of the bubble that it was getting to other teams?  And in the last few days, was there kind of a weird feeling of you're reaching not just possibly winning a championship but reaching the end of this journey?  Did that feel different than the other title runs?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   To answer your first question, with so much going on inside the bubble and everything and us going into the unknown, it was kind of hard for me personally -- once I got inside here, I said, okay, this is my mission: I want to win a championship; this is why I'm here.  It was hard for me to focus on other teams and what other players were feeling.  I didn't engage in that.  I didn't look for it.  I wanted to keep my energy in the right space. And over the last couple days, you definitely thought about it.  You thought about just being here, how successful it is.  I commend Adam Silver and the NBA, Michele Roberts, Chris Paul and everybody at the NBPA to make this happen and to make this work.  I think we can all say from the social injustice conversations, the voter suppression, police brutality, to have this platform, have our players be able to unite like that, it's something that you will miss.  You will think back on it. I think one of the biggest things, besides the social injustice, all the things I mentioned, we had zero positive tests.  We had zero positives tests for as long as we were here, 90-some days, 95 days maybe for myself.  I had a little calendar I was checking off.  But on a serious note, no positive tests.  That's a success for everybody that was involved."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What about this partnership that you have with Anthony makes it particularly special to you?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I can't really explain it.  There's just certain things you just know.  And any type of relationship, you kind of just feel, you know that vibe.  You have that respect.  You have that drive.  Sometimes you can't explain what links you with somebody, and then it's that organic. Sometimes, you don't even try to explain it.  You guys ask me about my relationship with AD, the first thing I think about is the respect, the no ego, the challenging each other.  We want each other to be better than actually ourselves.  I want AD to be better than me.  AD want me to be better than him.  Every single night, every single day.  And we challenge ourselves.  I think that's a part of it."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. With about three minutes left, you looked over and you saw Anthony sitting there, probably the realization of what you guys accomplished hitting him for the first time.  I'm wondering, how much of that reminded you of 2012 for you?  And what did that first title do for your career and what can this do for AD moving forward?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   It definitely reminded me of it, just the excitement, the \"I can't believe this.\"   I definitely saw myself, 27 LeBron, 27 AD.  I definitely saw myself in that. And what it did for me in my career, it basically let me know that the work I put in on my craft, and the way I play the game, how I was taught to play the game when I picked up a basketball when I was eight years old, it's okay to play that way and be able to win.  No matter how many people tell you, you should maybe shoot more, you should maybe do this more, you should maybe be like him more, it let me know that the way I play basketball and the way I was taught to play basketball is the right way to play it, because you do see results. And then it just continues to boost your confidence.  Not saying that AD doesn't already have confidence, but it takes it to another level."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You talk about how you can't focus on other teams and their bubble experience, but for you outside looking in, it seemed like you were locked in from the beginning of the entire journey to now. I imagine you had your days off the court when it comes to the personal sacrifice, when it comes to keeping this group together.  Is that the case?  Were there ups and downs?  How different is just is this championship feeling?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   To answer your first question, absolutely.  I think you wouldn't be human if you didn't have ups and downs in the bubble.  At times I was questioning myself, should I be here?  Is this worth sacrificing my family?  So many things.  I've never been without my family this long.  Missing the days of my daughter being in kindergarten, even though it's through Zoom.  Missing my son's 16th birthday, which we all know is a big birthday if you have kids. Seeing my middle child continue to grow and be who he is.  First of all, big-time shoutout to the late great Steve Jobs, because without him, without his vision, those FaceTime calls wouldn't be possible. Absolutely, I've had ups and downs throughout this journey.  For some odd reason, I was able to keep the main thing the main thing.  When I talked about all the stuff that I missed, they understood that, too, and that made it a lot easier for me. To answer your second question, it doesn't matter where it is if you win a championship.  A bubble, Miami, Golden State -- it doesn't matter.  When you get to this point, it's one of the greatest feelings in the world for a basketball player to be able to win at the highest level."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Does any one of your championships stand out in terms of the difficulty?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Well, I can't sit here and say one is more challenging than the other or one is more difficult than the other.  I can just say that I've never won with this atmosphere.  None of us have.  We've never been a part of this.  If you've been here throughout the start -- I mean, we got here July 9th.  Our ballclub got here July 9th.  It's October what -- I don't even , October 11th now. So this was very challenging and difficult.  It played with your mind.  It played with your body.  You're away from some of the things that you're so accustomed to to make you be the professional that you are.  So this is right up there. I heard some rumblings from people that are not in the bubble, oh, you don't have to travel, whatever. People just doubting what goes on in here.  This is right up there with one of the greatest accomplishments I've had."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. When you signed with the Lakers, over the course of the first year, Magic stepping down and everything that went into your start here, was there ever a moment where your mind wandered or you thought maybe the hill would be too high or hard to climb to get back to this point in L.A., or if not, how did you know or what gave you faith that you guys would get here?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   What gave me faith is that Rob Pelinka told me he would do whatever it takes to make sure that we would become a winning franchise once again.  Obviously, championships are not promised, and I don't expect that.  But he said he would do whatever it takes to make this franchise, whatever personnel changes he needs to make, any part of our organization, he would do it, because he wanted to win just as much. And for me, being able to get Jeanie back to this point, that's something that fueled me as well.  This is a historic franchise and to be a part of this is something that I'll be able to talk about and my grandkids and kids will be able to talk about; their pawpaw played for the Los Angeles Lakers.  It's like playing for the Yankees and winning or playing for the Cowboys and winning a Super Bowl, or the Patriots.  It's like playing for the Red Sox. So to be able to win with a historical franchise is something that, no matter if your mind wavers away, you can always remember what you're doing it for."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You and Jeanie shared a long hug right after as the trophy presentation was being prepared.  Did you say anything to her?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I don't want to lie to you.  I did, but if Jeanie at some point would ever want to reveal what I said to her, that's up to her.  It was just a special moment and I know how special it was for her.  So it was just in the words of, \"I'm proud to be a Laker.\""
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: LAKERS VS. HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=160301",
    "date": "October 9, 2020",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. What's your Finals experience over the years taught you about how to respond to a game like this and how to put that out to the rest of your teammates?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I mean for me, I've always stayed even keeled.  You know, throughout the highs, throughout the lows, you stay even keeled and get better with the process.  You stay in the moment, which I am, and understanding that we can be better. And how we make the adjustments and how we learn from tonight, tomorrow in our film session and when we get together and prepare ourselves for Sunday, will show the difference."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I was wondering if you could take us through that last minute of the game, the ups and downs, and your mentality when you were driving in. Frank described it as you were ready to take on the whole team and then you saw Danny open at the top?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Obviously it was back and forth, big play after big play.  A couple, you know, questionable calls that swayed their way and put Jimmy to the free-throw line.  Obviously, we can't do that.  He's been damn near perfect at the free-throw line in the series. We just needed to get one stop.  We felt like if we could get one stop, we could do something on the offensive end.  But we got a hell of a look.  We got a hell of a look to win the game, to win the series.  Didn't go down.  And then we got the offensive rebound, we turned the ball over.  I thought we had a lot more time than I think we even thought after the offensive rebound, and a pass wasn't executed as we would like. But we've got to be better.  We've just got to be better in Game 6 and close the series."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've obviously been on the other side of this coming back from a 3-1 deficit.  Is there something about that experience that helps you understand what it will take to slam the door on Miami now that it's been somewhat left ajar for them?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Listen, at the end of the day, you don't predetermine anything and you take the game as it's going and you play. You play each quarter, you play each possession and you live with the results.  You don't think about what could happen at the end of the game and things of that nature.  You don't get caught up in the aftermath.  You have to live in the moment and prepare yourself each and every possession, because if you start to wander and your mind starts to go, you make a mistake.  One thing about this team that we are playing, they make you pay for every mistake.  It's the same as when I was playing against Golden State all those years, you make a mistake, they make you pay.  So we have to understand that."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Two vets, Danny and Markieff were involved in that play.  Is that a situation where you talk to them after a game like this or do you feel they have experience and they kind of know what it is and they will come ready for Game 6?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I mean, theyâ€™re vets.  Theyâ€™re vets.  I don't think too much need to be said to them.  I believe they will be much better and I'm not saying they even played bad tonight.  Everybody in the lineup tonight that got minutes gave the effort.  We just had some mental breakdowns at times, and they make you pay for it, like I said.  We've got to look at the film tomorrow and see how we can be better."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. From I think 2:52 remaining to 0:46 remaining, you and Jimmy went back and forth; there was six straight possessions where one of you scored for your team.  And even with the questionable calls, you talked about Jimmy and his competitive nature, something that you relish.  Can you take us inside what it's like being in that battle with the game on the line?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   That's the beauty of the game, being able to compete at the highest level.  You take those opportunities and you live in the moment.  You're trying to make plays for your team and be successful on both ends, and we were both just trying to do that and trying to will our team to a victory.  You know, he was able to make one more play than I was able to make tonight and come away with a victory."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Talking about calls, not trying to get you in trouble, but just from your vantage point on the last foul that got Jimmy to the line, AD looked like he went straight up.  What did you see from your vantage point?  I know you didn't have a challenge but what was it like from your view.",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I thought AD made a heck of a play at the rim.  I felt he was chest to chest with Jimmy, making him change the trajectory of his shot and the call didn't go our way. I felt like, you know, at that point in time, I think it was a tough call, but they made the call.  We still had an opportunity to win. But we feel like, you know, with AD and with him at the rim and him contesting things like that, it could have swayed our way, but it didn't."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You talk about focus being so crucial down the stretch, AD seemed to hurt that left foot a little bit.  For you, is it tough in that moment when you're trying to figure out, you know, what can I do with him, what can't I do with him, as he's trying to fight through that?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Well, if he's on the floor â€“ I mean he's a warrior, man.  Just him being out there, hobbled, just brings a lot more confidence to myself and our team.  We know the nicks and bumps and bruises he's played through throughout the whole season.  We have to pick it up for him and pick it up for any one of our brothers if they are hobbling or lobbying or not at their full strength.  Just the makeup of our brotherhood."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've been in so many of these all over the years, going all the way back to throwing the ball in the corner to Donyell, Ray makes a three, Kyrie makes a three.  Tonight Danny got a great look but didn't make it.  How do you live with make or miss at this stage of a season to determine winning and losing when you've put so much into it?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I've always played the game the same way since I was a kid and I've had success doing it. And I won't let a play here or a play there change my outlook on the game and how I play the game.  I mean, if you just look at the play, I was able to draw two defenders below the free-throw line and find one of our shooters at the top of the key for a wide open three to win a championship.  I trusted him, we trusted him, and it just didn't go.  You live with that.  You live with that. It's one of the best shots that we could have got, I feel, in that fourth quarter, especially down the stretch with two guys on me, Duncan Robinson and Jimmy, and Danny had a hell of a look.  It just didn't go down.  I know he wish he can have it again.  I wish I could make a better pass.  You know, but you just live with it."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: LAKERS VS. HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=160224",
    "date": "October 8, 2020",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. We've asked you this basically every round, but close-out games you've won 16 of the last 17.  You said your mindset is about finding a way to be as desperate as the other team.  It seems like that would be so much easier said than done.  How do you find a way to do that?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Just who I am.  Just the way I prepare my mind, prepare my body, prepare for the moment.  Just having that desperation coming to a close-out game.  I've been victorious after having that mindset.  But that's just who I've become and how I've challenged and channeled my mindset.  Living in the moment and not taking it for granted and just channeling that desperation, just knowing that the opponent and the man that's across from you has that same feeling.  That's what it is."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. The Executive of the Year Award just came out and I think Rob [Pelinka] finished fifth or sixth.  We know how you guys feel about Defensive Player of the Year.  We heard what you said about MVP.  Typically, individual accolades come with great team success and you guys had it.  Do you have any idea as to why maybe it hasn't happened on this team, those individual accolades?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   You'd have to ask whoever voted."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Looking at what you did this year, being I think the oldest to be a first-time assist champ and being back on this stage with a third different team -- you don't need the list.  The fan vote for MVP, I think you won pretty easily.  What has this year done for legacy? Or do you think that no matter what you do from today forward, the legacy is already kind of written?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I don't really think about it too much.  I think the story will be told how it's supposed to be told and be written how it's supposed to be written.  But I don't live my life thinking about legacy.  What I do off the floor is what means more to me than what I do on the floor. Seeing my kids on the back of a Wheaties box yesterday was one of the best moments of my life.  Seeing my mom unveil the box back in my hometown of Akron, Ohio, yesterday was some of the best news, videos and pictures that I've ever seen, that I could ever get. The game of basketball will pass me by.  There will be a new group of young kids and vets and rookies throughout the course of this game.  So I can't worry about that as far as on the floor.  How I move, how I walk, what I preach, what I talk about, how I inspire the next generation is what matters to me the most.  And if you appreciate my game, then cool.  If you didn't, then that's cool, too. That's what it boils down to."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You guys are going to wear the Black Mamba uniforms tomorrow.  I want to know if you recall the first time seeing them either when the Lakers wore them a couple seasons ago or when you first got your hands on it.  And you are a guy who has aesthetic opinions.  What did you think about that look?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I thought they were cool from what I saw when they wore them a few years ago.  Obviously, until you get your hands on them, you don't get to see the detail in them.  It's super-duper detailed.  It has that snake Mamba print on it.  It means something. Something more than just a uniform.  It represents an individual who gave the franchise 20 years of his blood, sweat and tears and his dedication to his craft, both on and off the floor, to make that franchise be proud of him, and hopefully vice versa. I think last year we got a Shaq jersey.  Magic did one, as well.  I think it's just pretty cool when you know you're wearing a uniform that a legend had his hands on."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. The fact that you're potentially one win away from going home and being reunited with a lot of people that you want to see and care about, does it make it harder to kind of prepare the same way for this game than any of the others?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Absolutely not.  Absolutely not.  I have a support system at home that's taking care of that and that allows me to focus on my job.  So when I get home, I get home.  But I've got a job to do."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've talked about AD so much during this run, but I'm curious about the relationship pre-2018.  I think it was December of 2018, you mentioned to Dave about how it would be amazing to play with him.  You've talked about 2012 in the Olympics.  What was the evolution of the two of you between that time, and when did you decide, in terms of possible partners to do this thing, that this was the guy that you wanted to be with?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   First of all, you just look at his one year at Kentucky and what he was able to produce for that program in one year. His ability to outrun guards, ball-handling with the smalls, block shots, catch lobs.  I remember one game, I think they were playing North Carolina and he had the game-winning block.  He had the game-winning block, I believe it was versus John Henson if I'm not mistaken, if my basketball mind is correct. That block was incredible, and they won that game. Then you just look at his run throughout that whole March Madness.  He was just beyond the best player in college basketball. We get to [the Olympics in] 2012 when he's a young Anthony Davis, and he soaked up everything.  He was not a rookie that came in and thought he knew it all or felt like he was who he was, the National Player of the Year and national champion and so on and so on.  He came in with a sponge mentality right off the bat, just soaking up everything from myself, Kobe, D-Wade, Melo, so on and so on and so on.  You knew right then how great of a kid, how great of a player he was going to be just from that. I mean, in '18, I guess it was known; don't need to be said.  You look at a guy who can do everything out on the floor versus anybody, and you have visions of what that could look like if you were to team up. Yeah, I was speaking just true from the heart and from a basketball mindset. Dave paid for it, I paid for it, for that moment.  But I didn't care, because I just know how special he is."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've been a Laker now for two and a half calendar years.  I'm wondering what you've learned in that time about what it means to be part of this franchise.  And then the second is, could you share a little bit of how your relationship with Jeanie has evolved over the last couple years?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Well, one, what I've learned being a Laker is that the Laker faithful don't give a damn what you've done before. Until you become a Laker, you've got to do it with them, as well.  They don't care about your resume at all until you become a Laker.  Then you've got to do it as a Laker, and then they respect you.  I've learned that. My relationship with Jeanie I will say is incredible.  I think she's an unbelievable owner.  I think she's a powerful woman.  I think what she believes in is an extension of her father, and continuing to build this legacy of this great franchise.  I'm just happy to be a part of it.  I'm happy to have the relationship that I have with her and with Linda Rambis, as well.  It's very unique.  I'm just honored to be a part of it.  I love the history of the game and I've read so much about Dr. Buss and his teams and his success.  To be playing while his daughter is the owner of the team I think is pretty cool.  It just adds to the legacy of this franchise."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I wanted to go back to the uniforms just real quick.  Did the decision to wear those tomorrow for Game 5, was that something that came from the locker room?  Did the players have a say in that?  Were you consulted on whether it was the right time to wear those again?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   No, I have no idea where it came from.  I saw on the schedule it was prepared for Game 7, so I don't know where it came from.  I'll wear any uniform, to be honest.  Just put me on the court."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. As you remember when this thing started in the bubble, you were talking about how difficult it can be and was to play without fans.  You spoke at length about that.  And then separately you were just saying how rough it was to live in the bubble day to day.  I'm wondering for both things, when and sort of how you got over it or got through it.  How you were able to get over playing without that usual adrenaline rush of the crowd, and when you were able to get your own mind around life in the bubble.",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I don't know.  I don't know the exact date.  I think it's with anything in life.  Something that's different, something that's challenging, something that's uncomfortable.  I guess it would be like when I went from the eighth grade to the ninth grade, from middle school to high school.  It was uncomfortable, but I got used to it.  Or when you guys went to college, for the people that went to college, it was probably uncomfortable leaving home for the first time.  Not having your mom and dad's cooking or whatever the case may be, and now you're in a dorm room trying to figure this out.  But you figure it out. It's human.  It's just human growth.  It's a human mindset.  It's a growth mindset.  You just figure it out.  I kept the main thing the main thing, and everything else took care of itself.  You control what you can control.  What you cannot control, you don't worry about."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Can you talk about just the social justice movement that's taking place, how guys have used their platform here, and as it comes to an end, where do you guys go from here?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   We know that being here has given us the strength and the numbers.  You could take that from the Golden State Warriors: There's strength in numbers.  That's a byproduct of us being here, of being able to use this platform to be able to talk about everything that's going on outside of the court.  All the social injustice and the voter suppression and so many other things that are just going on, the police brutality and so on and so on and so on.  Being here and having the opportunity to talk about these issues and continuing to understand that this world is not just about basketball, even though we live in a small piece of the game of basketball.  There are so many bigger things and so many greater things going on.  If you can make an impact or you can make a change or you can have a vision, it just helps out so much not only in your community but all over the world. Where do we go from here?  We don't stop.  Obviously, when the season ends in less than a week, everyone disperses and goes back. But I hope people continue to use their platform.  Use their individual social media platforms, if they're doing it that way, or if you are an individual that goes into your community and does it that way.  However you can continue to create change for the better of all of us, it only makes us all better.  It doesn't matter what race you are, it doesn't matter what color you are, no matter how tall or whatever the case may be, because we all want to see better days.  No matter if you agree or don't agree with some of the things that are going on, I think we'd all love to see better days and see more love than hate. I know I do my part, as much as I do, on continuing to create change, continuing to educate, continuing to enlighten my community and communities all over the world that listen to me and follow me throughout my journey.  Like I said, you control what you can control, and what you can't, sometimes as much as it hurts, you just try not to worry about it."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: LAKERS VS. HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=160174",
    "date": "October 6, 2020",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. Just wanted to ask you about KCP down the stretch.  You grabbed a rebound off Jimmy's miss, pushed in transition, see him in the corner.  All the teammates you've had, you know which guys are going to be capable for those moments in a Finals game.  What do you think of his effort overall?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   At the end of the day, if you're on the floor at crunch time, then I believe in you.  Whoever is out on the floor with me, I believe can make plays, and tonight was a case in point of KCP.  Stays ready.  He works on his craft.  Like you said, that three in front of their bench was a huge three, and obviously the drive at the end of the shot clock was two big back-to-back plays in the fourth quarter, where we needed to continue to score versus this team."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I think it was after Game 2 that you made the comment that it's not just enough to win the game, you guys want to be great.  This game was one where defensively you were great, and then there was a lot of sloppiness early offensively with the turnovers.  I'm just wondering if there's a certain point where you stop striving for that winning in a great way, and it's just enough to get the wins?  Or is that not until the fourth win?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   It's kind of two different things, two different points you're making.  You never stop striving to be perfect or be great.  And you know that a perfect game is not going to happen, but that don't mean you still don't strive to be as great as you can be every night. Now, every game has its own adjustments and things of that nature, and tonight was one of those games where we had to win on the defensive end and make some timely shots.  But I think when you start thinking like, okay, well, I can't be great tonight or we can't be great tonight, okay, we just have to figure it out, then you sell yourself short.  Me personally, I would never do that as long as I lace them up and put on a uniform.  But I love what we did tonight."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You guys took a five-point lead to the fourth quarter and won the game, which made you as a team 56-0 this season taking a lead into the fourth.  What does that say about the makeup of your team, and do you take any pride in being on a team that can possess that stat?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think the fourth quarter, obviously it's winning time.  You've got 12 minutes to buckle down defensively with the lead, kind of hold that lead, and then you have to execute offensively.  Obviously, I didn't know the stat coming into tonight.  But for us, that's just the mindset.  We've got 12 minutes.  If we have the lead, it's our job to outscore the opponent or to hold them to [as many] points as us, which is the same exact thing, because if we win the quarter, we win the game. That's kind of been our mindset all year long."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I know you talked about AD's great games and that that's who AD is, but in the last two days, from where he sort of told us after Game 3 he felt like he could have been more aggressive, to the guy he was after hitting that shot, 39 seconds left, beating his chest, what did you see in him getting back to that place where he be the player that he can be?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   He's a big shot-maker late in the shot clock, early in the shot clock, fourth quarter, first quarter, everything in between.  It was just a great set up by Do [Rajon Rondo].  The possession before that, Do was able to fake it like he was going back to him, carry himself into the lane and get a layup.  And then the very next possession, he was able to find him and AD just kind of stared at the shot clock, knew it was late in the shot clock and obviously trusted his shot that he works on consistently. So big-time shot, big-time play for our team to be able to put the game away."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. This game, being tied back and forth the entire time, came down to moments of truth.  You guys won more than they did at the end of the day.  When AD hits that shot, and you're doing the Ric Flair and screaming, is there a different kind of satisfaction, when y'all are so tight all night long and you have a breakthrough at that point?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   You kind of know momentum plays and momentum shots, the score and the time, what's going on within the last few possessions.  They were going back and forth with us, and we were going back and forth with them.  Duncan Robinson hits one off the glass at the end of the shot clock for a three.  Bam hits one off the glass right there before that we thought possibly went out; obviously it didn't count.  Herro hit some big shots.  Me and Do had a clean rebound, we're both going for it and we smash each other in the paint.  They kick it out to Jae Crowder and he hits a shot. To be able to get some stops and then make a timely shot, up six, you know if you make that shot, that three to put you up nine at that point in time of the game, then you know that you want to get one more stop obviously, but you have the time on your side because it's a three-possession game with 39 seconds.  Most veteran ballclubs will be able to survive that. Just a big-time play, big-time moment not only for AD but for our ballclub and our franchise."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What does an extra day of rest mean in a very physical series like this, and does it matter more to you now than it used to?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   No.  I mean, for me, it doesn't matter.  I can go every other day if that's the case.  But I'm going to take full advantage of it.  Gives me an opportunity to continue to get my body right, my mind, everything in between.  I'll take full advantage of it, but it does nothing for me besides just getting a little extra day -- I guess it does.  I guess it does do some, but it's not needed for me personally."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I believe it's like the third game of this series where you guys have called for a challenge in the first half.  You got it overturned, the right call.  How do you weigh the pros and cons of doing it so early?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   There's certain momentum plays throughout the first half.  There's a certain rhythm that you have either offensively or defensively that if that call is made correctly, then you continue to stay in that zone.  You continue to stay in that rhythm.  And if the call is wrong, it can throw you off of your rhythm. So we've wanted to challenge some things in the first half that we just felt like, okay, even if we were right, maybe that's not the time; we've still got our rhythm, we're good, whatever the case may be.  But we felt like in that particular moment, we were playing some really good basketball.  We were defending at a high level, and we knew for sure, we knew 100 percent, because I was guarding the ball, I knew for sure I didn't touch the ball.  Herro tried to float it over me and it hit the backboard, then hit the wire. Coach is always kind of like, you know, 50/50 about it, and obviously as a player on the floor, you hate to tell your coach to challenge when you're not 100 percent.  But I was for sure 100 percent about that play."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You mentioned the fourth quarter being winning time.  You played just about every second of the fourth quarter in this series.  Given the score, are you predetermined you're going to play all 12 minutes?  And what is it about the fourth quarter and your sense of urgency that might be a little different than the previous three quarters?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   For me, I mean, at this point in the season, I don't care about rest.  I really don't.  I don't care about sleep.  I don't care about resting throughout the game.  Obviously, I come out of the game.  Coach has a rhythm and rotation that we live by and we go by.  But I don't care about resting because I can rest in a week, max, if it happens to go there.  I could rest for a month straight, which I won't do because of who I am; you guys know that.  But I can rest then.  I can sleep eight hours and get up and eat and then go right back to sleep if I want to."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. KCP and Markieff both talked about a text that you sent that this was a must-win game.  What was it about today that prompted you to do that?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   When I woke up from my nap this morning after our team meeting, I just felt that.  I felt that vibe.  I felt that pressure.  I felt like for me personally, this was one of the biggest games of my career.  I just wanted to relay that message to my teammates, the type of zone I was in, the type of moment it was, and the kind of team we were playing against.  After the Game 3 win, that confidence they had, the confidence they still have even after tonight's loss.  They are just a gritty, so damn-well-coached team. I feel like if we're going to be a championship ballclub, if we want to really be a championship team, that we got to have that same grit and that same attitude.  It was my mindset.  I'm still in it.  You can see my mind kind of working right now."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Anthony's versatility on defense is a weapon that allowed Frank to make the switch and say he can start possessions on Butler.  AD's ability to do that, and still get back to protect the rim and to still deter shots, is it kind of unmatched?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Yeah, that's why he's the Defensive Player of the Year.  We said that all year.  His ability to play one through five, guard anybody on the floor, take the challenge, not only guard on the perimeter, continue to protect the paint.  Guards drive on him.  It's hard to score on him.  You see how high Herro threw that ball up?  It went in, but he had to throw that thing up to the skyscrapers, right?  That guy can do everything defensively.  Guarding the ball, guard the post, slide his feet with guards, contest, can body up with bigs.  I mean, need I say more?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. This is your 258th playoff game.  I'm wondering, how much have you come to enjoy the adjustment game to game that you have to make when you're in the playoffs, against good teams with good coaches that you know?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think that's the best part.  That's the best part.  I get so excited -- like right now, I'm excited about our meeting tomorrow watching film and breaking that down and seeing things that we can do better.  Seeing things that we did do well.  Thinking about the adjustments that they possibly or will do, because I know Spo going into Game 5.  That's the best part about it.  It's a chess match. When you get to this point in your career, having your mind at a high level is so much more than the physical because we're all -- at this point, we're all great players.  We're all here for a reason.  We're in the Finals, Both conferences, anybody that is on the floor, they are on the floor for a reason. To be able to think through the game and understand and see the adjustments and try to make plays before plays even seem like they are going to be possible, that's the best part for me personally."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: LAKERS VS. HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=160149",
    "date": "October 5, 2020",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. Just wondering what stood out the most to you when you went through the film last night?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Our turnovers.  Our turnovers really killed us.  We understand that we can't turn the ball over versus this team.  We also had some breakdowns defensively throughout the course of the game that we're not accustomed to having.  Those will be cleaned up in Game 4."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You guys have responded pretty well after losses in the playoffs so far.  I'm wondering if there's a common theme between those different times, and are you seeing that same kind of mentality now?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   We're able to take a loss and understand why we lost. Understand things that we should have done better and things that we can apply to the next game to be better.  We're right back at that moment once again with the opportunity to be better than we were in the game before. Look forward to the opportunity tomorrow night."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Specifically with Anthony, when he's had off nights or what have you, he's always responded in a really big way.  He's talked about you always kind of knowing how to approach him after a night when he's struggled.  What's your approach been with him today and what do you expect from him tomorrow?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I expect him to be AD.  I'm looking forward to getting out on the floor with him once again tomorrow night."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've been in the Finals 10 times now.  You've been up in series, you've been down in series.  What's it like to process the time off in between games coming off a loss?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Pretty much the same coming off a win for me.  Until the series is completed, I kind of stay on edge, stay locked in on the job at hand.  Obviously, no one wants to ever lose.  You hate that feeling, especially when you know you didn't play your best, and I definitely wasn't at my best last night from an individual standpoint.  So I take that responsibility and I take that with a lot of passion and understanding of how I can be much better in the following game. Throughout the postseason, I stay even keel.  As I've grown in this game and I've grown over the years, I kind of stay even keel, understanding that there's always another opportunity to get better.  We have that opportunity today and also tomorrow night in the game."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You're wearing a \"More Than a Vote\" shirt right now. In terms of trying to influence change, thinking back eight years ago when you wore those hoodies as a statement of Trayvon Martin, what are the biggest things you've learned about impacting change off the court?  Is there advice you now would have given yourself eight years ago when you kind of started this journey?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   That you can't get caught up in what everybody else thinks, because everyone is not going to always agree with your movement.  Everyone is not going to agree with your words.  Everyone is not going to agree with your passion.  Everyone is not going to always agree with why you're doing it, things of that nature.  If you're true to it and it hits home and it hits the heart, then it shouldn't matter.  And it doesn't, because you have the knowledge and you have the passion and you have the support to be able to shed light on situations that you feel are either unjust or wrong. There's a thing called common sense.  You know the difference between right and wrong.  It's something I've always grew up on.  My mother always told me [about] being able to understand the difference between right and wrong and noticing it and being able to have that feeling.  To sit back and think eight years ago when we sat in Detroit in the ballroom as a part of the Miami Heat team, and we all decided to put our hoodies on in a reflection, in a remembrance of Trayvon Martin and that tragic incident, we knew that it was going to be uncomfortable to a lot of people.  But we didn't care, because we understood how much it hit home for us and a lot of our guys having sons of their own.  We could imagine if our kid was to leave home and not return.  I think that's what it boils down to."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. In terms of talking to opponents on the floor, are you a guy who just responds to trash talk?  Do you initiate it?  As your status has moved up in the league, has it changed?  Have different players said different things or do they not want to talk to you because they don't want to get you going?  How does that equation go?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   No, I've always been a guy who kind of let his game do the talking.  But when guys get to talking, I can do that, as well.  I've always tried to let my game do the talking. Some guys like to talk their way through the basketball game.  I think it helps them out personally.  There's always communication going on on the floor.  For me personally, as long as it doesn't get disrespectful, I'm fine with it. But I've never really started up a trash-talking dialogue.  That's just not me.  I believe the way I play the game is enough trash talking in itself."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. From just a strategy standpoint, Bam is the type of big who is obviously a really great playmaker but he doesn't space the floor so much with his shooting.  The guys that Miami plays at the position now, Meyers and Olynyk, both do.  How much different does that force you guys to be defensively?  You talked about those defensive breakdowns last night.  I imagine spacing had something to do with a couple of them.",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think it all boils down to, no matter who's in the lineup for those guys, they're a great team. It's just that simple.  They're going to put you in positions that may feel uncomfortable, that will be uncomfortable, throughout the course of 48 minutes, and we have to be able to adjust.  There's things that Meyers and Kelly do that Bam doesn't do, but we also understand that there's things Bam does that not too many guys in this league can do.  They create different challenges depending on who's out on the floor. When there's five guys out on the floor for the Miami Heat, they're going to play how they play.  They're going to move the ball, they're going to move with pace, they're going to share the ball.  They've got guys that can get into the paint.  They've got guys that can shoot threes.  They've got guys that command double teams and things of that nature.  It doesn't matter who's out on the floor for them; they're going to be playing at a high level because that's just the way they are.  They're extremely well-coached from top to bottom."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've always prided yourself on playing the right way.  You still have those moments like the fourth quarter against Denver in the close-out game where you're like, this is going to end now and you go to that place.  Jimmy parallels you in that regard in that he doesn't want to have the ball in his hands every possession; he wants to get other guys involved.  And then you saw last night what he ends up doing.  Are you in that space yet where you think you might have to go that tack to close this thing out and go to that fourth-quarter-Bron-against-Denver mode, like we've seen so many times from you in the past?  Or are you not there yet?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I've never predetermined my game plan throughout my whole career.  I've never gone into a game saying, okay, I need to score 40 tonight, I need to dominate in the scoring facet, things of that nature, I need to make big shots.  I've never predetermined my game.  Throughout my whole life, I've never done that.  One thing I've always been, I've always been prepared.  If you're prepared, then whatever the game -- however the course happens, you're able to make adjustments throughout the game and you're able to impact the game because you're prepared and you've put in the work.  It's just that simple for me. I think anytime I've ever thought about, okay, I'm going to try to go out and do this, it doesn't happen that way.  The game has too many things that can happen throughout the course of the game and throughout the course of a quarter or possessions here and possessions there where you can try to plan for it, but audibles happen in the football sense. The best thing I can tell you is that I'm always prepared and I know that I've put in the work.  I trust that."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Early in the pandemic you mentioned that your body was kind of in shock, that you were rounding toward third base for the playoffs and then you had to stop.  All these months later, how would you say your body has responded to all that?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I'm in great shape.  I bounce back extremely well in between games.  I could play right now if we had to play right now, at a high level."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: LAKERS VS. HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=160135",
    "date": "October 4, 2020",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. Was there anything that you noticed in that first quarter about just the general way the team was playing and the turnovers that surprised you, and how did that play out for the rest of the game?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   We know that we can't turn the ball over versus this team.  They are very active defensively.  It starts with myself, being the starting point guard of the team, having five first-half turnovers, eight total for the game. Can't do that, obviously, because it gives them more possessions and doesn't allow us to set our defense.  They are really, really good offensively, so you just can't turn the ball over against that team. I take full responsibility for that."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've had a 40-point triple-double in the Finals before.  Just wondered what you thought of Jimmy's effort tonight and how you need to defend him better or differently in Game 4.",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I thought Jimmy was phenomenal.  He did everything that they needed him to do tonight and he came through big time in a big-time game.  We'll watch film and see ways we can be better going into Game 4.  But I thought he was great."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Anthony got into foul trouble early and had trouble getting going.  What did you see happening with him?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I mean, you just said it, he got into some foul trouble.  You know, they even -- one of the shots he made when he had four fouls, they still tried to slide underneath him and get him a fifth in the third.  I think the foul trouble made him a little passive, because he wanted to be out on the floor but he couldn't be his aggressive self offensively and defensively.  I think the fouls slowed him down a lot tonight."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Despite seemingly Miami controlling the action, holding the lead for most of the start of the game, you guys took a lead around nine minutes to go in the fourth quarter.  From there on, what do you think allowed them to separate from you guys?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   They continued to make shots, and we had some turnovers.  We didn't make shots.  They came out and executed after we took the lead.  Jimmy, like I said, he had his hand on all those plays pretty much. Obviously, we have to do a better job of that coming down the stretch.  But I like our fight tonight, even as poorly as I believe we played."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You guys obviously had a chance to take a 3-0 lead.  Are you concerned about giving Miami a breath of fresh air?  And with the possibility of Bam returning in the next game, do you feel like an opportunity missed that way?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   When you have an opportunity and you don't make the most of it, then you come back the next time.  I mean, it's not like the series was over if we won tonight.  We know for sure that Miami is never going to quit, no matter if we won tonight and they go into a Game 4, 3-0.  I know how resilient that bunch is and how resilient that coaching staff is and their franchise.  I don't ever feel like we let our guard down.  Also, I don't feel like we're concerned.  We're not concerned.  We know we can play a lot better.  We have another opportunity to take a commanding lead on Tuesday.  You relish that opportunity."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. When you guys have lost games this postseason, you've responded very well.  What is it about this group that's handled quick adjustments that has bounced back from losses so well in these playoffs?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   We learn from our mistakes pretty quick.  You know, obviously right now with the games being every other day pretty much, it's the film room.  It's the film room and it's how well we can make adjustments from the film and take it to the floor, and we have done a great job throughout this postseason.  So we are going to definitely have to do that because we're playing against a very, very, very, very good team.  We have to learn from our mistakes and be better on Tuesday."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. It's usually pretty fun when you and Jimmy play against each other over the years.  Would you say that you enjoy playing against him?  You respect playing against him?  Where is your level and emotions toward him as you go against him over and over, different teams, different cities?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Love it.  Love it.  One of the best competitors we have in our game.  We love that opportunity.  For me personally, I don't know how many more opportunities I'm going to have, so to be able to go against a fierce competitor like that is something I'll look back on when I'm done playing.  I'll miss those moments."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. When you walked off the court with about ten seconds left, was that frustration or did you think the game was over?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Both."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Would you say tonight's loss was more about effort or execution or a combination of the two?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I just think we can be better, obviously.  I don't think we started the game defensively in tune, and then offensively taking care of the ball.  Like I said, we had some careless turnovers.  It starts with me, like I said, and I take full responsibility for that.  I'll be a lot better on Tuesday with that, understanding that they are very good with their hands.  They are very good with the stripping.  You can't allow this team to have extra possessions.  You can't turn the ball over at that high a rate, especially at this point in the season, as well. I'll be a lot better with the security of the ball and the turnovers and things of that nature.  We as a team will be a lot better defensively with our game plan."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: LAKERS VS. HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=160070",
    "date": "October 2, 2020",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. I believe you would have just finished your junior year in high school, 2002, Kobe and Shaq both go for 30-plus against the Nets, Game 3 of the Finals.  You were drafted the next year.  You and AD, first time Lakers teammates have done that since then.  Wondered your thoughts on the Kobe-Shaq dynamic and what it's like going through a game like today with AD, especially at a similar level of efficiency.",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   You know, obviously being in high school, watching the Kobe-Shaq duo was the most dominant duo that I have personally seen in my life from a basketball perspective.  Obviously we knew the force that Shaq brought to the table, but the elegance and force that Kobe played with, as well. They were very dominant in what they did on the floor, on both sides of the floor.  So to be in the conversation with those two guys, myself and Anthony, myself and AD -- he's going to kill me -- myself and AD, is just very humbling, because I know I grew up watching those guys.  I grew up admiring Kobe; obviously, a kid coming straight out of high school.  Admired that, as a kid when I was young, and obviously got the opportunity.  And the force that Shaq played with.  It's very humbling that we can be even mentioned with those greats."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. AD and Frank indicated that even though it's a win, they were not totally happy with how things went defensively, especially Frank had mentioned that.  Do you agree, and if so, what concerns you?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I definitely agree.  Myself, Coach and AD were not happy with our defensive presence tonight.  We know we can be a lot better and we're just, myself and AD, we're not satisfied with just the win.  We want to be great.  We want to be great, as close to 48 minutes as possible. I know I said it after Game 1, but I'm extremely excited to watch the film tomorrow, as well as a group, to see ways we can be better.  We're playing against a very dangerous team in Miami, where they have five guys on the floor that's a threat, as they have shown tonight. So we have to continue to stay on our P's and Q's and cross our T's and dot our I's throughout the course of a game, and if we have a breakdown, being able to cover for one another.  But they do a great job of putting your defense in positions that you may not be accustomed to. We definitely were not happy with our performance defensively tonight. Hopefully we can be -- well, we know, not hopefully, we know we can be better in Game 3."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Shaq's a big post presence, a five as much as a five can be.  Kobe, perimeter, all that.  You and AD seem to have elements maybe of a bit of both of their games.  I don't know if you would agree with that, but if you do, could you describe how maybe both of you are a bit of a hybrid of what those guys brought to the court?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Well, I guess if you look in the sense of the size and the power and the speed that Shaq at his size played with, you could look at my game throughout the course of my career and say that.  And then you look at the elegance and the ability to shoot the ball and the ability to play in the paint as well as post up and get to the perimeter, I guess you can say that you can have some of AD's game that could compare to Kobe's game in that sense. Obviously, all four of us are all different positions.  Kobe was a natural 2-guard.  I'm kind of a, I don't know, whatever position.  Shaq is a center. AD is kind of a hybrid, as well.  But I guess all four of us, we have a winning mentality and we just tried to make enough plays out on the floor throughout the course of the game that would benefit not only ourselves individually but for the most important thing, for the better of the team. I can't even believe I'm up here talking about myself and AD with Kobe and Shaq."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. After the Heat timeout with UD, it seemed like there was a turn in momentum and they started attacking aggressively.  What do you know about UD that makes him impactful to a bench of players like that, even though he himself is not playing in the game?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Check his rÃ©sumÃ©.  It's that simple.  I mean, he's put in the work.  He's been there through everything that the Heat franchise has seen.  He's seen it all, done it all.  Just check his rÃ©sumÃ©.  There's not many guys that talk about it and also be about it, and he's one of them.  If you want to be in the foxhole, that's somebody you want to be in the foxhole with."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You used the word \"force\" probably six or seven times in the first two answers today.  How important has your team's ability to play with force made a difference in these first two games?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think I was talking about force because Shaq's name came up.  There's no way that you can talk about Shaq and not have that word come up.  From the team's perspective, I think we've done a good job of, one, not turning the ball over, but also still being able to play with force, as you would say.  Play with tempo offensively, get good looks. Get good looks that we like and, make or miss, live with the results.  We have to play with that type of force defensively, but also from the cerebral side, as well.  Thinking the game a little bit better as they are going through their offense and their pace and their force, as well.  We've got to be a lot better obviously on that side."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. When you guys advanced past Denver, Frank was talking about the relationship he has with you, and he said that the buy-in that you had with him as a coach and the immediacy of that buy-in did a lot for this team and where you are right now.  What was it about Frank that gave that you immediate buy-in and that you gravitated toward?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   For one, from a competitive standpoint, going against Frank's teams in Indiana when we had our battles and I was in Miami, you understood how well those teams were coached.  It starts with the head coach, and the players are an extension of the head coach. So I had that memory of that, just battling those Indiana Pacers teams.  And then for me, I've always been a coachable player throughout my whole life.  I've played for multiple coaches and I've always been a coachable player. So you know, the respect, more importantly, he's the head coach.  The head coach should have the respect from all his players, no matter who you are, if you're really serious about trying to make an impact or really trying to do something special.  It was just that simple for me personally."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: LAKERS VS. HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=160005",
    "date": "October 1, 2020",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. Just wondered over the course of your career what's your approach when your opponent is missing a couple of key players?  What's the message to relate to your team?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Keep the same thing the same thing.  You prepare for whoever is out on the floor.  There's going to be five guys in opposing jerseys on the floor, and they're all dangerous, no matter who's in the lineup, no matter what the name is.  You have to approach it like they all can beat you as a unit, and as individuals they're on the floor for a reason.  We understand that.  We will have a game plan, no matter who's out on the floor.  But that's not for us to worry about.  For us to worry about is how we approach the game coming into Game 2 and how we continue to work our habits and try to be as great as we can be throughout 48 minutes."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. In what ways have you benefited from all these Finals appearances in terms of what it's meant to have the game's best coaches kind of expose any weaknesses and nitpick at your game?  What coaches that you've faced on this stage have had the biggest influence on your improvements?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Like I mentioned last night, the best teacher is life experience.  I've played against great coaches throughout my whole career, not only in the regular season but in the postseason, throughout first, second, third, Finals runs.  I've played against some exceptional coaches, great coaches, Hall of Fame coaches, Hall of Fame players.  They've all, opponents and coaches, helped me get to this point where I am today, to a point where I have no weakness, offensively or defensively, to where if I can read a defense, I can exploit it.  I can put myself in a position to be successful.  It doesn't mean that the ball goes in all the time, but there's nothing out on the floor that I cannot do at this point in my career.  That's all because of the competition and the adversity and the losses and everything I've been through throughout the course of my career.  At that point in time I say I've got to work on this because that's what they're allowing me to have; now I've got to work on this because they're shutting this down in my game.  It's just, like I said, the best teacher in life is life experience, and I've experienced it all."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Last night you were so excited to get back into the film and just go over what had happened in Game 1.  How late did you stay up watching last night, and then today have you guys gotten together at all to watch film?  And then also I was wondering what your biggest takeaways were from that review.",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I stayed up until about 4:00, 4:30 in the morning last night breaking down the film individually, watching the same things that we did throughout the course of the game, seeing ways we were great, seeing ways we were not so great, and a lot of them were things that we can control.  We're playing against an exceptional basketball team, obviously, great coached.  So we have to continue to understand that coming into Game 2.  It was great to get with the guys today earlier and go over the film, and like I said, see things that we can do a lot better, both offensively and defensively. They're going to make adjustments in Game 2, and we need to be ready for that.  We can't come out with the energy that we had in Game 1 and go down 23-10 and expect the same result as we had in Game 1.  So we look forward to that challenge."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What's it like going up against a guy like Jae Crowder, who you had playoff battles when he was in Boston, then you were teammates, and now here you are going against one another again with the Finals on the line and having some physical moments in Game 1?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   It was like every other individual I went against in this playoff run."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. We talk about your leadership and how much you're able to help teach your teammates.  What does that look like during the regular season versus during the Finals?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I think for me, it's all about how you approach being a professional.  That's both on and off the floor, how you show up to work, how you walk, how you move, how you prepare.  It's not all about just talking about it.  It's how you be about it as well.  You don't get to pick two or three days out of the week where you want to be a leader or you say I want it to be Monday, Wednesday, Friday.  No, it's an everyday thing, both on the court and off the court. I try to lead by example.  I lead by my voice as well.  But I put the work in.  I think my guys see how much I put the work in, and they allow me to lead them.  I respect them for that.  I'm humbled by that as well."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Non-Finals question.  One of your rookie basketball cards bid for $1.8 million and another bid for $900,000.  Given your humble beginnings, what do you think of that when -- you're still playing, and it's not like you're Honus Wagner or Babe Ruth.  How do you take that in when somebody is paying $1.8 million for your rookie card?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I think it's pretty cool.  That's the first thing I think about when I think about where I come from, hearing those numbers -- you didn't hear those numbers much growing up, obviously, where I'm from.  And the second thing I think about is I have two rookie cards of my own, so I'll be good for a very, very long time.  No matter what happens, I'm good."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. A couple days ago you talked about what's happening in the world right now, controlling what you can control.  On the voting front, the Washington Post today had a story come out saying that the players have gone from I think 22 percent to 85 percent representation.  That's you guys controlling what you can control.  How much pride do you take in that, and do you feel like that message is landing and will make a mark?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   That is the hope.  That's the hope every day, that you can educate and you can get people motivated to go out and create change.  I've just tried to put not only myself but my team in position to be able to educate whoever needs it and to encourage and to empower people in our communities.  Like I say, we always talk about change in our communities: We want change, we want to see this, we want to see that.  We have the opportunity to do so. It's an honor for me to be in a position where I can have a platform and I can have a support system and I can have a group of people that we can put together a plan and then execute that and give it back.  It's also very humbling as well to hear that number, that percentage go from the low 20s to the 80s.  It's something that we want to continue to grow.  Hopefully we can be in the 90s by next week and even higher and in the higher 90s by November.  We want to continue that. Also had a lot of the volunteer poll workers in the virtual fan thing last night, 40 of them to be exact, and we have over 10,000 volunteers right now with More Than a Vote with the campaign that we're doing, initiative that we're doing.  Hopefully we can get 11,000 tomorrow and 12,000 and continue to grow that because it's so important.  We understand that, especially with COVID going around and not having the elderly out of their homes and doing those things, having the younger generation being able to come in and help out in such a difficult time right now with the virus that's going on still is very, very key.  Like I say, I'm proud of where we are, but we have a lot more room to go.  Hopefully we continue to do that."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I know you referenced \"Step Brothers\" the other night in relationship to Anthony.  But I want to know the common ground that you guys may share or have shared that allowed your relationship to flourish and if there's any way that he has an influence on you on the basketball court.",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   We're not jealous of each other.  I think that's the best thing.  In professional sports, you have guys that join forces to become alpha males.  That's what they call them.  Two guys that have been dominant in a specific sport on their own respective teams, and they get together and they talk about how dominant they can be and they talk about this is going to be this and that. I believe jealousy creeps in a lot.  And that is the absolute contrary of what we are.  We know who we are.  We know what we're about.  We want the best, seriously, every single day, both on and off the floor, for one another.  We're just not jealous of one another.  I think that you align that with respect, I think the sky's the limit."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. To follow up on what you said about you and AD, do you feel like the ability to not be jealous of each other is sort of a natural quality or is that something that has to be learned for some guys, and what was that like for you kind of striking that balance?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I don't speak for other guys and what they -- I don't know, I just speak for myself.  For AD, I know who we are.  We respect one another.  We drive one another.  We command excellence out of one another.  And that's what it boils down to. Jealousy and envy has killed a lot of great things, not only in sports but in general.  If you're able to just throw that to the side and throw your egos to the side but continue to bring that confidence of what you're trying to do of keeping the main thing the main thing -- not saying it's that easy, but for us it's that easy when it comes to our relationship.  Like I said, it doesn't result in wins every night.  It doesn't result in me putting up numbers or him putting up numbers every night, but as far as our brotherhood and our chemistry, that's what it boils down to."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Last night you said that you think it's easier to learn from wins than it is from losses.  I'm curious, though, how did the 2007 Finals shape the next 13 years of your career, going through that first trip and feeling that pain from that series?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Well, I mean, obviously they were the better team.  Dealing with Timmy and Manu and Tony and Pop, four Hall of Famers, I knew it would be challenging, not only for myself but for our franchise and for our ballclub.  I saw the way they approached every game, how they approached every possession.  They didn't make mistakes.  They weren't just happy with being there; they wanted to be great, as a unit and as individuals as well. I sensed that as a 22-year-old, and I saw that as a 22-year-old.  That helped shape me year after year after year after year, just holding on to that feeling of not being able to reach the ultimate goal.  But at the same time, like I said, just having that adversity and having those moments has put me in a position where I've been throughout my career."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. When you went to the first Finals against Golden State, you lose Kyrie Irving in Game 1, you had already lost Kevin Love, then you went out and won the next couple games.  When a team is in Miami's situation now and they talk about next man up, next man up, how did you go from saying we can still do this to putting together a plan and then actually going out and doing it the next couple games?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I think every situation is different.  For us, obviously, losing Kyrie and losing Kevin in that playoff run was detrimental to our success.  We were still able to have some success, but we never fully reached the full potential of what our ballclub could be in that run. That's different from -- I can't correlate that to what today is all about.  For us as a ballclub and for us as the Lakers, our mindset is Game 1 is over and Game 2 we've got to be better than we were in Game 1.  And when we approach that with that mindset and be as desperate as the opponent, then we give ourselves a good chance to win."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You guys were still able to create and sustain three separate runs despite not having those benchmark things from points in the paint and fast break points.  What did you like most about the ability to do that despite not having those weapons?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Yeah, for us the game kind of dictates itself at times.  We have to win in different ways.  We're very good at the fast break game.  We understand that.  But when we make our mark on the defensive end, when we're getting deflections, we're getting blocked shots, we're contesting shots either at the rim or at the perimeter or mid-range, things of that nature, which creates early offense for us, it doesn't always show up in the box score, but when we're active defensively, we're an extremely good team. Every game is going to be its own challenge, and we understand that.  You have to win games in different fashions.  Sometimes even outside your own box.  But I think the great teams learn that throughout the course of a run, throughout the course of a season, and that's what puts them in a position to compete for a championship, which we are today."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: LAKERS VS. HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=159983",
    "date": "September 30, 2020",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. You guys went on a 75-30 run after falling down 13 early.  What allows you guys to have success like that over a sustained period of time, a run like that?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Paying attention to detail.  I don't think in the beginning that we were physical enough.  You have to get a feel for how hard Miami plays.  I think they smacked us in the mouth, and we got a sense of that.  And so we knew how hard we had to play if we wanted to try to make it a game. You know, from that moment when it was 23-10, we started to play to our capabilities.  We started flying around.  We started getting defensive stops.  We started sharing the ball a lot better offensively and just got into a really good groove."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. For AD, obviously his first Finals game.  What did you see about his preparation?  Was there any advice you gave him, and to see him perform like that, what do you feel about that?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I don't feel anything.  I expect it out of him.  Didn't need to give him no advice.  We've been preparing for this moment all season.  He's been preparing for this moment all season.  I'm happy to be on the same floor with him and in the same uniform.  He was, once again, a force in every facet of the game, offensively and defensively."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've felt the buzz of the NBA Finals nine times in your career, but what was it like today with nobody there, the sound?  I know you're used to bubble basketball at this point, but at this stage what did it feel like to play a Finals game?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Felt great.  Felt great.  I've been preparing for this moment for quite a while.  Fans, no fans, the inner challenge for myself and the way I prepare myself, it felt amazing to be playing in the Finals once again."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've seen plenty of times over the years where if one team has a bunch of injuries, the other team floats a little bit and doesn't come at them as hard.  How do you make sure that you guys don't do that in Game 2?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   We've got so much more work to do.  The job is not done.  We're not satisfied with winning one game.  It's that simple."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. There was a few times where you guys got up big, and there was a lot of celebrating going on, and I see sometimes you had to rein it in a little bit.  In your experience, what have you seen in the past that got you to the point where you felt like sometimes you need to say, okay, let's keep it on task?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   The best teacher in life is experience. I've experienced moments in my career where you have all the momentum in the world and you felt like you had the game under control, and one play here or one play there could change the course of a series or change the course of a game. One in particular that always rings home for me is Game 2 of the 2011 Finals in Miami versus Dallas.  D-Wade hits a three right by their bench.  I believe it put us up either 13 or 17.  From that moment on, Dallas went on a hell of a run and finished it off with a Dirk Nowitzki left-hand layup to steal that game.  That (expletive) burns me to this day. I always talk about the best teacher in life is experience, and I've experienced a lot.  That's what prompts me to be who I am today, is being able to have those experiences."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I'm wondering in a game like this when you had the kind of lead that you had, are you already thinking, \"This is what we could do better, here are some things that we're doing wrong.\" Were you already in that frame of mind during this game?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Yeah, absolutely.  I think you can learn so much more from a win than you can in a loss.  I can't wait for tomorrow for us to get back together and watch the film and see ways we can be better and see some of the breakdowns that we had, especially in that fourth quarter, especially in that first six minutes of the first quarter where we can be so much better defensively and also so much better offensively. So I can't wait.  I'm extremely amped up about watching the film with our ballclub tomorrow.  I'm going to watch some tonight obviously by myself, but I'm looking forward to getting together as a group tomorrow."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Teams have spent your whole career trying to keep you out of the paint, and you can say the same thing this season about AD.  What are some of the ways that you guys are still always seemingly able to get to the rim and still able to finish?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Because we have great spacing and great shooters.  KCP, Danny Green, Kyle Kuzma and Markieff Morris, a list of guys that can spread the floor, it allows myself and AD to be able to do the things that we do in the interior. We try to mix up our game, too.  We try to mix it in in the interior and the exterior.  But when you have guys that could space the floor like we have, it allows us to do some of the things that we do in the paint."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Why is Rondo so opposed to being called Playoff Rondo, and did you see some of that in the first half especially?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I'm not sure.  I've never called him that.  We've never called him that.  We only call him Do.  So that would be a Do question. But you know, just having him in this moment, having him on our side, and I think he mentioned yesterday or whenever Media Day was for the Finals, you just don't -- you never know.  You don't get these moments a lot.  It's been over a decade since he's been in the Finals.  I think he's just cherishing the moment, but also just playing the game that he loves to play -- the cerebral way, the determined way, the championship way, as he's been playing for quite a while now."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: LAKERS VS. HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=159954",
    "date": "September 29, 2020",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, just studying the Heat and what you've seen from them in this postseason, what's at the top of the list?  What stands out the most to you about the way that they're playing basketball?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I would think two things:  One, how hard they play for 48 minutes, no matter if they're up, no matter if they're down.  They play extremely hard.  And I think two, it would be the way they move off the ball, they share the ball.  Everyone is live on the floor.  There's not one guy that you can disrespect or be off throughout the course of an offensive possession.  And they do a hell of a job of moving without the ball, sharing the ball, cutting, passing.  Those are two things that stand out."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've described that time in Miami like it was going to college for you.  If you can think back to those four years, what were the most important lessons you learned about yourself and about leadership in general?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think as far as leadership, that grows no matter where you are every day, if you want to be a leader, if you strive to be a leader every day.  I think being around Riles and Spo, D-Wade and UD, just to name a few, being a part of that culture allowed me to grow, allowed me to see what it takes to not only compete for a championship but also to win a championship.  So it definitely put me in a position where I knew what it took.  I saw what it took.  But also I fit that culture as well because of how hard I worked.  It was a perfect match for those four years."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Would it have any extra meaning to you to win a championship against Pat Riley and Erik Spoelstra, guys that have helped shape you and vice versa in those years together?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Absolutely not.  It's no extra meaning to winning a championship, no matter who you're playing against.  It's already hard enough to even reach the Finals, to be in this position.  If you're able to become victorious out of the Finals, it doesn't matter who it's against.  I'm just happy that I'm here with the opportunity to represent not only myself but represent our fans, our fan base, our organization, my teammates, our coaching staff, our training staff and so many others that represent this organization to the utmost respect."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Six years after playing for Miami, how do you feel about Pat Riley?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   That's such a broad question.  I don't understand."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Leaves it open for interpretation.  When you hear the name Pat Riley, what do you think about?  How do you describe your relationship --",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   When I hear Pat Riley, I think about one of the greatest minds probably this game has ever had.  He's won at every level.  I saw the stat the other day that he's been part of a championship in four decades.  This league is not the same without Riles.  He's a great guy, great motivator, someone that just knows what it takes to win, and he's shown that over the course of, what, 40 years."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've talked about just sort of the difficulty of adapting to the bubble. How much have you sort of motivated yourself by reflecting that your teammates are taking cues from you and trying to see how you approach things and sort of approach getting through this grind, the three months here?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   It's probably been the most challenging thing I've ever done as far as a professional, as far as committing to something and actually making it through.  But I knew when I was coming what we were coming here for.  I would be lying if I sat up here and knew that everything inside the bubble, the toll that it would take on your mind and your body and everything else, because it's been extremely tough. But I'm here for one reason and one reason only, and that's to compete for a championship.  That was my mindset once I entered the bubble, once I entered the quarantine process the first two days.  Then right from my first practice, my mindset was to -- if I'm going to be here, make the most of it and see what you can do and lock in on what the main thing is.  The main thing was for us to finish the season and compete for a championship. So that's just been my mindset throughout these -- I don't even know how many days it is.  However many days it is, it feels like five years.  So it really doesn't matter.  I've been as locked in as I've ever been in my career."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Back in March the season comes to an end, two players on your team test positive for this virus.  When did you think getting to this point was even a possibility?  And what was it like kind of mourning the fact that maybe it wasn't happen?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I didn't know that this was a possibility until we actually got on the plane in L.A. to fly here to Orlando.  We had seen some other teams arrive before us.  We got here July 9th.  We had seen some of the teams arrive a couple days before us.  But until we landed here, actually got off the plane, got on the bus and pulled up here to the hotel, that's when it became a reality to me."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. From your vantage point, what do you think it is about Erik Spoelstra that, no matter if it's coaching No. 1 picks or a collection of undrafted/lower-drafted guys, allows him to continue to bring groups back here to the Finals, but also not necessarily always be in the conversation with that upper echelon of coaches?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Well, that's a question for you guys.  The players and the coaches know how great Spo is.  There's this narrative that Spo is not great, and the narrative that he doesn't get a lot of respect, which he should.  He prepares his team every single night.  If you watch the Miami Heat, no matter who's on the floor, they're going to play Heat culture. They're going to play hard. They're going to play together.  That's what he's always been about.  It's been you guys that have changed the narrative or has never given Spo his respect because he had D-Wade or he had myself or he had Bosh.  But a lot of coaches have talent.  A lot of coaches have had talent over the course of this league.  It's not one. It's unfortunate that he hasn't gotten his respect.  Every time we talked about Spo when I was there and we talked about how great he prepared us, and we talked about how great it was playing for Spo and things of that nature, you guys always said, Well, you have LeBron, you have D-Wade, you have Bosh; any coach can do it.  No, any coach can't do it.  If any coach could do it, then there would be a lot more champions in this league.  There would be a lot more successful coaches. Spo likes it.  That's what fuels Spo, is the disrespect that you guys give him, the basketball world.  I'm not going to sit up here and act like I don't know what Spo is all about, because he's damned good, if not great.  Probably is great, because his preparation.  He prepares like it's his last time ever coaching again every game, and I know that.  That's why I feel good."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. There is political financial data out there that shows that pro sports owners, including NBA owners, donate overwhelmingly to Republican causes.  I know they've pledged a lot of money to help with racial and social justice issues, but do you feel that those political contributions undercut some of the efforts that players are making to gain progress on those topics?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Well, one, I'm not going to give my energy to that because it's not surprising.  My mom has always told me, control what you can control, and I can't control that.  What I can control is what I'm doing on my side and trying to have people gather around me and gather around my initiatives and doing what we're doing to try to effect change, not only in our communities but outside of our communities with the youth, and let them understand how important their voice is and their vote is to our society.  It's hard as hell, because they just don't believe it.  They don't believe that their vote or their message or their minds or their voices matter.  But that's where my energy is, on continuing to push the envelope in my community, continue to let them know that they are the future, they are the reason why there will be change.  But I can't give my energy to the other side because that will take away from my people, and I can't do that. Control what you can control.  I can't control that. That is what it is.  It's not a surprise.  But I've got work to do on the other side.  So that's what my mission is about."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You mentioned you're as determined as ever, right now as locked in as you've ever been.  Usually during this postseason run you block out from social media.  You couldn't do it this year because you're in a bubble, away from family.  Important election coming up.  How has that adjustment been for you during this time to have access to social media?  You usually try to eliminate distractions, but you've got it right there in your hand.",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Yeah, I think in this particular case, everything about this year is different.  Everything about 2020 is different, and to make the most of it, you have to be able to adjust.  I've adjusted in the sense of understanding that there's also a bigger opportunity coming up as well in November, while I'm still keeping the main thing the main thing and the focus on leaving a legacy here and playing the game that I love to play and competing for a championship.  But also letting my people know that I'm not jaded, and I'm not too distracted where I cannot continue to give the resources, put the people in place to help them go to the places where they don't believe they can even go.  Sometimes you do things that even you personally don't even believe that you can do, but when you have a support system, and you have a group around you that's just as motivated as you, you're able to tackle a few things at once."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. The last couple times you were here, you were pretty outmanned by a team with four great players.  As you come back now with the team you have around you, how do you feel going into this 10th Finals now?  Do you feel like talent-wise you don't have to worry about that problem this time?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I never had a problem with any team I went to the Finals [with].  I've always been confident that we had the ability to win.  If you're going to a Finals saying you're undermanned or you feel like you don't have enough, then who are you?  The game is won between the four lines, not won on paper.  At the end of the day, when I've lost in the Finals, the better team won because they played well, they were more prepared and they did what they needed to do to win those four games.  When I've won, the same thing. I'm not here to talk about the talent we all have, the team that we have.  The game is won in between the four lines, 94 feet.  The team that is prepared and the team that executes, the team that is not careless throughout 48 minutes will give themselves a chance to win each and every game.  I'm confident going into this Finals, as I've always been in my career."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. It's been a long time, obviously, since you played for the Heat and a lot has happened to you and to the league since then.  All these years later, is there something that you still take away from your days in Miami?  The other one is, how are you different just from the last time that you were in the Finals, which was two years ago?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think every part of anybody's individual life where they were able to grow, it never leaves you.  That's no different for me having my four years in Miami, being around -- with that culture, growing.  You guys don't realize, I talk about it, I went to Miami when I was 25 years old.  I was 25.  I was 25 to 29, so I was still growing.  I was still a kid and still trying to figure out who I am as a person and as a man, growing while still trying to compete for a championship every single year. I grew, and they allowed me to grow.  We pushed each other every single day, and like I said, I fit perfectly in that culture because I worked just as hard as anybody else.  I show up to work and I don't leave until I feel like I was as great as I was.  Do you always become successful at it?  Are you always going to win?  No, it doesn't happen like that.  But you're able to sleep a little bit better at night when you know you've punched the clock. And how am I different today than two years ago when I entered the Finals?  I've got a little bit more gray hair in my beard."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA WESTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: LAKERS VS. NUGGETS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=159921",
    "date": "September 26, 2020",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. As the confetti fell on the court, you were sitting on the ground.  Can you share what was going through your mind?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Yeah, just, one, getting my breath back underneath me after a hard-fought series against one of most well-coached team I've ever played against in the postseason, one of the most respected teams I've played against. Obviously, you guys know how much I love Mike Malone.  He's incredible.  He's the reason why that team is so damn good.  So I was thinking about that. I was also thinking about some of my teammates who this is their first appearance to the Finals.  Obviously, AD had a lot on my thought process.  This is the reason why I wanted to be a teammate of his and why I brought him here.  I wanted him to see things that he had not seen before in this league.  To be able to come through for him meant a lot for me personally. Then I started thinking about the next opponent. Boston had a few moments in my head.  Miami had a few moments in my head as well.  How challenging that's going to be, whoever wins that series. Then I just started thinking about my journey as well.  All that was just going through my mind as the confetti was on the floor, was coming down, landing on my shoulder and things of that nature.  So hopefully that was a good description."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Frank said he felt like you played with a chip on your shoulder all year.  What does it mean to this have moment after everything you went through with your first year with the Lakers and after every single obstacle you kept hitting this season and yet you still end up where you were trying to get?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   For me personally, the job is not done.  But it's great to hit moments throughout the course of a journey and appreciate that.  This is all part of the process, but the job is not done for me personally. For us as a franchise, I'm extremely proud to be a part of this franchise getting back to where it belongs, and that's playing for championships and competing for championships and representing the Western Conference in the championships. This is what I came here for. I heard all the conversations and everything that was said about why did I decide to come to L.A -- the reason I came to L.A., it was not about basketball.  All those conversations, just naysayers and things of that nature.  I understood that, with the season I had last year and my injury, it just gave them more sticks and more wood to throw in the fire to continue to say the things that they would say about me.  But it never stopped my journey and never stopped my mindset and never stopped by goa. I'm happy, like I said, and proud of this organization and proud of my teammates and I'm proud of the coaching staff, the front office and our ownership as well at this very moment today."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You mentioned getting the Lakers back to the Finals.  Last time they got there, Game 6 Western Conference Finals, 2010, Kobe goes for 37, hits all those dagger jumpers in the fourth.  How do you process your emotions all year about Kobe, and as this run has continued, wearing the purple and gold, how that's all sat in your mind?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I mean, every time you put on purple and gold, you think about his legacy.  You think about him and about what he meant to this franchise for 20-plus years, and what he stood for both on the floor and off the floor.  What he demanded out of his teammates and what he demanded out of himself. We have some similarities in that sense. Our games are different, but as far as our mindset and our drive to want to be the best and our drive to not lose -- sometimes you're going to lose games, but that drive to always want to be victorious, it stops you from sleeping.  And sometimes you put certain things -- you sacrifice a lot of things.  You sacrifice your family at times because you're so driven to be so great that other things fall by the wayside at times. So I understand that.  I'm one of the few that can understand the mindset that he played with and the journey from high school to the NBA. It's just a thing that I carry with me, like I said, every time I decide at one point in that locker room before the game when I throw that jersey on."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Do you find yourself savoring these moments more than when you were younger?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I don't, unfortunately.  I wish I did.  They happen so fast and my mind is still so locked in on the journey that it's hard for me to take in and appreciate what we just accomplished. Just how I've always been. I always say that when I'm done playing the game, hopefully I look back on it and enjoy it -- and hopefully I will.  Hopefully I can, because I don't think I enjoy it enough when I'm in it because I'm so engulfed in the process until the final call. But I'm so damn proud of this team and where we are right now up until this day."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. The nature of your accomplishments has had you compared to the greats of the game for a long time, but you've insisted, \"I'm my own guy and it's my own story.\"  What about the fact that you didn't just stay on the first team you played with, first city; you go to Miami, you go to L.A.  What has that meant to you to blaze your own trail as a superstar or whatever?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I don't know, I've never looked at it that way.  I've never said, OK, I want to cast myself as a superstar or whatever the case may be.  I just want to travel my own journey, because it is my journey. I've appreciated everything that's happened along the way.  I mean, throughout -- the ups, the downs, the ups on the court, the downs on the court, the wins and losses. But I've been able to, I guess as Frank Sinatra would say, I did it my way.  At the end of the day and at the end of my career, I just hope that I inspire enough people to want to play the game the right way, and have that respect from all the opponents that I played against, all the teams that I played against and the organizations that I play for.  Because at the end of the day, I mean, that's all you have, is your respect."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. The Finals have been basically the LeBron James Invitational for the last decade.  What were you doing at this time last year and how did that affect your continued determination to get back here?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Well, it all depends what game you were talking about.  There were a couple games where I was at home.  There was one or two games where I was in Cabo and a couple games where I was at a hookah lounge during the Finals last year.  That's the truth.  I wasn't smoking hookah, but I was there."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Was the game on or no?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Absolutely.  I wouldn't have went.  The game was on in Cabo, the game was on in my house and at the hookah lounge.  I watched every single minute of the games until they stopped.  I actually watched every single postseason game last year.  I think I told David that; I watched every single postseason game. Part of me, I'm just a fan of the game.  I love the sport.  I love the competitive nature.  I love the playoffs. And then, also, of saying like, oh, I wish I was in this moment, what would I have done at that moment? What play would I have made in that moment if I was out there? So yes, I didn't miss a game.  I didn't miss one game.  Even on vacation, I didn't miss a game.  My wife didn't like it, but she'll be OK (smiling)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. In the fourth quarter, where is your head at in terms of deciding this thing is not going to a Game 6?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I've always had the mindset that in a close-out game for me personally, I'm just as desperate as the team that we are trying to close out.  I don't want to play another game.  And if we are in a position where we can win that game, that's just my mindset. Does it always go that route?  No, because I don't believe I'm undefeated.  I'm not undefeated in close-out games.  My mindset is that I do not -- if we have played well enough and we are in the fourth quarter and we have a chance to win, I do not want to play another game.  I mean, I love the game, but I do not want to play another game.  That's always been my mindset.  I want to be just as desperate as my opponent, just as desperate as the other team, the player that I'm lined up against, the coaching staff that's on the other side.  It's just who I am.  It's just a mindset I'm able to link into at that very moment."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, you said that you thought about AD and wanting to show him something that he has never seen before.  What has he meant to you this season?  Obviously, you guys are very close, but to go through this year with him, how have you needed him?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I guess it was a very, very, very, very long time ago, when I was 27, like a long-ass time ago when I was 27 in this league.  I just wanted to put myself kind of in his position.  Sometimes what I would be thinking at that age and if I was with someone in the later stage of their career, I just don't want to let them down.  And I'm not even talking on the floor, because there's things that sometimes they go in, they don't go in. But as far as, I don't want to say a role model, but someone that holds myself to a higher standard as far as character.  I don't want to let them down.  And then, it's funny because it's kind of rubbed off on me as well because he doesn't want to let me down. I don't know, you've seen the movie Step Brothers before, right?  Well, there it is."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Are you Will Ferrell or?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Yeah, I'm Will Ferrell, for sure.  I get on his nerves a lot, for sure.  I go in and mess with his drums and he's not watching -- yeah, that's me.  I get on his nerves a lot."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Alex Caruso, how has he grown and how much resolve has he shown?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think Alex Caruso is a true definition of when opportunity meets preparation.  He's been preparing for this moment for a long time and he just needed opportunity. Luke [Walton] gave him an opportunity last year, and now Coach Vogel and our coaching staff are giving him an opportunity on a bigger stage.  He's just taking full advantage of that and just full stride.  He's just gotten better and better every single minute he's on the floor. He's still learning.  Every game is still a learning experience for him because he's so new to the NBA.  He played a lot of his minutes over the course of his early stages in the G League. But first time I saw him, and seeing him in some of our practices, it wasn't the sneaky athleticism.  It was the way that he defended and how cerebral he played the game. I gravitate toward players like that right away, because the game, everybody talks about the physical side and how high you can jump and how fast you can run and all those things.  But the mental side is what gets you to the next level.  You know, I saw that from A.C. and he continues to learn.  He's just been great for us."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Your track record speaks for itself, and there's a lot of talent and experience with your teammates.  Given this is Frank's first year what jumped out of how he managed everything, not just this group, but all the unique challenges this year?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   He's been great.  He's been unbelievable.  I mean, we've faced, it's been a crazy obstacle course for our franchise this whole year.  I'm not going to sit here and give all the details, but you guys, everyone can go back and just see from the start of the season all the way up until now what we've gone through as a team.  He's been able to manage it the whole time.  Bringing in guys, losing guys.  He's just always been the anchor, and our coaching staff has been right behind him.  I can't say anything more than that. Just happy to be on the floor to kind of be his coach on the floor and just command to my teammates the same message that he's given to me and be an extension of his mind.  It's been great."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. In the postgame ceremony, you said how tough it is to get to the Finals.  You've now done it nine times over the last 10 years.  How have you been able to have that type of longevity, and how did this ceremony feel this year without fans?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   One, I've taken care of my body.  I've been available to my teammates.  That's one.  I sleep.  I try to get as much sleep as I can.  I think there's no better recovery than sleep.  And then I've never cheated the game as well.  I've put so much work into my craft, so much work into the game.  I think you add on to the fact that I've played with some great teammates and some great coaching staffs, from T-Lue and his coaching staff to Erik Spoelstra and his coaching staff, and now this coaching staff with Frank Vogel. I'm blessed.  I'm truly blessed.  They have all allowed me to be me.  They have allowed me to go out and do the things that I do on the floor.  Use my mind, my play and be able to command my teammates the way I do.  It's put me in position to be able to, like you said, be in the Finals nine out of 10 years. To answer your second question, everything is different.  It's 2020.  Nothing feels the same.  Everything is different.  So the ceremony is different.  The one thing I can say, I wish we were in Staples Center tonight with our fans, with our Laker faithful, because they deserve this as much as we do because they went through the last so many years of not being in a postseason run, feeling like their franchise would never get back to this moment.  But they continued to stay faithful.  It would have been great to celebrate with them tonight. So hopefully we can continue to give them something to smile about in the next round, as well. That's what our mindset is."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA WESTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: LAKERS VS. NUGGETS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=159898",
    "date": "September 24, 2020",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. Rondo said you switching over to Murray was key; wondered when you made that decision and what your mindset is when you're going against a smaller guy that's been that effective.",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I knew it was winning time, and Jamal had it going.  The kid is special.  He has an array of shots.  Triple threat from the three, mid-range and also in the paint. For me, it's just trusting my defensive keys.  Trusting my study of film.  Trusting personnel.  And living with the results.  I told my teammate that I had him and everyone else can kind of stay at bay and stay home.  I was able to get a couple stops and we were able to rebound the basketball, which is the most important thing."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. How are you feeling about the type of shots you guys are getting especially when they are packing the paint?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think at times we're doing a great job.  At certain times, we can do a better job with our spacing, especially on our post-ups.  They are doing a little doubling on the post at times, so we've got to get a better outlet for AD when he is posting up and get the ball swung-swung as quickly as possible to get more looks.  I thought we did a really good job, more importantly, tonight of not turning the ball over.  The thing we talked about in Game 2 and Game 3 is we cannot turn the ball over against this team.  We did a great job of that tonight."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Frank said the other day that he's been trying to manage your minutes to a level where it may be the least you've played in your postseason career.  With that management, did it allow you to keep something in reserve to make a move to guard Murray late?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Not for me.  I don't reserve any energy.  I'm on the floor, I give it all I got.  If I need a break, I ask for a break.  Coach has done a good job of getting me out throughout the course of the game.  I don't look at it as a reserve tank.  I've got pretty good energy when I'm on the floor all the time.  It's winning time and I don't have a chance or time to be feeling tired.  I'm tired now.  That's when I'm tired, when it's zeros on the clock.  That's when I'm tired.  I'm not tired during the game."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Now the Nuggets are down 3-1 just like they have been the last two series and that's a narrative everybody likes to talk about.  You guys have also been up 3-1 in both of your series and closed them out.  In this game you fixed some issues from Game 3.  What's your level of confidence that you'll be able to take care of this in five games?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   It's just about playing to our capability.  Coming out with the game plan and executing it for 48 minutes.  If we do that, we give ourselves a good chance to win."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. In the starting lineup with Dwight, he made a big impact early.  What was that impact?  And late in the game, what about the smaller lineup?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Dwight was a beast.  Gave us opportunities when we missed shots, which as a team, we missed a couple.  AD didn't miss any, but as a team, when we missed a couple shots, he was cleaning glass both offensively and defensively.  Got us put-backs and was able to control the paint.  We know we got smashed in the rebounding category in Game 3, so we wanted to do a better job in that. Dwight brought that physical presence.  It was great for our ballclub. Tonight, late game, Do [Rajon Rondo] was running pick-and-rolls.  I was able to run a couple.  But we just made our free throws.  We made our free throws down the stretch, and that's what closes games out.  You've got to get your stops defensively, make your free throws when you're fouled. And I thought we did that."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Anthony said he wasn't so happy with the way he played or ended the previous game.  He came out on fire tonight.  What have you learned about him on off days after a game he doesn't love?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   See how low his brow is.  If his brow is really low, then you know not to talk to him.  If it's higher, then he's accepted the fact that you're allowed to come into his office and talk to him. Yesterday his brow was very low in this part and no one talked to him.  So we already knew the mindset he was in, and he came out and did it."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. We saw your posts about protecting Black women.  Specifically for you, what does that actually mean?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think at the end of the day, respect.  You just look at the history of America and the disrespect that Black women have gotten for the last 400 years.  You can't turn a blind eye to that. When I look at my household and see my daughter, who is five on her way to six, my wife and my mom, rest in peace my grandmother, so many Black women have done so many things for me.  Seeing the sacrifices they made, especially my mom when I was growing up.  They were disrespected along the way and it's still like that today. In the case of Breonna Taylor's case, it's just shown once again that the walls of the neighbor is more important than her life. So not only did I want to acknowledge all the queens in this world, all the Black queens in this world, but the ones in my life, the personal ones, too.  I just kind of had a moment yesterday.  I mean, I have a lot of moments, but felt like it was important to let Black women know that you're not alone.  No matter the disrespect or what they may feel, don't stop.  Because that's exactly what they want you guys to do.  They want you guys to stop.  They want you guys not to be as powerful as you guys are, not as strong as you guys are, as determined as you guys are.  They want you all to be at bay.  They want you to accept what's going on.  For sure, I won't allow that. When they are feeling down or feeling like there's no journey for them or gateway to be heard or to be seen or be respected or be accepted, my job is to continue to let them know that they are.  They are important to everything that goes on, not only in America but in the world. Everything that goes on for 24 hours in day, 365 days a year, 366 in a leap year.  That's what it's about."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Were there any thoughts of not playing?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   We didn't talk about that.  One thing, we wanted to be there for our brother, Do.  As much as it's devastating to us, you can only imagine it happening in your backyard. Do being from Louisville,  we knew how tough it had to be on his family and the locals there. No, we didn't discuss that one bit.  But can't say that we were surprised at the verdict.  None of us are surprised at it.  That's what's more devastating, that none of us were surprised at what the outcome was."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Speaking of Do, can you talk about how he played tonight?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Do has been in a lot of playoff games.  He's won a championship.  He's played at the highest level, and he's someone that we can trust. In the postseason, every possession is so important. When you can have guys that have been in the moments and can understand and also be able to make adjustments on the fly, and know that you can count on them down the stretch, it just makes the team and you individually feel so much more confident in the outcome. Do has been, ever since he got back from injury and we saw this playoff run, he's been exceptional."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've been here 70-plus days --",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Thank you.  Reminded me."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Going through these experiences, like Breonna Taylor as a group, how does that change how a team processes something like that versus the way that when these things have happened in the past, how you would deal with it when maybe you weren't all together?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think the best thing is that we have been together.  We're able to see what's going on and be able to bounce things off one another and to be there for one another. This game is so much bigger than just us getting on the floor and running around and calling out screens and running plays and making mistakes and trying to figure out how we can be better the next time.  There's also a big thing called life that's involved in this, too.  And to have, like you said, things that happened in Kenosha, and the Breonna Taylor case and so many other things that are going on in America, as we speak and as we move forward, being around people that you can trust and confide in, be able to talk to, bounce things off and not feel that you have to tackle it by yourself, I think that's very important when you have a support system like that. The best thing that you can have is a close-knit group, because we're together more than we are with our families.  So having that support is pretty amazing."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA WESTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: LAKERS VS. NUGGETS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=159871",
    "date": "September 22, 2020",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. What did you think was the difference that let Denver build that 20-point lead?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think it was the same in Game 2, same thing that we were able to get by with AD's shot, turned the ball over too much.  We couldn't get to the free throw line, and you know, I give credit where credit is due, though. Denver came in and played exceptionally well.  They played better than us, more aggressive than us through three quarters, 36 minutes, but you know, we've got into the penalty in the third quarter with like nine and a half minutes to go and we had some turnovers that led to some easy buckets for them.  We had 16 turnovers for 25 points and put them to the line 29 times.  It's not going to be winning ingredients for us if we continue to do that and we knew that, even after Game 2, we talked about that, trying to assure that.  Got to be better than that Game 4."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Frank talked about the importance of touching the paint off drives when a team is packing it in like Denver has.  What are some things you can do better in Game 4?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think offensively we were very good.  At times, we weren't.  I think we just got to do a better job, like Coach was saying, of getting to the paint and once the defense collapses, just finding our guys weak side; if it's a guy that's slashing, through a weak side to the paint or if it's a guy that's spotted up on our side off one of our bigs, getting behind the defense for a lob. So Denver has been a pretty good defensive team all year.  We understand that.  I'm looking forward to seeing our film -- our film session tomorrow and continue to get better."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. The success you guys had in the fourth quarter, some due to zone defense, some due to activity, was it just a matter of upping intensity level or giving a different look that Denver wasn't anticipating?  How do you account for the run you went on?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think it's a bit of both.  I think we played with a lot more energy, and we understand we had 12 minutes left to try to make a game out of it and we were able to do that.  We were able to switch some things up defensively, going zone here, man here, trying to keep them off balance. When you dig yourself a hole like that, every shot that they make and every shot that we miss, feels like the game is collapsing.  So you know, we played some pretty good ball in the fourth quarter, but those first 36 minutes, that hurt us obviously."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I wanted to ask you something off the court.  You've spent so much time in the bubble talking about police brutality and the relationship of police in the black community and on Tuesday you expressed your condolences towards the officers in Compton who were shot and talked about the need for non-violence.  There's this sort of narrative in this framing that emerges from some people that frames your position in talking about police brutality as something that incites violence against officers, and the L.A. County Sheriff obviously had that kind of implication last week when he asked you to contribute to the reward.  I'm wondering what your reaction is when you hear those two things connected, and did you think it was appropriate for the sheriff to sort of bring that up and bring you into that discussion?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I've never in my 35 years ever condoned violence.  Never have.  But I also know what's right is right and what's wrong is wrong and I grew up in an inner city in a black community, in what we call the \"hood,\" the \"ghetto,\" however you want to picture it.  And I've seen a lot of counts, firsthand, of a lot of black people being, you know, I guess racially profiled because of our color, and I've seen it, you know, throughout my whole life.  You know, and I'm not saying that all cops are bad, because I actually throughout high school and things of that nature, I'm around them all the time and they are not all bad. But when you see the videos that's going on and you can see not only my hometown but all over America, you continue to see the acts of violence towards my kind, I can't do nothing but to speak about it and see the common denominator. But not one time have I ever said, you know, let's act violent towards cops.  I just said that what's going on in our community is not okay, and we fear for that and we fear for our lives.  It's something that we go on every single day as a black man and a black woman and a black kid and a black girl, we fear; we fear that moment where we are pulled over or -- I just seen something, I believe yesterday or the day before, of a guy in Wisconsin was renting a house, and the next door neighbor called the police on him, and the police came in the house without a warrant, without anything, and arrested the guy, a black man because he was sitting out on the porch, and if you can't tell me that's not racial profiling, then I don't know what the hell -- or what the hell we are looking at. But I do not condone violence towards anyone, police, black people, white people, anyone of color, anyone not of color, because that's not going to ever make this world or America what we want it to be. So -- and I have zero comment on the sheriff."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Do you want to talk about the game again?  The turnovers you had, the turnover issues, is there a common denominator with where those are coming?  Is it something Denver is doing defensively?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   It's some of the risk passes that we're making, including myself.  I mean, I had five turnovers in the first half and one in the second half, so I understood what I was doing in the first half and made an adjustment.  There are some passes that we have been able to complete throughout this season, but versus Denver we have to be a little bit more careful and make more -- more sound plays with the ball, and protect the ball, because like we always preach, every possession is very important.  When you give up 25 points off 16 turnovers, that's not good.  We did the same thing in Game 2, we had 24 turnovers and luckily it didn't bite us in the butt but it should have. We just got to do a better job of that and it's a conscious effort that not only starts with me because I'm the point guard of the team, and it trickles down to everyone else."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Murray had that elbow, and some people on the bench thought it was maybe Flagrant 2.  Talk us through that play and did you think it was?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I was just setting a screen and his elbow got high and was able to strike me -- strike me across the jaw.  I don't -- I don't care about flagrant ones or flagrant twos.  I don't want him to come out of the game.  I like the competition.  I don't think it was blatant but I don't know mindset, but I don't think he did it on purpose.  I was okay with it.  You know, went down for a little bit.  Got back up and was ready to play.  I was cool with the ruling.  I was okay with them saying a flagrant one.  I ain't here to fight."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA WESTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: LAKERS VS. NUGGETS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=159834",
    "date": "September 20, 2020",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. Last time you were in the playoffs, you made a couple game-winners, and that seemed to be something that has become such a big part of your skill set and persona on the court these days.  What's it like to see a teammate that clearly you have great chemistry with that you wanted to have be in L.A. with you be the guy to make that shot and win this game for you guys?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Did you see my reaction?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. It's all smiles.",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   No, did you see my reaction after he made it?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I didn't get to see it.",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I tried to chase him down just like every last one of the teammates and staff that we had out there.  Special moment for a special player.  Happy to be a part of it."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What does it take to want to take the pressure to take on a shot like that, and the fact that he was able to have that kind of moment, what will it do for his confidence going forward in situations like this?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   It's not about making a shot.  It's about having a belief of just taking it, for one, and living with the result.  I think right back to our game right before COVID hit.  We played Brooklyn at home and he had a similar shot right on that left wing in front of their bench to win the game and he missed it.  He was down on himself, but at the end of the day, I told him, if you're open, and I was able to drive that particular game and find him wide open and he just missed it. But it's just the confidence to take the shot.  You're not going to make them all, but the belief to just take it and live with the results is what it's all about.  Tonight was his moment.  Tonight was his moment to find a space, hunt the ball down and one of our top 10 assists leaders, Rondo, found him and he knocked it down.  A big-time play."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Even before that, he and Jokic were trading buckets.  Were you getting the sense that he was sort of rising to that particular duel, even before that game-winning shot?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   No, it's not about an individual matchup.  It's about us trying to execute and him just coming through for us. That's what he did.  It wasn't, okay, your turn, my turn.  It's about playing the game and trying to find ways to make an impact. Obviously, those two big shots that he had at the end, one was the floater to take the lead.  Joker was able to get the tip-in, and he comes back in with the three.  Just big-time plays, like I said, for a big-time player."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. AD is the kind of player that has had the skill set to do that for a long time but he is now with a team that is at a championship level competing for a championship, being in the Conference Finals.  What do you think that's like for him to finally get to be in the big moments?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I don't know.  That's actually an AD question.  Just happy to have him.  I know what he brought to the table.  I know what he's about.  I know his skill set.  That's why I wanted him here so badly."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You didn't have a timeout on that last play.  Were you able to talk about scenarios in which something like that could have happened?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   That's what this floor right here that we're all on right now is all about.  It's the practices; it's the shootarounds.  We talk about every single scenario possible:  up three; down three; up two; down two; do we have a foul to give, do we not; do we have a timeout, do we not; are we going full-court; half-court; BOB, which is baseline out-of-bounds; SOB, sideline out-of-bounds.  You talk about all those things.  You want to be a championship club, you have to be able to do that on the fly. So knowing we didn't have a timeout, we were able to get into a situation to a set that we worked on in practice and get right to it. The first option, for me if Do [Rondo] saw me over the top, and if not, AD flashes. And the rest is history."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You said it's not making the shot; it's taking it.   Caruso similar, took it right away.  He's been really vocal in huddles and stuff like that.  Where does he fit on the leadership hierarchy on the team and how important is his confidence to step up and take a shot?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   When you are trying to play high-level basketball, you have to have high-level IQ players, and he's one of them.  And not only does he have high-level IQ, but he also plays with high energy.  We know what we're going to get out of him every night. It's not about him making shots.  We know he's going to defend and he's going to play at a level that he's capable of playing at, and we all know that once he checks into the game every single night.  We know what to expect out of him.  To be honest, when he makes shots, it's extra credit for us.  But he puts that work in on his offensive skill set to get better and better.   We love everything about him."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. If I could jump off the court for a second, if I read the sweatshirt correctly, it said, \"Change isn't made from watching on the sidelines, you're more than a vote,\" a sweatshirt that you wore on the way in.  I wanted to ask you about that and where your mindset is as this one continues, and where your mind is outside of the court, I should say.",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   For sure.  I know we're here playing the game, but I'm not losing the fact of what's important, as well.  More than a vote, it's about protecting black voters and voter suppression that goes on in our communities. Like you said, change isn't made by sitting on the sidelines.  That's one of our slogans and we're very proud of that.  Getting the people that want to join us, getting them gear and wearing the T-shirt and wearing the hats and wearing the hoodies, because when they go in their community, that's something that they can continue to enlighten, continue to educate, continue to make people empowered about this movement. We always talk about change in our communities, and now we have an opportunity.  We have an opportunity to really create change for the better and we look forward to this opportunity."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Going back to 2009, do you remember the bank shot against Orlando?  What was it like going to sleep to, hit a shot that you dream of growing up, isn't that what that situation is?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   To be completely honest, man, it was probably one of the greatest moments of my career up until that point.  Just knowing the situation, we were about to go down 0-2 and we had home-court advantage.  We knew how powerful that Orlando team was, playing against actually my teammate now in Dwight.  So for me to be able to hit that shot was a huge moment for me.  I was still a young kid at the time, so big-time. The one thing I wish AD had tonight with the shot that he made, I wish we were playing at Staples.  We miss our fans so much and I can imagine in -- I probably would have blue the roof off Staples Center, AD hitting that shot with our crowd.  I would have loved to have that moment -- I know what it felt like for me when I was able to hit that shot that you mentioned against Orlando, Game 2 of the Eastern Conference Finals at the buzzer."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. AD has talked about how much he's leaned on you throughout the playoffs, and obviously he's played outstanding in the Western Conference Finals.  Curious what's the biggest thing that you've tried to instill in him during that time?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I think just staying even-keeled.  That's what it's all about.  The playoffs and the postseason, the more you advance into the postseason, the emotions and the adversity, it's going to be a roller coaster at times.  No matter if you're up, no matter if you're down, being able to keep your composure and your mindset on the main thing is very important.  This is the furthest he's gone in his career up to this point, and. I'm just happy to be here with him to give him any advice and lean on me.  To be completely honest, in the second half, I leaned on him, and he brought us home.  So I just tried to set the example early on, and we leaned on him, especially in the fourth quarter, and he brought us home."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Anthony came to L.A. asking for this pressure and asking for this burden to be a great player in the playoffs.  This is obviously a process that you've gone through.  What is the challenge for an athlete both to ask for that, to seek that out, but then also to perform when that moment comes?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I don't know.  I think for me, it's always been about the man in the arena, the quote from Theodore Roosevelt.  It's about the guy that's in the arena that's gone through everything -- the blood, the sweat, the tears and, in our situation, the competition. I's about the work that you put in and the belief in yourself.  It's not about the doubters or the naysayers or the people who are going to try to talk to you and slander you and bring you down every single day.  It's not about them because they have never been in the arena.  They don't understand. AD, he knows how special he is and when he doesn't, I'll be the first one to tell him how special he is.  He wanted to be here.  I'm happy he wanted to be here, because if he didn't, we wouldn't have a moment like tonight.  That's what it's all about. You put that pressure on yourself when you don't really care what other people think, because what other people think doesn't really matter because they don't understand.  Anybody can talk from outside, but if they got into the ring or they got into the arena, probably 10 times out of 10, they [expletive] their pants."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA WESTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: LAKERS VS. NUGGETS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=159728",
    "date": "September 18, 2020",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. With you and AD and then in the lineup when Dwight joined you in the frontline, what are ways you can impose your physicality, athleticism, size, how can this play out in this series?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   We just tried to follow the game plan.  Try not to foul and put teams on the free throw line because those are easy points and we just trust our game plan.  We trust our, what we've been doing all throughout the course of this whole year.  We have a lot of length out there with myself, AD, Dwight, KCP and Danny at the start of that third quarter, and we were able to get some deflections, get some turnovers and get out and do what we do best on the break. You know, just having that type of size and that athleticism helps tremendously."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You've talked about using Game 1 as a feel-out game.  Was there anything even after the first quarter that you guys identified when things seemed to switch for you defensively starting in the second quarter?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Well, yeah, we knew the first quarter definitely wasn't Laker basketball, Laker defense.  We just had some break downs.  We had some break downs, took a quarter for us to kind of figure it out.  Not saying that we fully figured them out because it's too early in the series to say that but started to get a better feel and rhythm defensively and started to get some stops in the second quarter and build that lead up going into halftime."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. We spoke about the MVP award with you in March and you said it's not something that's ever motivated you and your true motivation is to be considered the best ever, but when you see the results come out today, knowing you've won it four times but now you've come in second four times, what's that feeling like for you, and what did you think of the results?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   Pissed me off.  That's my true answer.  It pissed me off because out of 101 votes, I got 16 first-place votes.  That's what pissed me off more than anything.  You know, not saying that the winner wasn't deserving of the MVP. But that pissed me off.  And I finished second a lot in my career, either from a championship, and now four times as an MVP.  You know, like I said, I never came into this league to be MVP or to be a champion.  I've always just wanted to get better and better every single day, and those things will take care of itself.  But some things is just out of my hand and some things you can't control. But it pissed me off."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Did you surprise yourself by the reaction you had when you saw those results?  Did you know that -- I'm just wondering if you knew that you would have this strong of a reaction to seeing those numbers.",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   No."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Do you feel like the MVP criteria is something that rewards the Most Valuable Player in the league?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I don't know.  I'm not going to sit up here and talk about what the criteria should be or what it is. It's changed over the years since I've gotten into the league, I know that.  You know, it's just changed.  It's changed a lot.  You know, sometimes it's the best player on the best team.  Sometimes it's the guy with the best season statistically.  Sometimes -- it's changed over the course -- over the course of my career.  I mean, you don't know.  You don't know. But you know, Giannis had a hell of a season, I can definitely say that."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. In the past when you've had, call them slight or whatever, when you've finished second in the past, did it bother you as much?  And the next question would be, how much of your strong reaction do you think has to do with the fact that you've done what you've done in year 17 at 35 with a new team?  Does that factor into your kind of emotion here?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I mean, I'm fine.  Don't get it twisted.  I'm going back to my room.  I'm perfectly fine.  We're 1-0 in the Western Conference Finals.  I'm absolutely fine.  So don't -- like I was pissed off at the reaction earlier when I saw it.  I'm absolutely great now.  I'm going back to my room, drink some wine and sleep very well tonight.  Let's not get it twisted.  I'm great. It's just the voting scale is a little weird to me sometimes.  I mean, it you take 2012.  If you just stick with me -- or 2012-13, I had a chance to be Defensive Player of the Year and also MVP in the same season.  And that year [Marc] Gasol was [voted] Defensive Player of the Year, but he made Second Team All-Defense, okay. So that doesn't make sense.  It's like being MVP of the league but you make Second Team All-NBA.  That's when I really started to look at things kind of like differently.  I was like, how does that even make any sense.  It's like being Rookie of the Year but you make Second Team All-Rookie. And then I looked at the Most Improved this year, and rightfully so Brandon Ingram was amazing and I thought he should have won it.  But did you see the vote that Devonte' Graham got?  He averaged four points last year compared to 17 and a half.  If that's not improving, what is? And it's a weird thing sometimes that you just have -- I don't know how much we are really watching the game of basketball or are we just in the narration mode, the narrative."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Given all this team has been through and all you've had to lead them through, how would you compare this to years you've won MVP?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:   I don't even remember.  I don't remember, actually.  I don't know.  I don't remember.  I don't remember to be completely honest.  It would be hard for me to answer that question."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA WESTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: LAKERS VS. NUGGETS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=159648",
    "date": "September 17, 2020",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. LeBron, the All-NBA Team, 16 times now.  It passes Duncan, Kobe, Kareem.  There have been a lot of milestones like this.  What does it mean about longevity when you think about those threes names?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Like I said in my post, when I posted about it, I'm truly blessed.  I'm kind of at a loss for words.  I've been fortunate enough to be able to take care of my body, push my body to the limits, that maybe at times when I was younger I didn't think I could get to. I never put a ceiling on what I can do in this league.  I think one of the things I pride myself on is being available to my teammates.  It's allowed me to sit here at this point and talk about what we're talking about now. Anytime I'm linked with some of the GOATs that have played this game, it's an unbelievable thing.  You mentioned Timmy D, Kareem, Kobe as well.  Just some GOATs that have played this game, paved the way for myself.  Hopefully I'll leave it, when I'm done with my career, in a better place than what I started because of what they did, the groundwork they did, the examples they set.  Just blessed to be a part of this."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You guys have played six games in the last 20 days, in part because of winning 4-1 both times.  How does that feel physically in terms of basketball rhythm, rest?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   It doesn't feel like anything, to be honest.  It feels like we're preparing for an extremely dangerous, extremely well-coached, extremely great team in the Nuggets.  That's been our only focus.  At the same time, we've also been putting in our work individually before we knew who our opponent was, getting our individual work in, team work in, keeping our minds, bodies and souls up to speed, not losing focus of what the main thing is. We're here to compete for a championship.  That's what our mindset has been, no matter how many days we've had in between games, who our opponent has been.  We respect all our opponents because they're great teams."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You know what it's like to come back from a 3-1 deficit, how difficult that is.  The Nuggets have done it twice.  What does that say about them as a team and competitors?  And the second question, is your thumb OK?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   To the first question, very resilient, very confident, very driven, very well-coached team.  It takes a lot of energy, effort, a lot of desperation to be able to come back from a 3-1 deficit.  They did it twice.  So the respect level is out of this world for what we have for this ballclub.  That's how we're going into this series, understanding what they're capable of, where they stand. Yes, my thumb is fine.  I don't remember what game it was in the Houston series, I tried to block a shot.  My thumb got caught in the rim a little bit.  Just trying to do the treatment and keep myself healthy for the game.  But it won't affect me in any way, shape or form."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Michael Malone, you go way back.  Always shown him love when you've been playing against him.  What allowed you guys to create that connection, that respect and bond back when you were in Cleveland together?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   When you work hard on your craft, you see others working just as hard on their craft, it becomes organic and it becomes mutual respect.  I know how much Coach Mo put into our schemes, put into our productivity, put into what we needed to do to go out and win ballgames when we were together in Cleveland.  I saw that. So the respect level, just seeing what he was putting into his craft, it made it easy for me to grow likeness to him."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. A lot of young guys on this Denver team, but there's at least one familiar face in Paul Millsap, a guy you played in the Playoffs a couple times.  How do you look back on your battles over the years, what you think it will be like to see him in other Playoff series, what he's done for them?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   He's a winning guy.  He was that at Utah in his early days, Atlanta and Denver as well.  It's not hard to implement winning players into any situation.  That's why it's been so seamless for him.  A guy who is always consistent, who does what it takes to help the team win and is always like a sense of calmness.  He's a veteran.  He's been in Playoff matchups. He's been in big games.  For the young guys, someone they can always lean on."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. You have high expectations of yourself.  With AD and the way he works, is anything you've accomplished or pushed yourself this year a reflection of having him around, seeing the way he works?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I want to say no because I've never needed anyone to push me.  I'm an only child so I had to push myself.  But in the sense of being older than AD, I think it's showing him how much I put into my craft, and hopefully it trickles down to him. I feel like I would be cheating him if he came to be a part of this and I was cheating the game in some way, shape or form.  It's not an example I would ever set for any of my teammates, not just AD, but anybody I ever played with.  You can ask any of my teammates.  I just put that much work into my craft.  That's what it's about."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Nikola can do a lot of things, score, rebound.  Are you drawn to the way he can see the floor and pass?  Seems like you share that ability.  How much joy do you get out of that part of your game?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   It's probably the best part of the game, being able to get your teammates involved, putting the ball on time, on target, being able to see things happen before they happen, seeing the reward go to your teammates.  It's just the best part of the game."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Do you see that in him?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Yes.  It's just infectious.  When you have the best player on the team, one of the best players on the team, not really caring about himself at all for the better of the team, that sends a message to the rest of the group."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. (Question about peaking at the right time.)",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   Well, it's great to be playing the way we're playing right now.  It's the postseason, and that's when you want to kind of hit your stride.  We still have a ceiling that we feel like we can get better.  It's our job not to put a cap on where we can go.  We know as the series goes on, we start to get more and more comfortable with our opponent, with our schemes, with our system of what we want to do.  We hope we can continue that in this series. Starting from Game 1, being as great as we can be, then figuring out ways we can be even better going into Game 2, so on, so on."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. The Clippers-Nuggets Game 7, we were pretty shocked by the way it ended for the Clippers.  Do you have a different view?  Were you surprised?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I don't have a comment about it really.  I was just sitting back and watching the game from a fan's perspective, seeing big shots be made, big plays being made, missed shots, things of that nature.  I was also as a scout, scouting both teams at the same time.  I was trying to get as many log-in minutes for myself personally scouting both teams at the same time because we knew Game 7 will decide who we'll play.  That was kind of my mindset."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Any part of you that got caught up in the chance to face those guys, kind of settle it?  That's something we talk about.",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   What were we settling?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. The discussion about L.A., the clash of the two top teams.",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   (Shaking head.)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Frank was praising you and AD not just for your talent but the way that you guys set the tone throughout the season with creating a sense of urgency with the club in practice and film sessions, games.  How do you approach that overall this season?",
        "answer": "LeBRON JAMES:   I mean, it's just who I am personally.  I don't like the way season ended for us last year, especially for myself with the injury, the things I went through last year personally, then with our ballclub.  I didn't like the way that ended. My mindset coming into the season was already pretty much locked in just from the summertime, putting in my work, me training, getting up at 4 a.m., train before I was shooting \"Space Jam,\" things of that nature. When we were able to get AD and acquire Coach Vogel, having the battles I had with him, his Indiana Pacers team, I already knew what he would bring to the table as well. I was excited about the opportunity to link with Coach Vogel, the players we were starting to sign, things of that nature.  That's what it's all about.  Just excited, man, to get back to work whenever that was happening.  Like I told you guys earlier in the season, my mom told me, Don't talk about it, be about it. I didn't really say much. Just go out and do your job and live with the results."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR 2020",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=157181",
    "date": "February 16, 2020",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR 2020",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=157145",
    "date": "February 15, 2020",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND 2019",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=147131",
    "date": "February 17, 2019",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR 2019",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=147096",
    "date": "February 16, 2019",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS vs WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=140730",
    "date": "June 8, 2018",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS vs WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=140688",
    "date": "June 7, 2018",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS vs WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=140680",
    "date": "June 6, 2018",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS vs WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=140654",
    "date": "June 5, 2018",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS vs WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=140635",
    "date": "June 3, 2018",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS vs WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=140543",
    "date": "June 2, 2018",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS vs WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=140455",
    "date": "May 31, 2018",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS vs WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=140373",
    "date": "May 30, 2018",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS vs CELTICS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=140327",
    "date": "May 27, 2018",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS vs CELTICS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=140250",
    "date": "May 25, 2018",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS vs CELTICS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=140152",
    "date": "May 23, 2018",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS vs CELTICS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=140085",
    "date": "May 21, 2018",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS vs CELTICS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=139985",
    "date": "May 19, 2018",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS vs CELTICS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=139787",
    "date": "May 15, 2018",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS vs CELTICS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=139716",
    "date": "May 13, 2018",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR 2018",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=137423",
    "date": "February 18, 2018",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR 2018",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=137375",
    "date": "February 17, 2018",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CLEVELAND VS GOLDEN STATE",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=131026",
    "date": "June 12, 2017",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CLEVELAND VS GOLDEN STATE",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=130695",
    "date": "June 11, 2017",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CLEVELAND VS GOLDEN STATE",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=130656",
    "date": "June 9, 2017",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CLEVELAND VS GOLDEN STATE",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=130610",
    "date": "June 8, 2017",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CLEVELAND VS GOLDEN STATE",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=130599",
    "date": "June 7, 2017",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CLEVELAND VS GOLDEN STATE",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=130564",
    "date": "June 6, 2017",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CLEVELAND VS GOLDEN STATE",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=130471",
    "date": "June 3, 2017",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CLEVELAND VS GOLDEN STATE",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=130419",
    "date": "June 1, 2017",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CLEVELAND VS GOLDEN STATE",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=130356",
    "date": "May 31, 2017",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CELTICS VS CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=130161",
    "date": "May 25, 2017",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CELTICS VS CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=130083",
    "date": "May 23, 2017",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CELTICS VS CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=130006",
    "date": "May 21, 2017",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CELTICS VS CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=129916",
    "date": "May 19, 2017",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CELTICS VS CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=129827",
    "date": "May 18, 2017",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CELTICS VS CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=129803",
    "date": "May 17, 2017",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CELTICS VS CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=129743",
    "date": "May 16, 2017",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=127156",
    "date": "February 18, 2017",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=120673",
    "date": "June 19, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=120611",
    "date": "June 18, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=120538",
    "date": "June 16, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=120489",
    "date": "June 15, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=120465",
    "date": "June 13, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=120420",
    "date": "June 12, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=120389",
    "date": "June 10, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=120323",
    "date": "June 9, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=120315",
    "date": "June 8, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=120271",
    "date": "June 7, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=119997",
    "date": "June 5, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=119929",
    "date": "June 4, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=119878",
    "date": "June 3, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=119867",
    "date": "June 2, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=119811",
    "date": "June 1, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: RAPTORS v CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=119675",
    "date": "May 27, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: RAPTORS v CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=119569",
    "date": "May 25, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: RAPTORS v CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=119484",
    "date": "May 23, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: RAPTORS v CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=119406",
    "date": "May 22, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: RAPTORS v CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=119393",
    "date": "May 21, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: RAPTORS v CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=119288",
    "date": "May 19, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: RAPTORS v CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=119234",
    "date": "May 18, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: RAPTORS v CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=119219",
    "date": "May 17, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=116704",
    "date": "February 14, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=116663",
    "date": "February 13, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=116643",
    "date": "February 12, 2016",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=110342",
    "date": "June 16, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=110294",
    "date": "June 14, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=110229",
    "date": "June 13, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=110195",
    "date": "June 11, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=110115",
    "date": "June 10, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=110110",
    "date": "June 9, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=109861",
    "date": "June 7, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=109805",
    "date": "June 6, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=109773",
    "date": "June 5, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=109765",
    "date": "June 4, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v WARRIORS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=109714",
    "date": "June 3, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS PREVIEW",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_conference.php?id=109682",
    "date": "June 1, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS v HAWKS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=109458",
    "date": "May 26, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS v HAWKS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=109410",
    "date": "May 25, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS v HAWKS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=109400",
    "date": "May 24, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS v HAWKS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=109297",
    "date": "May 23, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS v HAWKS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=109274",
    "date": "May 22, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS v HAWKS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=109168",
    "date": "May 21, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS v HAWKS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=109162",
    "date": "May 20, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=106385",
    "date": "February 15, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=106285",
    "date": "February 13, 2015",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "CLEVELAND CAVALIERS MEDIA CONFERENCE",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_conference.php?id=101699",
    "date": "August 8, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=100063",
    "date": "June 15, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=99997",
    "date": "June 14, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=99915",
    "date": "June 12, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=99859",
    "date": "June 11, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=99834",
    "date": "June 10, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=99566",
    "date": "June 8, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=99496",
    "date": "June 7, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=99468",
    "date": "June 6, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=99462",
    "date": "June 5, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=99414",
    "date": "June 4, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v PACERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=99328",
    "date": "May 30, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v PACERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=99252",
    "date": "May 29, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v PACERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=99224",
    "date": "May 28, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v PACERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=99158",
    "date": "May 26, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v PACERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=99062",
    "date": "May 25, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v PACERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=99045",
    "date": "May 24, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v PACERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=98902",
    "date": "May 23, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v PACERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=98806",
    "date": "May 22, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v PACERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=98758",
    "date": "May 20, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v PACERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=98706",
    "date": "May 19, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v PACERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=98690",
    "date": "May 18, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=96204",
    "date": "February 16, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=96136",
    "date": "February 14, 2014",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: SPURS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=90245",
    "date": "June 20, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: SPURS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=90175",
    "date": "June 19, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: SPURS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=90155",
    "date": "June 18, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: SPURS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=90119",
    "date": "June 16, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: SPURS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=90017",
    "date": "June 15, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: SPURS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=89955",
    "date": "June 13, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: SPURS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=89889",
    "date": "June 12, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: SPURS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=89837",
    "date": "June 9, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: SPURS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=89777",
    "date": "June 8, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: SPURS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=89741",
    "date": "June 7, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: SPURS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=89720",
    "date": "June 6, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: SPURS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=89661",
    "date": "June 5, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: PACERS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=89628",
    "date": "June 3, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: PACERS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=89571",
    "date": "June 1, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: PACERS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=89503",
    "date": "May 31, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: PACERS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=89491",
    "date": "May 30, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: PACERS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=89451",
    "date": "May 28, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: PACERS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=89426",
    "date": "May 27, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: PACERS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=89411",
    "date": "May 26, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: PACERS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=89290",
    "date": "May 24, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: PACERS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=89176",
    "date": "May 23, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: PACERS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=89144",
    "date": "May 22, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=86563",
    "date": "February 15, 2013",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v THUNDER",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80796",
    "date": "June 21, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v THUNDER",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80801",
    "date": "June 21, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v THUNDER",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80738",
    "date": "June 20, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v THUNDER",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80719",
    "date": "June 19, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v THUNDER",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80677",
    "date": "June 18, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v THUNDER",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80668",
    "date": "June 17, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v THUNDER",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80593",
    "date": "June 16, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v THUNDER",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80553",
    "date": "June 14, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v THUNDER",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80495",
    "date": "June 13, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v THUNDER",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80479",
    "date": "June 12, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: HEAT v THUNDER",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80455",
    "date": "June 11, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CELTICS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80422",
    "date": "June 9, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CELTICS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80380",
    "date": "June 7, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CELTICS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80344",
    "date": "June 6, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CELTICS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80207",
    "date": "June 2, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CELTICS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80186",
    "date": "June 1, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CELTICS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80093",
    "date": "May 30, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CELTICS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80054",
    "date": "May 29, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CELTICS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=80025",
    "date": "May 28, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=77791",
    "date": "February 26, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=77692",
    "date": "February 24, 2012",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: MAVERICKS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71965",
    "date": "June 12, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: MAVERICKS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71912",
    "date": "June 11, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: MAVERICKS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71885",
    "date": "June 9, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: MAVERICKS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71838",
    "date": "June 8, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: MAVERICKS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71817",
    "date": "June 7, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: MAVERICKS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71777",
    "date": "June 6, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: MAVERICKS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71764",
    "date": "June 5, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: MAVERICKS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71685",
    "date": "June 4, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: MAVERICKS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71646",
    "date": "June 2, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: MAVERICKS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71580",
    "date": "June 1, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: MAVERICKS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71571",
    "date": "May 31, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: MAVERICKS v HEAT",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71528",
    "date": "May 30, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v BULLS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71393",
    "date": "May 26, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v BULLS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71322",
    "date": "May 25, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v BULLS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71303",
    "date": "May 24, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v BULLS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71256",
    "date": "May 23, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v BULLS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71241",
    "date": "May 22, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v BULLS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71187",
    "date": "May 21, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v BULLS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71156",
    "date": "May 20, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v BULLS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71070",
    "date": "May 17, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: HEAT v BULLS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=71059",
    "date": "May 16, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=69114",
    "date": "February 20, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=69044",
    "date": "February 18, 2011",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA SEASON GAME: HEAT v CELTICS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=67273",
    "date": "October 26, 2010",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "MIAMI HEAT MEDIA CONFERENCE",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=64815",
    "date": "July 9, 2010",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "MIAMI HEAT MEDIA CONFERENCE",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=64825",
    "date": "July 9, 2010",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=61431",
    "date": "February 14, 2010",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: MAGIC v CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=56741",
    "date": "May 29, 2009",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: MAGIC v CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=56757",
    "date": "May 28, 2009",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: MAGIC v CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=56795",
    "date": "May 26, 2009",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: MAGIC v CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=56806",
    "date": "May 25, 2009",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: MAGIC v CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=56850",
    "date": "May 24, 2009",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: MAGIC v CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=56903",
    "date": "May 22, 2009",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: MAGIC v CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=56921",
    "date": "May 21, 2009",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: MAGIC v CAVALIERS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=56930",
    "date": "May 20, 2009",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=54387",
    "date": "February 15, 2009",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=54326",
    "date": "February 13, 2009",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=47645",
    "date": "February 17, 2008",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=47598",
    "date": "February 15, 2008",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=43656",
    "date": "June 14, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=43607",
    "date": "June 13, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=43596",
    "date": "June 12, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=43575",
    "date": "June 10, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=43534",
    "date": "June 9, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=43512",
    "date": "June 8, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=43500",
    "date": "June 7, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA FINALS: CAVALIERS v SPURS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=43446",
    "date": "June 6, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS v PISTONS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=43402",
    "date": "June 2, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS v PISTONS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=43348",
    "date": "May 31, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS v PISTONS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=43279",
    "date": "May 29, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS v PISTONS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=43242",
    "date": "May 28, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS v PISTONS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=43229",
    "date": "May 27, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS v PISTONS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=43161",
    "date": "May 26, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS v PISTONS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=43131",
    "date": "May 25, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS v PISTONS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=43109",
    "date": "May 24, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA EASTERN CONFERENCE FINALS: CAVALIERS v PISTONS",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=43017",
    "date": "May 21, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=41284",
    "date": "February 18, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=41233",
    "date": "February 16, 2007",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=28617",
    "date": "February 19, 2006",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=40457",
    "date": "February 20, 2005",
    "qa": []
  },
  {
    "title": "NBA ALL-STAR WEEKEND",
    "url": "http://www.asapsports.com/show_interview.php?id=31692",
    "date": "February 18, 2005",
    "qa": [
      {
        "question": "Q. You're the busiest man in show business.  How are you going to get it all done this weekend?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:  It's called a schedule.  Everything is in time frames, to my liking.  I'm going to take care of business on and off the court and get everything done."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What's it like to be a prodigy?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:  Can you rephrase that?  Give me a better sense, I don't understand that."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. What's it like to be so good at something, a maestro",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:  I don't even look at it like that.  I just go out, just play my game.  I'm glad I've got the God-given talent to go out and showcase my talent.  I don't take that for granted.  I'm happy to go out every night and play the game of basketball."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Was there any chance you would not play tonight?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:  No, the only chance would have been me missing the shoot-around this morning, but that's not going to keep me out of no game.  The fans are here for us to come play and I'm not going to sit out."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Obviously it's been tough for Carmelo to be here in his home court and not be able to play the All-Star Game, and he put extra motivation into tonight's game.  Was it nice to see him play as well as he did?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:  Always.  I know he can play this game of basketball.  Things have not went his way this year, but he's starting to get his mind straight and not worry about the off-the-court things.  I'm so happy for him he got the MVP tonight.  It's supposed to work out this way.  It's going to work out the best for him."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. A lot of the so-called big names don't do the Slam Dunk any more, if you were completely healthy, would you have done it and how do you feel about that?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:  I think it would have been a great possibility to be doing that.  Right now, you could just see that my jumping ability right now is not where I want it to be.  I think if I was very healthy or 100 percent healthy, like I was before, there would be a great possibility of me being in the contest."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. I understand Usher is going to buy a piece of the Cavaliers with this transaction, do you have any aspiration in music or movies?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:  No, not right now.  My main focus is on winning basketball games, helping my team get better and taking of business."
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. Why don't the big guys don't do it any more (dunk contest)?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:  Because all the dunks is taken.  Ain't no more dunks.  If we come up with some new dunks, people might do it.  Every time it's a dunk contest, people say \"we have seen that before.\""
      },
      {
        "question": "Q. How is the learning curve speeded up for you so fast to where in this second year, you're really just seem to understand things in advance?",
        "answer": "LEBRON JAMES:  Just being a student of the game, just wanting to get better.  Knowing that if I got better that my teammates will also get better and that it will help our team.  That's all it's about. End of FastScripts..."
      }
    ]
  }
]